{
  "name": "JPDB 25K",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "同質",
      "answer": "どうしつ",
      "meaning": "same quality, same nature, homogeneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "既読",
      "answer": "きどく",
      "meaning": "already read"
    },
    {
      "question": "汽笛",
      "answer": "きてき",
      "meaning": "steam whistle"
    },
    {
      "question": "一体全体",
      "answer": "いったいぜんたい",
      "meaning": "... the heck (e.g. 'what the heck?'), ... in the world (e.g. 'why in the world?'), ... on earth (e.g"
    },
    {
      "question": "子守",
      "answer": "こもり",
      "meaning": "nursemaid, nanny, babysitter, child-minding, babysitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "呂律",
      "answer": "ろれつ",
      "meaning": "articulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "気紛れ",
      "answer": "きまぐれ",
      "meaning": "whim, caprice, whimsy, fickle, moody, uneven temper"
    },
    {
      "question": "下駄",
      "answer": "げた",
      "meaning": "geta, Japanese wooden clogs, turn (in set-type proofing), upside-down character"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来心",
      "answer": "できごころ",
      "meaning": "sudden impulse, passing fancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚立",
      "answer": "きゃたつ",
      "meaning": "stepladder, steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝶番",
      "answer": "ちょうつがい,ちょうばん",
      "meaning": "hinge, joint (esp. an anatomical joint)"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂れ流し",
      "answer": "たれながし",
      "meaning": "incontinence, soiling oneself, wetting one's pants, discharge (e.g. of contaminants), effluence"
    },
    {
      "question": "気位",
      "answer": "きぐらい",
      "meaning": "pride, haughtiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "立役者",
      "answer": "たてやくしゃ",
      "meaning": "leading actor, star, leading figure, central figure, key figure, leading spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "罹る",
      "answer": "かかる",
      "meaning": "to contract (a disease), to suffer from"
    },
    {
      "question": "傲然",
      "answer": "ごうぜん",
      "meaning": "proud, arrogant, haughty"
    },
    {
      "question": "静電気",
      "answer": "せいでんき",
      "meaning": "static electricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗澹",
      "answer": "あんたん",
      "meaning": "dark, gloomy, somber, depressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷え冷え",
      "answer": "ひえびえ",
      "meaning": "with an extreme cold (i.e. temperature), lonelily, lonesomely, (acting) coldly (toward someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口中",
      "answer": "こうちゅう",
      "meaning": "interior of the mouth, oral cavity"
    },
    {
      "question": "撲殺",
      "answer": "ぼくさつ",
      "meaning": "beat to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕餉",
      "answer": "ゆうげ",
      "meaning": "evening meal, supper, dinner"
    },
    {
      "question": "血抜き",
      "answer": "ちぬき",
      "meaning": "letting out blood prior to cooking, draining blood from meat, fish, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "栄",
      "answer": "ロン,えい,はやし",
      "meaning": "winning by picking up a discarded tile, honor, honour, glory, prosperity, ornament, adornment, decor"
    },
    {
      "question": "無色",
      "answer": "むしょく",
      "meaning": "colourless, colorless, achromatic, neutral (position), impartial"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝耳に水",
      "answer": "ねみみにみず",
      "meaning": "bolt from the blue, great surprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "人の口",
      "answer": "ひとのくち",
      "meaning": "what people say, rumours, public opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "双葉",
      "answer": "ふたば",
      "meaning": "seed leaves (of a dicot), cotyledons, bud, sprout, early stages, very beginning"
    },
    {
      "question": "三世",
      "answer": "さんせい,さんぜ,みよ",
      "meaning": "three generations, third generation (immigrant, monarch, etc.), sansei, three temporal states of exi"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥棒猫",
      "answer": "どろぼうねこ",
      "meaning": "thieving cat, adulterer, homewrecker"
    },
    {
      "question": "独裁者",
      "answer": "どくさいしゃ",
      "meaning": "dictator, despot"
    },
    {
      "question": "時系列",
      "answer": "じけいれつ",
      "meaning": "chronological order, time series"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀟洒",
      "answer": "しょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "stylish, smart, elegant, chic, refined, trim, neat"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜂起",
      "answer": "ほうき",
      "meaning": "uprising, revolt"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼酎",
      "answer": "しょうちゅう",
      "meaning": "shōchū, Japanese spirit distilled from sweet potatoes, rice, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "寝食",
      "answer": "しんしょく",
      "meaning": "bed and food, eating and sleeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "藩",
      "answer": "はん",
      "meaning": "feudal domain (Edo and early Meiji periods, precursor to current prefectures), fiefdom, province, cl"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚礼",
      "answer": "こんれい",
      "meaning": "marriage ceremony, wedding"
    },
    {
      "question": "無二",
      "answer": "むに",
      "meaning": "peerless, matchless"
    },
    {
      "question": "一食",
      "answer": "いっしょく,いちじき",
      "meaning": "one meal, one meal (a day)"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼虫",
      "answer": "ようちゅう",
      "meaning": "larva, grub, maggot"
    },
    {
      "question": "炊き出し",
      "answer": "たきだし",
      "meaning": "emergency food distribution (esp. cooked rice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟膏",
      "answer": "なんこう",
      "meaning": "ointment, salve"
    },
    {
      "question": "漂流",
      "answer": "ひょうりゅう",
      "meaning": "drifting, drift, being adrift"
    },
    {
      "question": "箔",
      "answer": "はく",
      "meaning": "foil, (gold, etc.) leaf, prestige"
    },
    {
      "question": "一進一退",
      "answer": "いっしんいったい",
      "meaning": "now advancing and now retreating, ebb and flow, seesawing, taking alternately favorable and unfavora"
    },
    {
      "question": "自主性",
      "answer": "じしゅせい",
      "meaning": "autonomy, independence"
    },
    {
      "question": "便利屋",
      "answer": "べんりや",
      "meaning": "handyman, utility man, odd-job man"
    },
    {
      "question": "感無量",
      "answer": "かんむりょう",
      "meaning": "deep emotion, being filled with emotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "併合",
      "answer": "へいごう",
      "meaning": "merger, joining into one, amalgamation, melding, merging, annexation, absorption"
    },
    {
      "question": "死期",
      "answer": "しき",
      "meaning": "time of death, one's final hour, one's end"
    },
    {
      "question": "世界史",
      "answer": "せかいし",
      "meaning": "world history, international history"
    },
    {
      "question": "専門学校",
      "answer": "せんもんがっこう",
      "meaning": "vocational school, technical school"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓使い",
      "answer": "ゆみづかい,ゆみつかい",
      "meaning": "bowing (a string instrument), archer (character, in anime, video games, etc.), bowman"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒針",
      "answer": "どくしん,どくばり",
      "meaning": "stinger (of a bee, etc.), needle covered with poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗用車",
      "answer": "じょうようしゃ",
      "meaning": "(passenger) car, automobile"
    },
    {
      "question": "火葬",
      "answer": "かそう",
      "meaning": "cremation"
    },
    {
      "question": "山里",
      "answer": "やまざと",
      "meaning": "mountain hamlet, mountain village"
    },
    {
      "question": "妖魔",
      "answer": "ようま",
      "meaning": "ghost, apparition"
    },
    {
      "question": "指標",
      "answer": "しひょう",
      "meaning": "index, indices, indicator"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜び勇む",
      "answer": "よろこびいさむ",
      "meaning": "to be in high spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "法案",
      "answer": "ほうあん",
      "meaning": "bill (law), measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "出稼ぎ",
      "answer": "でかせぎ",
      "meaning": "working away from home"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦肉の策",
      "answer": "くにくのさく",
      "meaning": "last resort, desperate measure taken under pressure of necessity"
    },
    {
      "question": "公女",
      "answer": "こうじょ",
      "meaning": "young noblewoman, princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "舵",
      "answer": "かじ",
      "meaning": "rudder, helm"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち返る",
      "answer": "たちかえる",
      "meaning": "to come back (to), to return to a starting point"
    },
    {
      "question": "観劇",
      "answer": "かんげき",
      "meaning": "theatre-going, theater-going"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋文",
      "answer": "こいぶみ",
      "meaning": "love letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲目",
      "answer": "きょくもく",
      "meaning": "name of a piece of music, (musical) number, (musical) program, programme, selection (of music), list"
    },
    {
      "question": "相当数",
      "answer": "そうとうすう",
      "meaning": "a considerable number, a fair number"
    },
    {
      "question": "憩い",
      "answer": "いこい",
      "meaning": "rest, relaxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "気を揉む",
      "answer": "きをもむ",
      "meaning": "to worry, to fret, to get anxious"
    },
    {
      "question": "思わしい",
      "answer": "おもわしい",
      "meaning": "suitable, satisfactory, desirable"
    },
    {
      "question": "土間",
      "answer": "どま",
      "meaning": "dirt floor, room with dirt floor, pit (theater seating), parterre"
    },
    {
      "question": "川面",
      "answer": "かわづら,かわも",
      "meaning": "river surface, surface of a river"
    },
    {
      "question": "接着剤",
      "answer": "せっちゃくざい",
      "meaning": "adhesive, glue"
    },
    {
      "question": "丘陵",
      "answer": "きゅうりょう",
      "meaning": "hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "包まる",
      "answer": "くるまる",
      "meaning": "to be wrapped up (e.g. in a blanket), to cover oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "提灯",
      "answer": "ちょうちん,ていとう",
      "meaning": "paper lantern, Chinese lantern, Japanese lantern"
    },
    {
      "question": "今日明日",
      "answer": "きょうあす",
      "meaning": "today and tomorrow, today or tomorrow, in a day or two"
    },
    {
      "question": "退役",
      "answer": "たいえき",
      "meaning": "retiring from military service"
    },
    {
      "question": "金槌",
      "answer": "かなづち",
      "meaning": "hammer, hopeless swimmer, complete beginner at swimming, someone who sinks like a stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "原始",
      "answer": "げんし",
      "meaning": "origin, beginning, genesis, primeval, primordial, primitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "紛い物",
      "answer": "まがいもの",
      "meaning": "imitation, fake, sham"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り払う",
      "answer": "きりはらう",
      "meaning": "to clear away, to clear land, to prune, to lop off"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒人",
      "answer": "くろうと,くろと,こくじん",
      "meaning": "expert, professional, master, connoisseur, woman in the nightlife business, demimondaine, geisha and"
    },
    {
      "question": "火器",
      "answer": "かき",
      "meaning": "firearms, guns"
    },
    {
      "question": "教育者",
      "answer": "きょういくしゃ",
      "meaning": "educator, teacher, educationalist"
    },
    {
      "question": "横道",
      "answer": "よこみち,おうどう",
      "meaning": "byway, side street, cross street, wrong way, digression, wickedness, evil, iniquity, wrongness"
    },
    {
      "question": "一命",
      "answer": "いちめい",
      "meaning": "(a) life, (a) command"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓穴",
      "answer": "ぼけつ,はかあな",
      "meaning": "grave (pit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "心に染む",
      "answer": "こころにそむ",
      "meaning": "to be pleased with, to suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し子",
      "answer": "もうしご",
      "meaning": "heaven-sent child (in answer to a Shinto or Buddhist prayer), child (e.g. of an era), product"
    },
    {
      "question": "古文書",
      "answer": "こもんじょ,こぶんしょ",
      "meaning": "historical document, archives, old manuscript, paleograph, pre-Meiji era document addressed to someo"
    },
    {
      "question": "無碍",
      "answer": "むげ",
      "meaning": "free from obstacles"
    },
    {
      "question": "新参",
      "answer": "しんざん",
      "meaning": "newcomer, tyro"
    },
    {
      "question": "生殖",
      "answer": "せいしょく",
      "meaning": "reproduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗅ぎ取る",
      "answer": "かぎとる",
      "meaning": "to smell, to sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮立つ",
      "answer": "にたつ",
      "meaning": "to boil, to simmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が君",
      "answer": "わがきみ",
      "meaning": "my lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚屋",
      "answer": "さかなや",
      "meaning": "fish market, fish dealer"
    },
    {
      "question": "ビー玉",
      "answer": "ビーだま",
      "meaning": "marble, glass marble"
    },
    {
      "question": "竦める",
      "answer": "すくめる",
      "meaning": "to shrug (shoulders), to duck (head), to draw back (body)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一気",
      "answer": "いっき",
      "meaning": "one breath, chug!, drink!"
    },
    {
      "question": "巌",
      "answer": "いわ,いわお",
      "meaning": "rock, boulder, crag, cliff, anchor, huge rock, massive boulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "不干渉",
      "answer": "ふかんしょう",
      "meaning": "abstention, nonintervention, noninterference"
    },
    {
      "question": "美談",
      "answer": "びだん",
      "meaning": "moving tale, impressive tale"
    },
    {
      "question": "配送",
      "answer": "はいそう",
      "meaning": "delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰み",
      "answer": "つみ",
      "meaning": "checkmate"
    },
    {
      "question": "情念",
      "answer": "じょうねん",
      "meaning": "sentiments, passions"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人旅",
      "answer": "ひとりたび",
      "meaning": "travelling alone, solitary journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "平謝り",
      "answer": "ひらあやまり",
      "meaning": "earnest apology"
    },
    {
      "question": "包皮",
      "answer": "ほうひ",
      "meaning": "foreskin, prepuce"
    },
    {
      "question": "空中戦",
      "answer": "くうちゅうせん",
      "meaning": "air battle, dog fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "兄弟子",
      "answer": "あにでし",
      "meaning": "senior pupil (of the same master), senior disciple, senior student, senior member"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢人",
      "answer": "けんじん",
      "meaning": "wise person, virtuous person, sage, unrefined sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "者共",
      "answer": "ものども",
      "meaning": "you, people"
    },
    {
      "question": "激震",
      "answer": "げきしん",
      "meaning": "severe earthquake, violent tremor"
    },
    {
      "question": "新築",
      "answer": "しんちく",
      "meaning": "new building, new construction"
    },
    {
      "question": "任じる",
      "answer": "にんじる",
      "meaning": "to appoint, to nominate, to assume (responsibility), to pose as"
    },
    {
      "question": "独力",
      "answer": "どくりょく",
      "meaning": "one's own effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴れ合う",
      "answer": "なれあう",
      "meaning": "to collude (with), to conspire (with), to make friends with, to get along well with, to become intim"
    },
    {
      "question": "特上",
      "answer": "とくじょう",
      "meaning": "first class plus, extra special"
    },
    {
      "question": "極悪人",
      "answer": "ごくあくにん",
      "meaning": "utter villain, atrocious fiend, devil"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵空事",
      "answer": "えそらごと",
      "meaning": "fabrication, pipe dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜き差し",
      "answer": "ぬきさし",
      "meaning": "addition and deletion, taking out and putting in, plugging and unplugging, making do, getting by, ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "壊れ物",
      "answer": "こわれもの",
      "meaning": "fragile article, breakables, broken article"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に様",
      "answer": "しにざま",
      "meaning": "manner of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "監査",
      "answer": "かんさ",
      "meaning": "inspection, audit, judgement, judgment"
    },
    {
      "question": "非常口",
      "answer": "ひじょうぐち",
      "meaning": "emergency exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "入居",
      "answer": "にゅうきょ",
      "meaning": "moving into (house)"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫の息",
      "answer": "むしのいき",
      "meaning": "faint breath, dying whisper, at death's door"
    },
    {
      "question": "珊瑚",
      "answer": "さんご",
      "meaning": "coral"
    },
    {
      "question": "隊商",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "caravan (of merchants)"
    },
    {
      "question": "見分け",
      "answer": "みわけ",
      "meaning": "distinction"
    },
    {
      "question": "親書",
      "answer": "しんしょ",
      "meaning": "official letter (from the Emperor, Prime Minister, etc.), personal message, handwritten letter, auto"
    },
    {
      "question": "香港",
      "answer": "ホンコン",
      "meaning": "Hong Kong, Hongkong"
    },
    {
      "question": "中距離",
      "answer": "ちゅうきょり",
      "meaning": "middle-distance (races), intermediate-range (missile)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賛美",
      "answer": "さんび",
      "meaning": "praise, glorification, extolment"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮れ",
      "answer": "くれ",
      "meaning": "sunset, sundown, nightfall, dusk, end, close, year-end, end of the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "挑戦状",
      "answer": "ちょうせんじょう",
      "meaning": "written challenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "運の尽き",
      "answer": "うんのつき",
      "meaning": "out of luck, (at the) end of one's rope"
    },
    {
      "question": "重低音",
      "answer": "じゅうていおん",
      "meaning": "very low frequency sound, heavy bass sound, low-register sound"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝き出し",
      "answer": "むきだし",
      "meaning": "naked, bare, uncovered, frank, open, blunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "咬む",
      "answer": "かむ",
      "meaning": "to bite, to chew, to gnaw, to masticate, to fumble one's words (esp. during a play, broadcast, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷塊",
      "answer": "ひょうかい",
      "meaning": "lump of ice, block of ice, ice floe"
    },
    {
      "question": "利便性",
      "answer": "りべんせい",
      "meaning": "convenience, user-friendliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "銛",
      "answer": "もり",
      "meaning": "lance, harpoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "人件費",
      "answer": "じんけんひ",
      "meaning": "personnel expenses, labor cost, labour cost, indirect labour costs, indirect labor costs"
    },
    {
      "question": "産み出す",
      "answer": "うみだす",
      "meaning": "to create, to bring forth, to produce, to invent, to think up and bring into being, to give birth to"
    },
    {
      "question": "楯突く",
      "answer": "たてつく",
      "meaning": "to defy, to disobey, to rebel against, to oppose, to resist"
    },
    {
      "question": "退位",
      "answer": "たいい",
      "meaning": "abdication"
    },
    {
      "question": "精が出る",
      "answer": "せいがでる",
      "meaning": "to work hard, to make an effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "発着",
      "answer": "はっちゃく",
      "meaning": "arrival and departure"
    },
    {
      "question": "外来",
      "answer": "がいらい",
      "meaning": "foreign, imported, outpatient, outpatient care, outpatient clinic, outpatient ward"
    },
    {
      "question": "微風",
      "answer": "そよかぜ,びふう",
      "meaning": "gentle breeze, soft wind, breath of air, zephyr"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨獣",
      "answer": "きょじゅう",
      "meaning": "large animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "金塊",
      "answer": "きんかい",
      "meaning": "gold nugget, gold bullion, gold bar, gold ingot"
    },
    {
      "question": "微熱",
      "answer": "びねつ",
      "meaning": "slight fever"
    },
    {
      "question": "流布",
      "answer": "るふ",
      "meaning": "circulation, dissemination"
    },
    {
      "question": "士道",
      "answer": "しどう",
      "meaning": "chivalry, samurai code"
    },
    {
      "question": "神の子",
      "answer": "かみのこ",
      "meaning": "Son of God, Jesus Christ, child of God, Christian, prodigy, young ace"
    },
    {
      "question": "不健全",
      "answer": "ふけんぜん",
      "meaning": "morbid, unhealthful, insalubrious"
    },
    {
      "question": "横槍",
      "answer": "よこやり",
      "meaning": "interruption, interference, butting in"
    },
    {
      "question": "快調",
      "answer": "かいちょう",
      "meaning": "good (condition), going well, fine, smooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "悦に入る",
      "answer": "えつにいる",
      "meaning": "to be pleased, to gloat, to glow with self-satisfaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "奈良",
      "answer": "なら",
      "meaning": "Nara (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "極彩色",
      "answer": "ごくさいしき,ごくさいしょく",
      "meaning": "richly colored, richly coloured"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁者",
      "answer": "えんじゃ",
      "meaning": "relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋慕",
      "answer": "れんぼ",
      "meaning": "love, attachment, tender emotions, falling in love"
    },
    {
      "question": "機械化",
      "answer": "きかいか",
      "meaning": "mechanization, mechanisation, computerization"
    },
    {
      "question": "教職員",
      "answer": "きょうしょくいん",
      "meaning": "teaching staff, faculty"
    },
    {
      "question": "物差し",
      "answer": "ものさし",
      "meaning": "ruler, measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗っ取り",
      "answer": "のっとり",
      "meaning": "capture, takeover, hijack, skyjacking"
    },
    {
      "question": "整合性",
      "answer": "せいごうせい",
      "meaning": "integrity, consistency, conformity, compliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "留",
      "answer": "ルーブル,ルーブリ,りゅう",
      "meaning": "ruble (Russian currency), rouble, stationary"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞表",
      "answer": "じひょう",
      "meaning": "letter of resignation"
    },
    {
      "question": "硫黄",
      "answer": "いおう,ゆおう",
      "meaning": "sulfur (S), sulphur"
    },
    {
      "question": "字面",
      "answer": "じづら,じめん",
      "meaning": "appearance of written words, impression given by written letters, characters, etc., literal meaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳めしい",
      "answer": "いかめしい",
      "meaning": "stern, grave, austere, imposing, dignified, formidable, solemn, majestic, strict (e.g. security), se"
    },
    {
      "question": "参入",
      "answer": "さんにゅう",
      "meaning": "entering (the marketplace), introducing (something) to the market, access, visiting a high-class or"
    },
    {
      "question": "街区",
      "answer": "がいく",
      "meaning": "block (of land)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒見",
      "answer": "どくみ",
      "meaning": "tasting (food or drink) for poison, checking the taste (of a dish), seeing how something tastes"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐屯",
      "answer": "ちゅうとん",
      "meaning": "stationing (troops), occupancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒れ地",
      "answer": "あれち",
      "meaning": "wasteland, wilderness, abandoned land, devastated land, The Wasteland (poem by T.S. Eliot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "続報",
      "answer": "ぞくほう",
      "meaning": "follow-up report, further news"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄紅",
      "answer": "うすべに,うすくれない",
      "meaning": "light pink, light crimson"
    },
    {
      "question": "符合",
      "answer": "ふごう",
      "meaning": "agreement, coincidence, correspondence, conformity"
    },
    {
      "question": "ほろ苦い",
      "answer": "ほろにがい",
      "meaning": "slightly bitter (taste), bittersweet (memory, experience, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "重体",
      "answer": "じゅうたい",
      "meaning": "serious condition, critical condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "強運",
      "answer": "きょううん",
      "meaning": "very good luck, excellent fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "何時でも",
      "answer": "いつでも,なんどきでも",
      "meaning": "(at) any time, always, at all times, whenever"
    },
    {
      "question": "身に余る",
      "answer": "みにあまる",
      "meaning": "to be undeserved, to be more than one deserves, to be more than one can handle"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲穂",
      "answer": "いなほ",
      "meaning": "ear (head) of rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "且つ",
      "answer": "かつ",
      "meaning": "and, moreover, besides, as well as, and on top of that, at the same time"
    },
    {
      "question": "極致",
      "answer": "きょくち",
      "meaning": "culmination, acme, height, peak, ultimate, perfection, ideal"
    },
    {
      "question": "活き活き",
      "answer": "いきいき",
      "meaning": "in a lively way, vividly, freshly, animatedly, actively, energetically"
    },
    {
      "question": "終幕",
      "answer": "しゅうまく",
      "meaning": "end, close"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち気",
      "answer": "かちき",
      "meaning": "determined spirit, unyielding spirit, will"
    },
    {
      "question": "発言権",
      "answer": "はつげんけん",
      "meaning": "right to speak"
    },
    {
      "question": "期す",
      "answer": "きす,ごす",
      "meaning": "to fix (a time, date, etc.), to set, to expect, to hope for, to look forward to, to foresee, to anti"
    },
    {
      "question": "開け閉め",
      "answer": "あけしめ",
      "meaning": "opening and shutting"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣れっこ",
      "answer": "なれっこ",
      "meaning": "being used to ..., getting used to ..., being accustomed to, being conditioned to, be familiar with"
    },
    {
      "question": "布切れ",
      "answer": "ぬのぎれ,ぬのきれ",
      "meaning": "piece of cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "梓",
      "answer": "あずさ,し",
      "meaning": "Japanese cherry birch (Betula grossa), yellow catalpa (Catalpa ovata), Japanese mallotus (Mallotus j"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄ら寒い",
      "answer": "うすらさむい",
      "meaning": "chilly, rather cold, somewhat cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "運動場",
      "answer": "うんどうじょう,うんどうば",
      "meaning": "sports ground, playing field, playground"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚息",
      "answer": "ぐそく",
      "meaning": "(one's) son"
    },
    {
      "question": "人任せ",
      "answer": "ひとまかせ",
      "meaning": "leaving (it) to others"
    },
    {
      "question": "伴奏",
      "answer": "ばんそう",
      "meaning": "(musical) accompaniment"
    },
    {
      "question": "収監",
      "answer": "しゅうかん",
      "meaning": "imprisonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "弊社",
      "answer": "へいしゃ",
      "meaning": "our company, our firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "同点",
      "answer": "どうてん",
      "meaning": "same score, deadlock, tie, draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "地蔵",
      "answer": "じぞう",
      "meaning": "Kshitigarbha (bodhisattva who looks over children, travellers and the underworld), Ksitigarbha, Jizō"
    },
    {
      "question": "直筆",
      "answer": "じきひつ,ちょくひつ",
      "meaning": "one's own handwriting, autograph, writing with an upright brush (using just the tip to create a narr"
    },
    {
      "question": "頸動脈",
      "answer": "けいどうみゃく",
      "meaning": "carotid artery"
    },
    {
      "question": "天誅",
      "answer": "てんちゅう",
      "meaning": "heaven's punishment, divine punishment, well-deserved punishment, just punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "学園都市",
      "answer": "がくえんとし",
      "meaning": "university town, college town"
    },
    {
      "question": "台湾",
      "answer": "たいわん",
      "meaning": "Taiwan"
    },
    {
      "question": "斑点",
      "answer": "はんてん",
      "meaning": "speck, fleck"
    },
    {
      "question": "銘打つ",
      "answer": "めいうつ",
      "meaning": "to engrave an inscription, to call (designate) itself, to mark, to label"
    },
    {
      "question": "猜疑心",
      "answer": "さいぎしん",
      "meaning": "suspicion (of others), jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "練り直す",
      "answer": "ねりなおす",
      "meaning": "to knead again, to rework, to revise, to polish"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫外線",
      "answer": "しがいせん",
      "meaning": "ultraviolet rays, ultraviolet radiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "慈善事業",
      "answer": "じぜんじぎょう",
      "meaning": "philanthropic work, charitable enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "救急箱",
      "answer": "きゅうきゅうばこ",
      "meaning": "first-aid kit"
    },
    {
      "question": "息災",
      "answer": "そくさい",
      "meaning": "good health"
    },
    {
      "question": "殉じる",
      "answer": "じゅんじる",
      "meaning": "to sacrifice oneself, to die a martyr"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨界",
      "answer": "りんかい",
      "meaning": "boundary, (nuclear) criticality, critical (mass, pressure, temperature, state, point, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弛む",
      "answer": "ゆるむ,たるむ,たゆむ",
      "meaning": "to become loose, to slacken (e.g. rope), to become less tense, to relax, to let one's guard down, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "一票",
      "answer": "いっぴょう",
      "meaning": "ballot, vote"
    },
    {
      "question": "無作為",
      "answer": "むさくい",
      "meaning": "random, unintentional, unintended"
    },
    {
      "question": "群青",
      "answer": "ぐんじょう",
      "meaning": "ultramarine"
    },
    {
      "question": "白光",
      "answer": "はっこう",
      "meaning": "white light, corona"
    },
    {
      "question": "増設",
      "answer": "ぞうせつ",
      "meaning": "adding (equipment, facilities, etc.), establishing more, installing more, increase, extension, expan"
    },
    {
      "question": "婿養子",
      "answer": "むこようし",
      "meaning": "son-in-law taken (adopted) into family"
    },
    {
      "question": "飼い猫",
      "answer": "かいねこ",
      "meaning": "pet cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "衆人環視",
      "answer": "しゅうじんかんし",
      "meaning": "(in) the presence of the whole company, with all eyes filed upon (one)"
    },
    {
      "question": "支配権",
      "answer": "しはいけん",
      "meaning": "right of control, supremacy, sovereignty"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹違い",
      "answer": "はらちがい",
      "meaning": "(brother and sister) born of a different mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "防水",
      "answer": "ぼうすい",
      "meaning": "waterproofing, making watertight"
    },
    {
      "question": "絆す",
      "answer": "ほだす",
      "meaning": "to fetter, to shackle, to bind"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬猿の仲",
      "answer": "けんえんのなか",
      "meaning": "like cats and dogs, (on) very bad terms, relationship of dogs and monkeys"
    },
    {
      "question": "大本",
      "answer": "たいほん,おおもと",
      "meaning": "foundation, basic principles, root, origin, source, cause, basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "考え抜く",
      "answer": "かんがえぬく",
      "meaning": "to think thoroughly"
    },
    {
      "question": "過半数",
      "answer": "かはんすう",
      "meaning": "majority"
    },
    {
      "question": "太陽系",
      "answer": "たいようけい",
      "meaning": "solar system"
    },
    {
      "question": "来日",
      "answer": "らいにち,らいじつ",
      "meaning": "arrival in Japan, coming to Japan, visit to Japan, future day, later date"
    },
    {
      "question": "計算高い",
      "answer": "けいさんだかい",
      "meaning": "calculating"
    },
    {
      "question": "術中",
      "answer": "じゅっちゅう",
      "meaning": "trick, trap, stratagem, intraoperative, during surgery"
    },
    {
      "question": "天板",
      "answer": "てんぱん,てんばん,てんいた",
      "meaning": "countertop, tabletop, baking tray, baking sheet"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑然",
      "answer": "ざつぜん",
      "meaning": "messy, untidy, disorderly, higgledy-piggledy"
    },
    {
      "question": "御社",
      "answer": "おんしゃ",
      "meaning": "your company, your shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯れ枝",
      "answer": "かれえだ",
      "meaning": "dead branch (or twig, etc.), withered branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩塩",
      "answer": "がんえん,いわしお",
      "meaning": "halite, rock salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "先延ばし",
      "answer": "さきのばし",
      "meaning": "delay, putting off, procrastination"
    },
    {
      "question": "原稿用紙",
      "answer": "げんこうようし",
      "meaning": "Japanese writing paper (lined with a square grid, one square per character), manuscript paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "培養",
      "answer": "ばいよう",
      "meaning": "cultivation, nurture, culture"
    },
    {
      "question": "失速",
      "answer": "しっそく",
      "meaning": "stall (in flying), downturn, slowdown, slump, weakening, decline"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪符",
      "answer": "じゅふ",
      "meaning": "amulet, charm"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガラス戸",
      "answer": "ガラスど",
      "meaning": "glass door"
    },
    {
      "question": "事も無げ",
      "answer": "こともなげ",
      "meaning": "careless"
    },
    {
      "question": "改名",
      "answer": "かいめい,かいみょう",
      "meaning": "name change"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き",
      "answer": "いき",
      "meaning": "living, being alive, freshness, liveliness, vitality, situation in which a group of stones cannot be"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨組み",
      "answer": "ほねぐみ",
      "meaning": "skeletal frame, skeleton, build, physique, framework, frame, structure, outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い風",
      "answer": "おいかぜ,おいて",
      "meaning": "tailwind, fair wind, favorable wind (favourable), favorable condition (favourable), advantageous sit"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨額",
      "answer": "きょがく",
      "meaning": "huge sum (esp. of money), enormous sum, massive amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "後継ぎ",
      "answer": "あとつぎ",
      "meaning": "heir, inheritor, successor"
    },
    {
      "question": "小癪",
      "answer": "こしゃく",
      "meaning": "impudent, cheeky"
    },
    {
      "question": "満遍",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "筋道",
      "answer": "すじみち",
      "meaning": "reason, logic, method, system, order, thread (e.g. of an argument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "団地",
      "answer": "だんち",
      "meaning": "multi-unit apartments, apartment complex"
    },
    {
      "question": "半世紀",
      "answer": "はんせいき",
      "meaning": "half century"
    },
    {
      "question": "独断専行",
      "answer": "どくだんせんこう",
      "meaning": "acting arbitrarily on one's own authority, acting arbitrarily without consultation"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤目",
      "answer": "あかめ,あかべ",
      "meaning": "red eyes, bloodshot eyes, red-eye, red mullet (Chelon haematocheilus), facial gesture of pulling one"
    },
    {
      "question": "天涯孤独",
      "answer": "てんがいこどく",
      "meaning": "a person without a single relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "総額",
      "answer": "そうがく",
      "meaning": "sum total, total amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "無限大",
      "answer": "むげんだい",
      "meaning": "infinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "幅広",
      "answer": "はばびろ",
      "meaning": "wide-width (e.g. cloth), broad"
    },
    {
      "question": "平穏無事",
      "answer": "へいおんぶじ",
      "meaning": "tranquillity and peace, tranquility and peace, peaceful and uneventful"
    },
    {
      "question": "重ね重ね",
      "answer": "かさねがさね",
      "meaning": "repeatedly, frequently, over and over, time and time again, exceedingly, sincerely, very much"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝蹴り",
      "answer": "ひざげり",
      "meaning": "knee strike, kneeing"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞台裏",
      "answer": "ぶたいうら",
      "meaning": "offstage, backstage, behind the scenes"
    },
    {
      "question": "動力源",
      "answer": "どうりょくげん",
      "meaning": "source of power"
    },
    {
      "question": "火急",
      "answer": "かきゅう",
      "meaning": "urgency, exigency, emergency"
    },
    {
      "question": "準じる",
      "answer": "じゅんじる",
      "meaning": "to follow, to conform, to apply to"
    },
    {
      "question": "入港",
      "answer": "にゅうこう",
      "meaning": "entry into port, arriving in harbor"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪知恵",
      "answer": "わるぢえ,わるじえ",
      "meaning": "craft, cunning, guile, serpentine wisdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "肯定的",
      "answer": "こうていてき",
      "meaning": "affirmative"
    },
    {
      "question": "起き抜け",
      "answer": "おきぬけ",
      "meaning": "first thing after rising, as soon as getting up"
    },
    {
      "question": "円筒",
      "answer": "えんとう",
      "meaning": "cylinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷点下",
      "answer": "ひょうてんか",
      "meaning": "below freezing"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉め切る",
      "answer": "しめきる",
      "meaning": "to close up, to shut up (e.g. behind doors), to cut off (e.g. because a deadline has expired), to cl"
    },
    {
      "question": "再開発",
      "answer": "さいかいはつ",
      "meaning": "redevelopment"
    },
    {
      "question": "前述",
      "answer": "ぜんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "aforementioned, above-mentioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "喧嘩腰",
      "answer": "けんかごし",
      "meaning": "belligerent"
    },
    {
      "question": "警邏",
      "answer": "けいら",
      "meaning": "patrol"
    },
    {
      "question": "入学試験",
      "answer": "にゅうがくしけん",
      "meaning": "entrance examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "理路整然",
      "answer": "りろせいぜん",
      "meaning": "logical, cogent, well-reasoned"
    },
    {
      "question": "青銅",
      "answer": "せいどう",
      "meaning": "bronze"
    },
    {
      "question": "応援団",
      "answer": "おうえんだん",
      "meaning": "cheering party"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄柵",
      "answer": "てっさく",
      "meaning": "iron railing or fence"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝聞",
      "answer": "でんぶん",
      "meaning": "hearsay, rumor, rumour, report"
    },
    {
      "question": "錫杖",
      "answer": "しゃくじょう,さくじょう",
      "meaning": "bishop's staff, khakkhara"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊豆",
      "answer": "いず",
      "meaning": "Izu (former province located on the Izu Peninsula in present-day Shizuoka Prefecture, and the Izu Is"
    },
    {
      "question": "施術",
      "answer": "しじゅつ,せじゅつ",
      "meaning": "medical treatment (esp. surgical)"
    },
    {
      "question": "取捨選択",
      "answer": "しゅしゃせんたく",
      "meaning": "selection, making a choice, sifting, decision to adopt or reject"
    },
    {
      "question": "お安い",
      "answer": "おやすい",
      "meaning": "easy, simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴落",
      "answer": "ぼうらく",
      "meaning": "slump, crash, heavy fall, sudden decline"
    },
    {
      "question": "義憤",
      "answer": "ぎふん",
      "meaning": "righteous indignation"
    },
    {
      "question": "食道",
      "answer": "しょくどう",
      "meaning": "esophagus, gullet, esophageal"
    },
    {
      "question": "思いの丈",
      "answer": "おもいのたけ",
      "meaning": "one's whole heart, everything one feels"
    },
    {
      "question": "守",
      "answer": "もり,まもり,かみ",
      "meaning": "babysitting, babysitter, protecting, keeping, keeper, protection, defense, defence, providence, amul"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗印",
      "answer": "はたじるし",
      "meaning": "design (on a banner), emblem (on a flag), insignia, banner (e.g. of democracy), slogan, cause, objec"
    },
    {
      "question": "略称",
      "answer": "りゃくしょう",
      "meaning": "abbreviation"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰核",
      "answer": "いんかく,へのこ",
      "meaning": "clitoris, testicles, penis"
    },
    {
      "question": "柴",
      "answer": "しば",
      "meaning": "brushwood, firewood"
    },
    {
      "question": "短冊",
      "answer": "たんざく,たんじゃく",
      "meaning": "long, narrow card on which Japanese poems are written (vertically), strip of paper, tanzaku, thin re"
    },
    {
      "question": "神輿",
      "answer": "みこし,しんよ,じんよ",
      "meaning": "portable shrine (carried in festivals), palanquin, buttocks, lower back, waist, hips"
    },
    {
      "question": "球形",
      "answer": "きゅうけい",
      "meaning": "globular shape, spherical shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "並木",
      "answer": "なみき",
      "meaning": "roadside tree, row of trees"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵便局",
      "answer": "ゆうびんきょく",
      "meaning": "post office"
    },
    {
      "question": "体温計",
      "answer": "たいおんけい",
      "meaning": "medical thermometer"
    },
    {
      "question": "大音声",
      "answer": "だいおんじょう",
      "meaning": "very loud voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "得てして",
      "answer": "えてして",
      "meaning": "often (happens), tend to, be apt to, be likely to"
    },
    {
      "question": "接収",
      "answer": "せっしゅう",
      "meaning": "requisition, requisitioning, seizure, confiscation, impounding, retaining (e.g. deposit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "車線",
      "answer": "しゃせん",
      "meaning": "traffic lane, road lane"
    },
    {
      "question": "保守的",
      "answer": "ほしゅてき",
      "meaning": "conservative"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴動",
      "answer": "めいどう",
      "meaning": "rumbling, (ringing) cadence"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘度",
      "answer": "ねんど",
      "meaning": "viscosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "食器棚",
      "answer": "しょっきだな",
      "meaning": "cupboard, sideboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "日替わり",
      "answer": "ひがわり",
      "meaning": "changing every day"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬力",
      "answer": "ばりき",
      "meaning": "horsepower, hp, energy, vitality, vigour"
    },
    {
      "question": "情状酌量",
      "answer": "じょうじょうしゃくりょう",
      "meaning": "taking the extenuating circumstances into consideration"
    },
    {
      "question": "対局",
      "answer": "たいきょく",
      "meaning": "(playing) a game of go, shogi or chess, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "退化",
      "answer": "たいか",
      "meaning": "degeneration, retrogression"
    },
    {
      "question": "約定",
      "answer": "やくじょう",
      "meaning": "agreement, stipulation, contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "総司令官",
      "answer": "そうしれいかん",
      "meaning": "commander-in-chief, supreme commander"
    },
    {
      "question": "新妻",
      "answer": "にいづま",
      "meaning": "new wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "出兵",
      "answer": "しゅっぺい",
      "meaning": "dispatch of troops, despatch of troops, expedition"
    },
    {
      "question": "年金",
      "answer": "ねんきん",
      "meaning": "annuity, pension"
    },
    {
      "question": "折衝",
      "answer": "せっしょう",
      "meaning": "negotiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩辛い",
      "answer": "しおからい",
      "meaning": "salty (taste), briny"
    },
    {
      "question": "五月蠅い",
      "answer": "うるさい",
      "meaning": "noisy, loud, annoying, troublesome, tiresome, persistent, importunate, fussy, finicky, picky, partic"
    },
    {
      "question": "柿",
      "answer": "かき,こけら",
      "meaning": "kaki, Japanese persimmon (Diospyros kaki), chopped wood, wood chips, thin shingles"
    },
    {
      "question": "気軽い",
      "answer": "きがるい",
      "meaning": "cheerful, buoyant, lighthearted"
    },
    {
      "question": "宵",
      "answer": "よい",
      "meaning": "evening, early night hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "泡沫",
      "answer": "うたかた,ほうまつ,うたがた",
      "meaning": "bubble on surface of liquid, ephemeral, transient"
    },
    {
      "question": "途絶",
      "answer": "とぜつ",
      "meaning": "stoppage, interruption, cessation, suspension"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り身",
      "answer": "きりみ",
      "meaning": "cut, slice (meat, fish), fillet"
    },
    {
      "question": "店名",
      "answer": "てんめい",
      "meaning": "store name"
    },
    {
      "question": "埠頭",
      "answer": "ふとう",
      "meaning": "pier, wharf, quay, dock"
    },
    {
      "question": "普遍的",
      "answer": "ふへんてき",
      "meaning": "universal, omnipresent, ubiquitous"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵方",
      "answer": "てきがた",
      "meaning": "hostile party, enemy side"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆鉄砲",
      "answer": "まめでっぽう",
      "meaning": "peashooter"
    },
    {
      "question": "音波",
      "answer": "おんぱ",
      "meaning": "sound wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "批難",
      "answer": "ひなん",
      "meaning": "criticism, blame, censure, attack, reproach"
    },
    {
      "question": "注目度",
      "answer": "ちゅうもくど",
      "meaning": "degree of attention, profile"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩が凝る",
      "answer": "かたがこる",
      "meaning": "to have stiff shoulders, to feel ill at ease, to feel uncomfortable, to feel tense, serious, sober"
    },
    {
      "question": "殴り込み",
      "answer": "なぐりこみ",
      "meaning": "raid, attack, assault"
    },
    {
      "question": "納入",
      "answer": "のうにゅう",
      "meaning": "payment (taxes, fees, etc.), supply (of goods), delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "定年",
      "answer": "ていねん",
      "meaning": "retirement age, years of service in a military rank before eligibility for promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "先天的",
      "answer": "せんてんてき",
      "meaning": "inborn, innate, inherent, congenital, hereditary, a priori"
    },
    {
      "question": "象徴的",
      "answer": "しょうちょうてき",
      "meaning": "symbolic"
    },
    {
      "question": "名折れ",
      "answer": "なおれ",
      "meaning": "disgrace, discredit, dishonor, dishonour, blot, shame"
    },
    {
      "question": "付き纏う",
      "answer": "つきまとう",
      "meaning": "to follow around, to shadow, to tag along, to haunt one (e.g. feeling, failure), to follow one"
    },
    {
      "question": "職業柄",
      "answer": "しょくぎょうがら",
      "meaning": "due to the nature of one's job, because of one's line of work"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き抜き",
      "answer": "ひきぬき",
      "meaning": "hiring from another company, recruitment, scouting, headhunting, quick costume change in kabuki (tak"
    },
    {
      "question": "目敏い",
      "answer": "めざとい",
      "meaning": "sharp sighted, easily awakened"
    },
    {
      "question": "前振り",
      "answer": "まえふり",
      "meaning": "preface, introduction, lead in (to a joke, question, etc.), lead up, payment in advance (by bank tra"
    },
    {
      "question": "状況判断",
      "answer": "じょうきょうはんだん",
      "meaning": "one's assessment of the situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋菓子",
      "answer": "ようがし",
      "meaning": "Western confectionery"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い足す",
      "answer": "かいたす",
      "meaning": "to buy more (of something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "迫真",
      "answer": "はくしん",
      "meaning": "realistic, true to life"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝苦しい",
      "answer": "ねぐるしい",
      "meaning": "unable to sleep well"
    },
    {
      "question": "企て",
      "answer": "くわだて",
      "meaning": "plan, attempt, undertaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "封殺",
      "answer": "ふうさつ",
      "meaning": "suppression (e.g. free speech), forceout"
    },
    {
      "question": "直情",
      "answer": "ちょくじょう",
      "meaning": "frankness, impulsiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "英傑",
      "answer": "えいけつ",
      "meaning": "great man, hero, master mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘り気",
      "answer": "ねばりけ",
      "meaning": "stickiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺",
      "answer": "し,とげ",
      "meaning": "calling card, thorn, spine, prickle, splinter (esp. lodged in one's flesh), hard sharp item (esp. lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "必要経費",
      "answer": "ひつようけいひ",
      "meaning": "necessary expense"
    },
    {
      "question": "に就き",
      "answer": "につき",
      "meaning": "because of, on account of, regarding, per, apiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "簪",
      "answer": "かんざし",
      "meaning": "ornate hairpin"
    },
    {
      "question": "血の涙",
      "answer": "ちのなみだ",
      "meaning": "bitter tears, tears of blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "梱包",
      "answer": "こんぽう",
      "meaning": "packing, crating, packaging"
    },
    {
      "question": "落語",
      "answer": "らくご",
      "meaning": "rakugo, traditional Japanese comic storytelling, comic story (told by a professional storyteller)"
    },
    {
      "question": "写本",
      "answer": "しゃほん",
      "meaning": "manuscript (book), written copy of a book, codex, transcription, copying"
    },
    {
      "question": "演奏会",
      "answer": "えんそうかい",
      "meaning": "concert, recital"
    },
    {
      "question": "漏洩",
      "answer": "ろうえい,ろうせつ",
      "meaning": "leak (of secrets, information, etc.), disclosure, divulging, leak (of gas, liquid, etc.), leakage, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "現場検証",
      "answer": "げんばけんしょう",
      "meaning": "on-the-site inspection"
    },
    {
      "question": "明晰",
      "answer": "めいせき",
      "meaning": "clear, distinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "神戸",
      "answer": "こうべ",
      "meaning": "Kobe (city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚介",
      "answer": "ぎょかい",
      "meaning": "marine products, seafood, fish and shellfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "古書店",
      "answer": "こしょてん",
      "meaning": "secondhand bookshop, antiquarian bookshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "路傍",
      "answer": "ろぼう",
      "meaning": "roadside"
    },
    {
      "question": "相模",
      "answer": "さがみ",
      "meaning": "Sagami (former province located in present-day Kanagawa Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "囚われ",
      "answer": "とらわれ",
      "meaning": "imprisonment, captive"
    },
    {
      "question": "自決",
      "answer": "じけつ",
      "meaning": "self-determination, suicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "養生",
      "answer": "ようじょう",
      "meaning": "taking care of one's health, recuperation, covering (with a protective material), coating, curing (c"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷害",
      "answer": "しょうがい",
      "meaning": "wound, injury, accident, casualty, assault, inflicting bodily injury"
    },
    {
      "question": "憤然",
      "answer": "ふんぜん",
      "meaning": "angry, indignant, wrathful, enraged"
    },
    {
      "question": "精彩",
      "answer": "せいさい",
      "meaning": "brilliance, luster, lustre, colorfulness, colourfulness, vividness, life"
    },
    {
      "question": "准将",
      "answer": "じゅんしょう",
      "meaning": "commodore, brigadier general"
    },
    {
      "question": "入江",
      "answer": "いりえ",
      "meaning": "inlet, cove, creek, bay"
    },
    {
      "question": "本拠",
      "answer": "ほんきょ",
      "meaning": "stronghold, inner citadel, base, headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "手管",
      "answer": "てくだ",
      "meaning": "wiles, trick, artifice, coquetry, lover (male) (esp. of a prostitute)"
    },
    {
      "question": "妥協点",
      "answer": "だきょうてん",
      "meaning": "(find) common (meeting) ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "息が合う",
      "answer": "いきがあう",
      "meaning": "to (work, talk, etc.) together smoothly"
    },
    {
      "question": "新薬",
      "answer": "しんやく",
      "meaning": "new medicine, new drug"
    },
    {
      "question": "撃鉄",
      "answer": "げきてつ",
      "meaning": "percussion hammer, firing hammer, cocking piece"
    },
    {
      "question": "大雪",
      "answer": "おおゆき,たいせつ",
      "meaning": "heavy snow, 'major snow' solar term (approx. Dec. 7)"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁判官",
      "answer": "さいばんかん",
      "meaning": "judge"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚気",
      "answer": "のろけ",
      "meaning": "speaking fondly about one's sweetheart (spouse, girlfriend, etc.), going on about one's love affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "多人数",
      "answer": "たにんずう,たにんず",
      "meaning": "large number of people"
    },
    {
      "question": "才人",
      "answer": "さいじん",
      "meaning": "talented person, clever person"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁日",
      "answer": "えんにち",
      "meaning": "temple festival, fair, fete day, day related to a particular deity and thought to bring divine bless"
    },
    {
      "question": "刻限",
      "answer": "こくげん",
      "meaning": "time, appointed time"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐れ",
      "answer": "くされ",
      "meaning": "rotting, spoiling, decaying, corroding, rotten, worthless, paltry, contemptible"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘性",
      "answer": "ねんせい",
      "meaning": "viscosity"
    },
    {
      "question": "口当たり",
      "answer": "くちあたり",
      "meaning": "taste, smooth talking, reception, hospitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "親兄弟",
      "answer": "おやきょうだい",
      "meaning": "parents and siblings, one's relatives"
    },
    {
      "question": "預言者",
      "answer": "よげんしゃ",
      "meaning": "prophet, predictor, prognosticator"
    },
    {
      "question": "尖兵",
      "answer": "せんぺい",
      "meaning": "vanguard, advance-guard point, advance detachment, pioneer, avant-garde, leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "孵る",
      "answer": "かえる",
      "meaning": "to hatch out"
    },
    {
      "question": "処世術",
      "answer": "しょせいじゅつ",
      "meaning": "worldly wisdom, secret of success in life"
    },
    {
      "question": "当て馬",
      "answer": "あてうま",
      "meaning": "stallion brought close to a mare to test her readiness to mate, stalking horse, spoiler"
    },
    {
      "question": "万事休す",
      "answer": "ばんじきゅうす",
      "meaning": "there is nothing more that can be done, it's all over"
    },
    {
      "question": "福岡",
      "answer": "ふくおか",
      "meaning": "Fukuoka (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拗らせる",
      "answer": "こじらせる",
      "meaning": "to aggravate, to complicate, to make worse"
    },
    {
      "question": "現出",
      "answer": "げんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "appearance, emergence"
    },
    {
      "question": "過分",
      "answer": "かぶん",
      "meaning": "excessive, unmerited, generous, past participle"
    },
    {
      "question": "角砂糖",
      "answer": "かくざとう",
      "meaning": "cube sugar, sugar cube"
    },
    {
      "question": "川魚",
      "answer": "かわうお,かわざかな",
      "meaning": "river fish, freshwater fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "無作法",
      "answer": "ぶさほう",
      "meaning": "ill-mannered, rude"
    },
    {
      "question": "足し",
      "answer": "たし",
      "meaning": "supplement, top up, complement, making up (a deficiency)"
    },
    {
      "question": "腑抜け",
      "answer": "ふぬけ",
      "meaning": "fool, coward"
    },
    {
      "question": "大将軍",
      "answer": "たいしょうぐん,だいしょうぐん",
      "meaning": "commander-in-chief, Taishōgun, one of the eight gods of the koyomi"
    },
    {
      "question": "包装紙",
      "answer": "ほうそうし",
      "meaning": "wrapping paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "呉",
      "answer": "ご",
      "meaning": "go, soy beans soaked and mashed to a creamy paste (ingredient of tofu and soy milk), Wu, region in C"
    },
    {
      "question": "某所",
      "answer": "ぼうしょ",
      "meaning": "certain place"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟分",
      "answer": "おとうとぶん",
      "meaning": "sworn younger brother, junior male peer (in a club, group, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃業",
      "answer": "はいぎょう",
      "meaning": "discontinuation (of business), closing down, giving up (one's practice), retiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕章",
      "answer": "わんしょう",
      "meaning": "armband, arm band, brassard"
    },
    {
      "question": "総菜",
      "answer": "そうざい",
      "meaning": "small dish (served as a part of an ordinary household meal), side dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神衛生",
      "answer": "せいしんえいせい",
      "meaning": "mental health, mental hygiene"
    },
    {
      "question": "属国",
      "answer": "ぞっこく",
      "meaning": "vassal state, vassal nation, dependency"
    },
    {
      "question": "以心伝心",
      "answer": "いしんでんしん",
      "meaning": "telepathy, tacit understanding, thought transference, communion of mind with mind, non-verbal Zen Bu"
    },
    {
      "question": "依る",
      "answer": "よる",
      "meaning": "to be due to, to be caused by, to depend on, to turn on, to be based on, to come from, to be based a"
    },
    {
      "question": "蚕",
      "answer": "かいこ",
      "meaning": "silkworm (Bombyx mori)"
    },
    {
      "question": "所轄",
      "answer": "しょかつ",
      "meaning": "jurisdiction"
    },
    {
      "question": "産毛",
      "answer": "うぶげ",
      "meaning": "soft, downy hair (i.e. such as on one's cheek), peach fuzz, fluff, pappus, lanugo, lanuginous, pappo"
    },
    {
      "question": "涸れる",
      "answer": "かれる",
      "meaning": "to dry up (spring, pond, etc.), to run out"
    },
    {
      "question": "野蛮人",
      "answer": "やばんじん",
      "meaning": "barbarian, savage"
    },
    {
      "question": "動植物",
      "answer": "どうしょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "plants and animals, flora and fauna"
    },
    {
      "question": "驕り",
      "answer": "おごり",
      "meaning": "arrogance, haughtiness, conceitedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝の山",
      "answer": "たからのやま",
      "meaning": "gold mine, treasure trove, golconda, mountain of treasures"
    },
    {
      "question": "深読み",
      "answer": "ふかよみ",
      "meaning": "reading too much into (what ... says)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し切る",
      "answer": "かしきる",
      "meaning": "to reserve (for exclusive use), to charter, to book, to lend out completely, to lend out all of (som"
    },
    {
      "question": "紀",
      "answer": "き",
      "meaning": "period, Nihon-shoki"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚部",
      "answer": "きゃくぶ",
      "meaning": "leg, leg portion, foot (of a page)"
    },
    {
      "question": "家訓",
      "answer": "かくん,かきん",
      "meaning": "family precepts, family motto, rule of the home"
    },
    {
      "question": "下郎",
      "answer": "げろう",
      "meaning": "servant, valet, menial"
    },
    {
      "question": "刃渡り",
      "answer": "はわたり",
      "meaning": "length of a blade (sword, knife, etc.), walking on the edge of a sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "相成る",
      "answer": "あいなる",
      "meaning": "to become (formal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔が差す",
      "answer": "まがさす",
      "meaning": "to be possessed by an evil spirit, to be tempted, to give in to an urge, to succumb to temptation"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪い虫",
      "answer": "わるいむし",
      "meaning": "undesirable lover (boyfriend, girlfriend), passion, temper, irritability"
    },
    {
      "question": "子持ち",
      "answer": "こもち",
      "meaning": "parenthood, parent or someone with children on the way (esp. an expecting mother), (of a fish) conta"
    },
    {
      "question": "処断",
      "answer": "しょだん",
      "meaning": "judgement, judgment, carrying out a sentence (e.g. execution)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気心",
      "answer": "きごころ",
      "meaning": "temper, disposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙考",
      "answer": "もっこう",
      "meaning": "contemplation, meditation"
    },
    {
      "question": "自供",
      "answer": "じきょう",
      "meaning": "confession"
    },
    {
      "question": "様付け",
      "answer": "さまづけ",
      "meaning": "attaching the polite suffix '-sama' to somebody's name (more polite than '-san')"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち進む",
      "answer": "かちすすむ",
      "meaning": "to win and advance to the next round"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦勝",
      "answer": "せんしょう",
      "meaning": "winning a war, victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "真骨頂",
      "answer": "しんこっちょう",
      "meaning": "one's true worth, one's true self, what one is really made of"
    },
    {
      "question": "闘士",
      "answer": "とうし",
      "meaning": "fighter (for), militant, champion (of), boxer"
    },
    {
      "question": "戒律",
      "answer": "かいりつ",
      "meaning": "(religious) precept, discipline, commandment, mitzvah"
    },
    {
      "question": "染料",
      "answer": "せんりょう",
      "meaning": "dyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "大らか",
      "answer": "おおらか",
      "meaning": "placid, composed, serene, calm, big hearted, broad-minded, magnanimous, great quantity (of something"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴走族",
      "answer": "ぼうそうぞく",
      "meaning": "young motorcycle-riding delinquents, bōsōzoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "修得",
      "answer": "しゅうとく",
      "meaning": "learning, acquisition (of a skill, knowledge, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生放送",
      "answer": "なまほうそう",
      "meaning": "live broadcast"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍神",
      "answer": "ぐんしん,いくさがみ,ぐんじん",
      "meaning": "god of war, war hero"
    },
    {
      "question": "実子",
      "answer": "じっし",
      "meaning": "biological child, one's own child"
    },
    {
      "question": "傅く",
      "answer": "かしずく,かしづく",
      "meaning": "to wait upon, to serve"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い気",
      "answer": "くいけ",
      "meaning": "appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "誕生会",
      "answer": "たんじょうかい",
      "meaning": "birthday party"
    },
    {
      "question": "喧しい",
      "answer": "やかましい,かまびすしい",
      "meaning": "noisy, loud, clamorous, boisterous, much talked of, much-discussed, vexed, strict, severe, stern, pa"
    },
    {
      "question": "稜線",
      "answer": "りょうせん",
      "meaning": "ridgeline, lines of a mountain ridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "神気",
      "answer": "しんき",
      "meaning": "qi, mysterious life force that makes up everything, spirits, mind, divine atmosphere, mysterious pre"
    },
    {
      "question": "居丈高",
      "answer": "いたけだか",
      "meaning": "high-handed, overbearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "理想論",
      "answer": "りそうろん",
      "meaning": "idealistic thought (argument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘っこい",
      "answer": "ねばっこい",
      "meaning": "sticky, stiff, tenacious, persistent"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み水",
      "answer": "のみみず",
      "meaning": "drinking water, potable water"
    },
    {
      "question": "定員",
      "answer": "ていいん",
      "meaning": "fixed number (of people), prescribed number (of regular personnel, students, etc.), quota, numerical"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕試し",
      "answer": "うでだめし",
      "meaning": "trying one's ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "幾重",
      "answer": "いくえ",
      "meaning": "piling up, multiple layers"
    },
    {
      "question": "食前",
      "answer": "しょくぜん",
      "meaning": "before meals"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂地",
      "answer": "すなじ,すなち",
      "meaning": "sandy soil"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍資金",
      "answer": "ぐんしきん",
      "meaning": "war funds, war chest, funds (for activities), campaign funds"
    },
    {
      "question": "火を吹く",
      "answer": "ひをふく",
      "meaning": "to burst into flames, to fire (of a gun), to fan a fire with one's breath"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸刃の剣",
      "answer": "もろはのつるぎ",
      "meaning": "double-edged sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び級",
      "answer": "とびきゅう",
      "meaning": "skipping a grade"
    },
    {
      "question": "時差",
      "answer": "じさ",
      "meaning": "time difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄明かり",
      "answer": "うすあかり",
      "meaning": "dim light, faint light, half-light of early morning, twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "劇薬",
      "answer": "げきやく",
      "meaning": "powerful medicine, strong poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報通",
      "answer": "じょうほうつう",
      "meaning": "well-informed person"
    },
    {
      "question": "一匹狼",
      "answer": "いっぴきおおかみ",
      "meaning": "lone wolf, loner, self-reliant person"
    },
    {
      "question": "喚ぶ",
      "answer": "よぶ",
      "meaning": "to call out (to), to call, to invoke, to summon (a doctor, etc.), to invite, to designate, to name,"
    },
    {
      "question": "謀",
      "answer": "はかりごと",
      "meaning": "plan, strategy"
    },
    {
      "question": "足を洗う",
      "answer": "あしをあらう",
      "meaning": "to quit (a shady business), to wash one's hands of, to cut one's ties with, to turn over a new leaf,"
    },
    {
      "question": "多種多様",
      "answer": "たしゅたよう",
      "meaning": "a great variety of, diversity"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖夜",
      "answer": "せいや",
      "meaning": "Christmas Eve, holy night"
    },
    {
      "question": "役場",
      "answer": "やくば",
      "meaning": "town hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "集い",
      "answer": "つどい",
      "meaning": "meeting, get-together (e.g. among friends)"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来立て",
      "answer": "できたて",
      "meaning": "just made, fresh (from the oven), newly-built (house)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子連れ",
      "answer": "こづれ",
      "meaning": "taking one's children along (to an event, into a new marriage, etc.), parent with child"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃霧",
      "answer": "のうむ",
      "meaning": "heavy fog, dense fog, thick fog"
    },
    {
      "question": "可視化",
      "answer": "かしか",
      "meaning": "visualization (data, results, etc.), visualisation, making something visible (that was previously un"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞令",
      "answer": "じれい",
      "meaning": "notice of personnel change (appointment, dismissal, etc.), wording, choice of language, phraseology"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚策",
      "answer": "ぐさく",
      "meaning": "stupid plan, inane way of doing something, (one's own) plan or project"
    },
    {
      "question": "女傑",
      "answer": "じょけつ",
      "meaning": "brave woman, heroine, lady of character, Amazon"
    },
    {
      "question": "長槍",
      "answer": "ながやり",
      "meaning": "long spear, pike"
    },
    {
      "question": "中旬",
      "answer": "ちゅうじゅん",
      "meaning": "middle of a month, second third of a month, 11th to 20th day of a month"
    },
    {
      "question": "憤懣",
      "answer": "ふんまん",
      "meaning": "anger, resentment, indignation, chagrin, irritation"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂丘",
      "answer": "さきゅう,しゃきゅう",
      "meaning": "sand dune, sand hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "海藻",
      "answer": "かいそう",
      "meaning": "seaweed"
    },
    {
      "question": "共生",
      "answer": "きょうせい",
      "meaning": "coexistence, living together, symbiosis, paragenesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り場",
      "answer": "のりば",
      "meaning": "place for boarding vehicles, bus stop, bus terminal, railway platform, taxi stand, jetty, wharf"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼穹",
      "answer": "そうきゅう",
      "meaning": "blue sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "口直し",
      "answer": "くちなおし",
      "meaning": "removing a bad taste, cleansing one's palate, palate cleanser, intermezzo, dish or beverage to clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛禽",
      "answer": "もうきん",
      "meaning": "bird of prey"
    },
    {
      "question": "世俗",
      "answer": "せぞく,せいぞく",
      "meaning": "wordly things, common customs, ordinary life, popular taste, the world, the (common) people, the mas"
    },
    {
      "question": "一切合切",
      "answer": "いっさいがっさい",
      "meaning": "any and every thing, altogether, lock, stock, and barrel, the whole shooting match, the whole kit an"
    },
    {
      "question": "減",
      "answer": "げん",
      "meaning": "reduction, decrease, subtraction, reduction of penalty (under the ritsuryo codes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "退席",
      "answer": "たいせき",
      "meaning": "leaving one's seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "極光",
      "answer": "きょっこう,きょくこう",
      "meaning": "northern or southern lights, aurora borealis or australis"
    },
    {
      "question": "東洋人",
      "answer": "とうようじん",
      "meaning": "Asian people, Orientals"
    },
    {
      "question": "指切り",
      "answer": "ゆびきり",
      "meaning": "pinky swear, pinky promise, hooking each other's little fingers to confirm a promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "慎み",
      "answer": "つつしみ",
      "meaning": "modesty, self-control, discretion"
    },
    {
      "question": "音信不通",
      "answer": "おんしんふつう,いんしんふつう",
      "meaning": "break in contact, not hearing from, having no communication with"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦土",
      "answer": "しょうど",
      "meaning": "scorched earth"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘党",
      "answer": "あまとう",
      "meaning": "person who prefers sweet things to alcoholic drinks, person with a sweet tooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "莫迦",
      "answer": "ばか",
      "meaning": "idiot, moron, fool, trivial matter, folly, absurdity, stupid, foolish, dull, absurd, ridiculous, fer"
    },
    {
      "question": "不時着",
      "answer": "ふじちゃく",
      "meaning": "emergency landing, forced landing, crash landing"
    },
    {
      "question": "方位",
      "answer": "ほうい",
      "meaning": "bearing, heading, point of the compass"
    },
    {
      "question": "検閲",
      "answer": "けんえつ",
      "meaning": "censorship, inspection, examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "闇討ち",
      "answer": "やみうち",
      "meaning": "attack under the cover of darkness, surprise attack, sneak attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "人中",
      "answer": "ひとなか,じんちゅう,にんちゅう",
      "meaning": "society, company, the public, the world, in company, among people, philtrum, vertical groove between"
    },
    {
      "question": "清廉潔白",
      "answer": "せいれんけっぱく",
      "meaning": "being upright and cleanhanded"
    },
    {
      "question": "独壇場",
      "answer": "どくだんじょう",
      "meaning": "field in which one acts unchallenged, unrivaled sphere of activity (unrivalled), one's monopoly"
    },
    {
      "question": "口が軽い",
      "answer": "くちがかるい",
      "meaning": "having a loose tongue, being talkative, speaking without thinking, being unable to keep a secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "執行部",
      "answer": "しっこうぶ",
      "meaning": "(the) executive, administration, leadership"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲劇的",
      "answer": "ひげきてき",
      "meaning": "tragic"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹脂",
      "answer": "じゅし",
      "meaning": "resin, rosin"
    },
    {
      "question": "凜々しい",
      "answer": "りりしい",
      "meaning": "gallant, brave, imposing, awe-inspiring, severe, biting, chivalrous, manly, dignified"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻を叩く",
      "answer": "しりをたたく",
      "meaning": "to encourage to do (something), to urge a person on, to demand action, to spank, to give a spanking,"
    },
    {
      "question": "園児",
      "answer": "えんじ",
      "meaning": "kindergarten pupil, kindergartener"
    },
    {
      "question": "虹彩",
      "answer": "こうさい",
      "meaning": "iris (of the eye)"
    },
    {
      "question": "材木",
      "answer": "ざいもく",
      "meaning": "lumber, timber"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪腕",
      "answer": "ごうわん",
      "meaning": "strong arm, stout arm, ability to carry out a difficult job, capable person"
    },
    {
      "question": "細まる",
      "answer": "ほそまる",
      "meaning": "to narrow (e.g. eyes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "信ずる",
      "answer": "しんずる",
      "meaning": "to believe, to believe in, to place trust in, to confide in, to have faith in"
    },
    {
      "question": "拍手喝采",
      "answer": "はくしゅかっさい",
      "meaning": "clapping and cheering, applause"
    },
    {
      "question": "ドラム缶",
      "answer": "ドラムかん",
      "meaning": "drum (e.g. oil, gasoline), metal barrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "不可避",
      "answer": "ふかひ",
      "meaning": "inevitable, inescapable, unavoidable"
    },
    {
      "question": "加賀",
      "answer": "かが",
      "meaning": "Kaga (former province located in the south of present-day Ishikawa Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半生",
      "answer": "はんしょう,はんせい",
      "meaning": "half death, half a lifetime"
    },
    {
      "question": "結城",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "無重力",
      "answer": "むじゅうりょく",
      "meaning": "weightlessness, zero gravity"
    },
    {
      "question": "余所見",
      "answer": "よそみ",
      "meaning": "looking away, looking aside"
    },
    {
      "question": "手堅い",
      "answer": "てがたい",
      "meaning": "steady, firm, solid, secure"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎",
      "answer": "ごと,まい",
      "meaning": "each, every, every (usu. with events, e.g. every weekend)"
    },
    {
      "question": "断わる",
      "answer": "ことわる",
      "meaning": "to refuse, to reject, to dismiss, to turn down, to decline, to inform, to give notice, to tell in ad"
    },
    {
      "question": "機銃",
      "answer": "きじゅう",
      "meaning": "machine gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "水溜まり",
      "answer": "みずたまり",
      "meaning": "puddle, pool of water"
    },
    {
      "question": "安上がり",
      "answer": "やすあがり",
      "meaning": "cheap, economical"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚の骨頂",
      "answer": "ぐのこっちょう",
      "meaning": "the height of folly, sheer stupidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴官",
      "answer": "きかん",
      "meaning": "you"
    },
    {
      "question": "後進",
      "answer": "こうしん",
      "meaning": "one's junior, younger generation, next generation, moving backwards, backing up, reversing"
    },
    {
      "question": "導火線",
      "answer": "どうかせん",
      "meaning": "fuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "沸点",
      "answer": "ふってん",
      "meaning": "boiling point"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗",
      "answer": "むね,しゅう,そう",
      "meaning": "principle, aim, main purpose, central part, pillar, sect, denomination, tenets (of a religious sect)"
    },
    {
      "question": "選び取る",
      "answer": "えらびとる",
      "meaning": "to pick out item(s) from a group to keep"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂喜",
      "answer": "きょうき",
      "meaning": "wild joy, ecstasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗体",
      "answer": "こうたい",
      "meaning": "antibody"
    },
    {
      "question": "白菜",
      "answer": "はくさい,パクチョイ",
      "meaning": "napa cabbage (Brassica rapa subsp. pekinensis), nappa cabbage, Chinese cabbage, bok choy (Brassica r"
    },
    {
      "question": "杜撰",
      "answer": "ずさん,ずざん",
      "meaning": "careless, sloppy, faulty, using unreliable sources (in a piece of writing), piece of writing with un"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷物",
      "answer": "きずもの",
      "meaning": "defective article, damaged goods, deflowered girl, unvirtuous girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "尊顔",
      "answer": "そんがん",
      "meaning": "your countenance (his ..., her ..., etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "攻城",
      "answer": "こうじょう",
      "meaning": "castle siege"
    },
    {
      "question": "最大値",
      "answer": "さいだいち",
      "meaning": "global maximum, greatest value"
    },
    {
      "question": "物々交換",
      "answer": "ぶつぶつこうかん",
      "meaning": "bartering"
    },
    {
      "question": "比べ",
      "answer": "くらべ",
      "meaning": "contest, comparison, competition"
    },
    {
      "question": "明るみ",
      "answer": "あかるみ",
      "meaning": "bright place, the light, the open, light of day, public knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭文字",
      "answer": "かしらもじ",
      "meaning": "first letter of a word, capital letter (at the start of a word or sentence), initials (of one's name"
    },
    {
      "question": "同人",
      "answer": "どうじん,どうにん",
      "meaning": "same person, said person, the person in question, coterie, clique, fraternity, kindred spirits, comr"
    },
    {
      "question": "露天",
      "answer": "ろてん",
      "meaning": "open air"
    },
    {
      "question": "家長",
      "answer": "かちょう",
      "meaning": "patriarch, family head"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝気",
      "answer": "かちき",
      "meaning": "determined spirit, unyielding spirit, will"
    },
    {
      "question": "用向き",
      "answer": "ようむき",
      "meaning": "business, errand, nature of one's business"
    },
    {
      "question": "決断力",
      "answer": "けつだんりょく",
      "meaning": "decisiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲愴",
      "answer": "ひそう",
      "meaning": "pathetic, sad, sorrowful, grievous"
    },
    {
      "question": "平均点",
      "answer": "へいきんてん",
      "meaning": "average mark, mean point"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗派",
      "answer": "しゅうは",
      "meaning": "sect, denomination, school (e.g. of poetry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "場末",
      "answer": "ばすえ",
      "meaning": "outskirts (of a town), run-down district"
    },
    {
      "question": "流星群",
      "answer": "りゅうせいぐん",
      "meaning": "meteor swarm, meteor shower"
    },
    {
      "question": "文房具",
      "answer": "ぶんぼうぐ",
      "meaning": "stationery"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵庫",
      "answer": "ひょうご,へいこ",
      "meaning": "Hyogo (prefecture), armory, armoury, arsenal"
    },
    {
      "question": "武家",
      "answer": "ぶけ",
      "meaning": "samurai, warrior, military family"
    },
    {
      "question": "別途",
      "answer": "べっと",
      "meaning": "separate, special, another, separately"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖遺物",
      "answer": "せいいぶつ",
      "meaning": "relics, relic"
    },
    {
      "question": "巾着",
      "answer": "きんちゃく",
      "meaning": "drawstring purse, money pouch, pouch of fried tofu stuffed with var. ingredients, used in oden, unli"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸与",
      "answer": "たいよ",
      "meaning": "loan, lending"
    },
    {
      "question": "外的",
      "answer": "がいてき",
      "meaning": "external, outside"
    },
    {
      "question": "症例",
      "answer": "しょうれい",
      "meaning": "case"
    },
    {
      "question": "水量",
      "answer": "すいりょう",
      "meaning": "quantity or volume of water"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬場",
      "answer": "ばば",
      "meaning": "horse-riding ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "養育",
      "answer": "よういく",
      "meaning": "bringing up, rearing, upbringing"
    },
    {
      "question": "摘出",
      "answer": "てきしゅつ",
      "meaning": "picking out, taking out, (surgical) removal, exposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵愾心",
      "answer": "てきがいしん",
      "meaning": "hostility, enmity"
    },
    {
      "question": "腫れ物",
      "answer": "はれもの",
      "meaning": "tumor, tumour, swelling, boil, abscess"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅慮",
      "answer": "せんりょ",
      "meaning": "imprudence, indiscretion, thoughtlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "締め切る",
      "answer": "しめきる",
      "meaning": "to close up, to shut up (e.g. behind doors), to cut off (e.g. because a deadline has expired), to cl"
    },
    {
      "question": "号外",
      "answer": "ごうがい",
      "meaning": "newspaper extra"
    },
    {
      "question": "通用口",
      "answer": "つうようぐち",
      "meaning": "side entrance, tradesman's entrance, service entrance, staff entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "特設",
      "answer": "とくせつ",
      "meaning": "setting up specially, special installation"
    },
    {
      "question": "其処",
      "answer": "そこ,それどころ",
      "meaning": "there (place relatively near listener), there (place just mentioned), that place, then (of some inci"
    },
    {
      "question": "携行",
      "answer": "けいこう",
      "meaning": "carrying (on one's person), taking with one"
    },
    {
      "question": "音源",
      "answer": "おんげん",
      "meaning": "sound source, sound generator, tone generator"
    },
    {
      "question": "本田",
      "answer": "ほんでん",
      "meaning": "rice paddy"
    },
    {
      "question": "男湯",
      "answer": "おとこゆ",
      "meaning": "men's bath, men's section in a public bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "香油",
      "answer": "こうゆ",
      "meaning": "pomade, balm, perfumed oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "音楽家",
      "answer": "おんがくか,おんがっか",
      "meaning": "musician"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き血",
      "answer": "いきち",
      "meaning": "lifeblood"
    },
    {
      "question": "重し",
      "answer": "おもし",
      "meaning": "stone weight (as used on pickle-tub covers), weight (as used in balances)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気象",
      "answer": "きしょう",
      "meaning": "weather, climate, disposition, temperament"
    },
    {
      "question": "出任せ",
      "answer": "でまかせ",
      "meaning": "speaking without thinking, words spoken without much thought"
    },
    {
      "question": "人畜無害",
      "answer": "じんちくむがい",
      "meaning": "harmless to humans and animals, having no influence, unimportant, insignificant, harmless"
    },
    {
      "question": "金欠",
      "answer": "きんけつ",
      "meaning": "having no money, lack of money"
    },
    {
      "question": "題する",
      "answer": "だいする",
      "meaning": "to be titled (e.g. a book), to be named"
    },
    {
      "question": "血脈",
      "answer": "けつみゃく,けちみゃく",
      "meaning": "blood vessel, blood relationship"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷解",
      "answer": "ひょうかい",
      "meaning": "being cleared (doubt, misgivings, etc.), being dispelled, melting away, melting (of ice)"
    },
    {
      "question": "外科医",
      "answer": "げかい",
      "meaning": "surgeon"
    },
    {
      "question": "靴箱",
      "answer": "くつばこ",
      "meaning": "shoe box, shoe shelf"
    },
    {
      "question": "左端",
      "answer": "ひだりはし,さたん",
      "meaning": "left end, left edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘技",
      "answer": "ひぎ",
      "meaning": "secret technique"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁天",
      "answer": "べんてん",
      "meaning": "Benten (goddess of arts and wisdom)"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘗める",
      "answer": "なめる",
      "meaning": "to lick, to lap, to suck, to taste, to experience (esp. a hardship), to look down on (someone), to m"
    },
    {
      "question": "電話機",
      "answer": "でんわき",
      "meaning": "telephone (device)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自明",
      "answer": "じめい",
      "meaning": "self-evident, obvious, axiomatic, self-explanatory, trivial"
    },
    {
      "question": "快復",
      "answer": "かいふく",
      "meaning": "recovery (from an illness), recuperation, convalescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "法師",
      "answer": "ほうし,ほっし",
      "meaning": "Buddhist priest, bonze, layman dressed like a priest, person"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩甲骨",
      "answer": "けんこうこつ",
      "meaning": "shoulder blade, scapula"
    },
    {
      "question": "街頭",
      "answer": "がいとう",
      "meaning": "(on the) street"
    },
    {
      "question": "坊主頭",
      "answer": "ぼうずあたま",
      "meaning": "close-cropped hair, shaven head"
    },
    {
      "question": "長閑",
      "answer": "のどか",
      "meaning": "tranquil, calm, quiet, peaceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "克明",
      "answer": "こくめい",
      "meaning": "detailed, scrupulous, careful, minute, faithful, elaborate, diligent, honest, upright, sincere"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し撮り",
      "answer": "かくしどり",
      "meaning": "taking a picture secretly, taking a sneak shot, making a secret video recording, filming without som"
    },
    {
      "question": "準ずる",
      "answer": "じゅんずる",
      "meaning": "to apply correspondingly, to correspond to, to be proportionate to, to conform to"
    },
    {
      "question": "引継ぎ",
      "answer": "ひきつぎ",
      "meaning": "taking over, handing over, transfer of control, inheriting, passing on the baton"
    },
    {
      "question": "疾患",
      "answer": "しっかん",
      "meaning": "disease, ailment, illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "窄まる",
      "answer": "すぼまる,つぼまる",
      "meaning": "to get narrower, to contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "悄然",
      "answer": "しょうぜん",
      "meaning": "dejected, dispirited, crestfallen, discouraged"
    },
    {
      "question": "局部",
      "answer": "きょくぶ",
      "meaning": "part, section, affected part (of the body), private parts, genitals"
    },
    {
      "question": "法外",
      "answer": "ほうがい",
      "meaning": "exorbitant, outrageous, ridiculous, absurd, excessive, inordinate, extravagant, immoderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "一眠り",
      "answer": "ひとねむり",
      "meaning": "nap, short sleep, first sleep of silkworms"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が乗る",
      "answer": "きがのる",
      "meaning": "to come around to do, to become inclined to do, to get excited about, to take an interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み漁る",
      "answer": "よみあさる",
      "meaning": "to read a large number (of), to read widely, to read everything that one can lay one's hands on (usu"
    },
    {
      "question": "梟",
      "answer": "ふくろう,ふくろ,さけ",
      "meaning": "owl (esp. the Ural owl, Strix uralensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "攻め手",
      "answer": "せめて",
      "meaning": "offense, offence, method of attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "不義理",
      "answer": "ふぎり",
      "meaning": "dishonesty, injustice, dishonor, dishonour, ingratitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し売り",
      "answer": "おしうり",
      "meaning": "high-pressure salesmanship, the hard sell, aggressive peddling"
    },
    {
      "question": "量子",
      "answer": "りょうし",
      "meaning": "quantum"
    },
    {
      "question": "血縁関係",
      "answer": "けつえんかんけい",
      "meaning": "blood relationship, blood relations, being genetically related"
    },
    {
      "question": "院内",
      "answer": "いんない",
      "meaning": "inside the House (Diet), inside the hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫紺",
      "answer": "しこん",
      "meaning": "bluish purple"
    },
    {
      "question": "童女",
      "answer": "どうじょ,どうにょ",
      "meaning": "(little) girl"
    },
    {
      "question": "紺碧",
      "answer": "こんぺき",
      "meaning": "deep blue, azure"
    },
    {
      "question": "港湾",
      "answer": "こうわん",
      "meaning": "harbour, harbor"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝染病",
      "answer": "でんせんびょう",
      "meaning": "contagious disease, communicable disease, transmissible disease, infectious disease, epidemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "不法",
      "answer": "ふほう",
      "meaning": "unlawful, illegal, unreasonable, outrageous, unjust, unwarranted"
    },
    {
      "question": "早死に",
      "answer": "はやじに",
      "meaning": "premature death, untimely death, dying young"
    },
    {
      "question": "御使い",
      "answer": "おつかい,みつかい",
      "meaning": "errand, mission, going as envoy, messenger, bearer, errand boy, errand girl, familiar spirit, angel"
    },
    {
      "question": "中国語",
      "answer": "ちゅうごくご",
      "meaning": "Chinese (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子供部屋",
      "answer": "こどもべや",
      "meaning": "child's room, nursery"
    },
    {
      "question": "と来たら",
      "answer": "ときたら",
      "meaning": "when it comes to ..., concerning, where ... are concerned"
    },
    {
      "question": "膝下",
      "answer": "ひざもと,しっか,ひざした",
      "meaning": "near one's knee, (by) one's side, (at) one's hand, place under the protection (of one's parents, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊魂",
      "answer": "れいこん",
      "meaning": "soul, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "硬派",
      "answer": "こうは",
      "meaning": "hard-liners, diehards, hawks, (young) man with traditionally masculine interests, tough boy, man's m"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄養価",
      "answer": "えいようか",
      "meaning": "nutritional value, food value"
    },
    {
      "question": "満杯",
      "answer": "まんぱい",
      "meaning": "full"
    },
    {
      "question": "庶子",
      "answer": "しょし",
      "meaning": "illegitimate child"
    },
    {
      "question": "正道",
      "answer": "せいどう,しょうどう",
      "meaning": "path of righteousness, path of duty, right track, correct path"
    },
    {
      "question": "飢饉",
      "answer": "ききん",
      "meaning": "famine, crop failure, chronic shortage (e.g. of water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸想",
      "answer": "けそう",
      "meaning": "falling in love, attachment"
    },
    {
      "question": "一例",
      "answer": "いちれい",
      "meaning": "example, an instance"
    },
    {
      "question": "原宿",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "秒読み",
      "answer": "びょうよみ",
      "meaning": "countdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "哺乳類",
      "answer": "ほにゅうるい",
      "meaning": "mammal, mammalian"
    },
    {
      "question": "病魔",
      "answer": "びょうま",
      "meaning": "demon of ill health, disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬効",
      "answer": "やっこう",
      "meaning": "medical efficacy, effect of a medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤信号",
      "answer": "あかしんごう",
      "meaning": "red light (traffic), red light, signal to stop, sign of danger"
    },
    {
      "question": "数刻",
      "answer": "すうこく",
      "meaning": "a few hours, several hours, about two to six hours"
    },
    {
      "question": "利き手",
      "answer": "ききて",
      "meaning": "one's dominant hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "意地汚い",
      "answer": "いじきたない",
      "meaning": "gluttonous, greedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "白粉",
      "answer": "おしろい",
      "meaning": "(face) powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯医者",
      "answer": "はいしゃ",
      "meaning": "dentist"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜色満面",
      "answer": "きしょくまんめん",
      "meaning": "being all smiles with joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼装",
      "answer": "れいそう",
      "meaning": "formal dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "直上",
      "answer": "ちょくじょう",
      "meaning": "above, going steadily upward"
    },
    {
      "question": "貼り紙",
      "answer": "はりがみ",
      "meaning": "paper patch, paper backing, poster, sticker, label"
    },
    {
      "question": "泣きべそ",
      "answer": "なきべそ",
      "meaning": "face contorted and about to cry"
    },
    {
      "question": "男気",
      "answer": "おとこぎ,おとこげ,おとこけ",
      "meaning": "chivalrous spirit, chivalry, male presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊急避難",
      "answer": "きんきゅうひなん",
      "meaning": "emergency evacuation"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕っ節",
      "answer": "うでっぷし",
      "meaning": "physical strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "残飯",
      "answer": "ざんぱん",
      "meaning": "leftover food, leftovers, food scraps"
    },
    {
      "question": "土気色",
      "answer": "つちけいろ",
      "meaning": "earth (color, colour), ashen, deathly pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関車",
      "answer": "きかんしゃ",
      "meaning": "locomotive, engine"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄紫",
      "answer": "うすむらさき",
      "meaning": "light purple"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆賊",
      "answer": "ぎゃくぞく",
      "meaning": "rebel, traitor, insurgent"
    },
    {
      "question": "生殺与奪",
      "answer": "せいさつよだつ",
      "meaning": "(having) life-and-death power (over)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本史",
      "answer": "にほんし",
      "meaning": "history of Japan, Japanese history"
    },
    {
      "question": "中退",
      "answer": "ちゅうたい",
      "meaning": "leaving school during a term"
    },
    {
      "question": "続",
      "answer": "ぞく,しょく",
      "meaning": "continuation, sequel"
    },
    {
      "question": "年増",
      "answer": "としま",
      "meaning": "mature woman, middle-aged woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "制定",
      "answer": "せいてい",
      "meaning": "enactment, establishment, creation"
    },
    {
      "question": "決",
      "answer": "けつ",
      "meaning": "decision, vote"
    },
    {
      "question": "胞子",
      "answer": "ほうし",
      "meaning": "spore"
    },
    {
      "question": "演舞",
      "answer": "えんぶ",
      "meaning": "dance performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "高架",
      "answer": "こうか",
      "meaning": "elevated (structure), overhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵便受け",
      "answer": "ゆうびんうけ",
      "meaning": "mailbox, letter box, letterbox, mail slot"
    },
    {
      "question": "失明",
      "answer": "しつめい",
      "meaning": "loss of eyesight, loss of vision, going blind, blindness"
    },
    {
      "question": "開門",
      "answer": "かいもん",
      "meaning": "opening gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "手向け",
      "answer": "たむけ",
      "meaning": "offering to a deity or somebody's spirit, tribute to a person who is about to depart"
    },
    {
      "question": "御飯",
      "answer": "ごはん,おんいい,おまんま",
      "meaning": "cooked rice, meal, steamed rice as an offering to a god"
    },
    {
      "question": "畔",
      "answer": "あぜ,くろ,ほとり",
      "meaning": "ridge of earth between rice fields, ridge between grooves in threshold or lintel, footpath between r"
    },
    {
      "question": "一次",
      "answer": "いちじ",
      "meaning": "first, preliminary, primary (sources, industry, etc.), original, linear (function, equation), first-"
    },
    {
      "question": "餓える",
      "answer": "うえる,かつえる",
      "meaning": "to starve, to be famished, to be hungry, to be starved of (e.g. love), to be thirsty for (e.g. knowl"
    },
    {
      "question": "百面相",
      "answer": "ひゃくめんそう",
      "meaning": "making different (comic) faces, esp. using small props"
    },
    {
      "question": "懸案",
      "answer": "けんあん",
      "meaning": "pending question, unresolved problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "百人力",
      "answer": "ひゃくにんりき",
      "meaning": "tremendous strength, strength of a hundred people"
    },
    {
      "question": "小夜",
      "answer": "さよ",
      "meaning": "evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗証番号",
      "answer": "あんしょうばんごう",
      "meaning": "personal identification number, PIN, password number"
    },
    {
      "question": "一考",
      "answer": "いっこう",
      "meaning": "consideration, thought"
    },
    {
      "question": "語らい",
      "answer": "かたらい",
      "meaning": "talk, chat, troth, lovers' vow"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い込み",
      "answer": "おいこみ",
      "meaning": "final stage, final stretch, final spurt, last spurt, final push, late charge, live printing area (in"
    },
    {
      "question": "烏合の衆",
      "answer": "うごうのしゅう",
      "meaning": "disorderly crowd, mob, rabble"
    },
    {
      "question": "次兄",
      "answer": "じけい",
      "meaning": "second elder brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "無計画",
      "answer": "むけいかく",
      "meaning": "lacking a plan, haphazard"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵影",
      "answer": "てきえい",
      "meaning": "signs of the enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "視聴",
      "answer": "しちょう,してい",
      "meaning": "looking and listening, (television) viewing, attention, interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "篤い",
      "answer": "あつい",
      "meaning": "kind, cordial, hospitable, warm, faithful, serious (of an illness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "火を通す",
      "answer": "ひをとおす",
      "meaning": "to cook, to heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "波状攻撃",
      "answer": "はじょうこうげき",
      "meaning": "attacking in waves"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻が利く",
      "answer": "はながきく",
      "meaning": "to have an acute sense of smell, to have a good nose (e.g. for bargains), to have a keen nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦げ",
      "answer": "こげ",
      "meaning": "scorch, burn, scorching, burnt rice, part of ceramic glaze that has become dark or darkish-brown dur"
    },
    {
      "question": "六花",
      "answer": "りっか",
      "meaning": "snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "美男",
      "answer": "びなん,びだん",
      "meaning": "handsome man"
    },
    {
      "question": "鐘楼",
      "answer": "しょうろう,しゅろう",
      "meaning": "belfry, bell tower"
    },
    {
      "question": "月見",
      "answer": "つきみ",
      "meaning": "moon viewing (esp. during the eight month of the lunar calendar)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小粒",
      "answer": "こつぶ",
      "meaning": "small grain, small stature or ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "厄介払い",
      "answer": "やっかいばらい",
      "meaning": "driving off a troublesome person, getting rid of a nuisance"
    },
    {
      "question": "総括",
      "answer": "そうかつ",
      "meaning": "summarization, summary, generalization, review (by labour or political movements of past activities,"
    },
    {
      "question": "美濃",
      "answer": "みの",
      "meaning": "Mino (former province located in the south of present-day Gifu Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "担い手",
      "answer": "にないて",
      "meaning": "bearer, carrier, person bearing responsibility, person in charge, supporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄ばむ",
      "answer": "きばむ",
      "meaning": "to turn yellow, to become tinged with yellow, to yellow (with age)"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち逃げ",
      "answer": "もちにげ",
      "meaning": "making off with (something), absconding, stolen, absconded (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛虫",
      "answer": "けむし",
      "meaning": "hairy caterpillar, woolly bear, pest, nudnik (nudnick)"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳飾り",
      "answer": "みみかざり",
      "meaning": "earring"
    },
    {
      "question": "品目",
      "answer": "ひんもく,しなめ",
      "meaning": "item, commodity, list of articles"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱立",
      "answer": "らんりつ",
      "meaning": "standing together in a disorderly fashion, standing close around, crowding together, flooding in (ap"
    },
    {
      "question": "選び出す",
      "answer": "えらびだす",
      "meaning": "to select, to pick out"
    },
    {
      "question": "長野",
      "answer": "ながの",
      "meaning": "Nagano (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "最新式",
      "answer": "さいしんしき",
      "meaning": "latest style"
    },
    {
      "question": "語源",
      "answer": "ごげん",
      "meaning": "origin of a word, derivation of a word, etymology"
    },
    {
      "question": "警棒",
      "answer": "けいぼう",
      "meaning": "baton"
    },
    {
      "question": "従姉",
      "answer": "じゅうし,いとこ",
      "meaning": "cousin (elder female)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不眠不休",
      "answer": "ふみんふきゅう",
      "meaning": "no sleep or rest, working day and night"
    },
    {
      "question": "人攫い",
      "answer": "ひとさらい",
      "meaning": "kidnapping, kidnaping, abduction, kidnapper, kidnaper, abductor"
    },
    {
      "question": "原材料",
      "answer": "げんざいりょう",
      "meaning": "raw materials, ingredients"
    },
    {
      "question": "火事場",
      "answer": "かじば",
      "meaning": "scene of a fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "非効率",
      "answer": "ひこうりつ",
      "meaning": "inefficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜神",
      "answer": "りゅうじん",
      "meaning": "dragon god, dragon king, naga"
    },
    {
      "question": "排泄物",
      "answer": "はいせつぶつ",
      "meaning": "excretion, discharge, excrement"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑事",
      "answer": "ざつじ",
      "meaning": "miscellaneous matters"
    },
    {
      "question": "外堀",
      "answer": "そとぼり",
      "meaning": "outer moat (of a castle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "利発",
      "answer": "りはつ",
      "meaning": "intelligence"
    },
    {
      "question": "従軍",
      "answer": "じゅうぐん",
      "meaning": "military service, serving in a war, taking part in a campaign"
    },
    {
      "question": "臍",
      "answer": "へそ,ほぞ",
      "meaning": "navel, belly button, protrusion or depression in the middle of an object, center, centre, most impor"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃",
      "answer": "のう,こ",
      "meaning": "dark (color), concentrated, thick"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒字",
      "answer": "くろじ",
      "meaning": "(being in) the black, surplus, black letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "町外れ",
      "answer": "まちはずれ",
      "meaning": "outskirts (of a town), edge (of a town), just outside the city limits"
    },
    {
      "question": "生後",
      "answer": "せいご",
      "meaning": "post-natal, since birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "達す",
      "answer": "たっす",
      "meaning": "to reach, to get to"
    },
    {
      "question": "僅差",
      "answer": "きんさ",
      "meaning": "narrow margin, slim margin"
    },
    {
      "question": "手作業",
      "answer": "てさぎょう",
      "meaning": "manual labor, manual labour, manual procedures"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼け死ぬ",
      "answer": "やけしぬ",
      "meaning": "to be burnt to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔手",
      "answer": "ましゅ",
      "meaning": "evil influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝命",
      "answer": "はいめい",
      "meaning": "receiving an official appointment, being appointed (to the post of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "煩わす",
      "answer": "わずらわす",
      "meaning": "to trouble, to bother, to annoy, to give trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱帽",
      "answer": "だつぼう",
      "meaning": "removing one's hat, admiring someone greatly, 'taking off one's hat' to someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "高層",
      "answer": "こうそう",
      "meaning": "high-rise (building), multistory, multistoried, tall, high (altitude), upper (atmosphere, air curren"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚職",
      "answer": "おしょく",
      "meaning": "corruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "八千",
      "answer": "はっせん,やち",
      "meaning": "8000, eight thousand, many"
    },
    {
      "question": "公私",
      "answer": "こうし",
      "meaning": "public and private, official and personal, government and people"
    },
    {
      "question": "目が届く",
      "answer": "めがとどく",
      "meaning": "to keep an eye on, to take care of"
    },
    {
      "question": "迂遠",
      "answer": "うえん",
      "meaning": "roundabout, indirect, circuitous, impractical, useless, ignorant (of the world)"
    },
    {
      "question": "野心家",
      "answer": "やしんか",
      "meaning": "ambitious person"
    },
    {
      "question": "人工衛星",
      "answer": "じんこうえいせい",
      "meaning": "artificial satellite, man-made satellite"
    },
    {
      "question": "漬け込む",
      "answer": "つけこむ",
      "meaning": "to pickle thoroughly, to pickle a large amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "傲岸不遜",
      "answer": "ごうがんふそん",
      "meaning": "arrogance"
    },
    {
      "question": "別離",
      "answer": "べつり",
      "meaning": "parting, separation"
    },
    {
      "question": "平安",
      "answer": "へいあん",
      "meaning": "peace, tranquility, tranquillity, Heian period (794-1185)"
    },
    {
      "question": "拒否反応",
      "answer": "きょひはんのう",
      "meaning": "rejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "河川",
      "answer": "かせん",
      "meaning": "rivers"
    },
    {
      "question": "正面衝突",
      "answer": "しょうめんしょうとつ",
      "meaning": "head-on collision"
    },
    {
      "question": "溜まり場",
      "answer": "たまりば",
      "meaning": "gathering spot, haunt, rendezvous, meeting place, hang-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に顔",
      "answer": "しにがお",
      "meaning": "face of a dead person"
    },
    {
      "question": "農耕",
      "answer": "のうこう",
      "meaning": "farming, agriculture, cultivation"
    },
    {
      "question": "競合",
      "answer": "きょうごう",
      "meaning": "contention, competition, rivalry, quarrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "騒がす",
      "answer": "さわがす",
      "meaning": "to annoy, to cause trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "破壊的",
      "answer": "はかいてき",
      "meaning": "destructive, devastating"
    },
    {
      "question": "物欲",
      "answer": "ぶつよく",
      "meaning": "greed, worldly or materialistic desires"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲解",
      "answer": "きょっかい",
      "meaning": "misconstruction, distortion, misinterpretation, misunderstanding, perversion, contortion"
    },
    {
      "question": "笑止",
      "answer": "しょうし",
      "meaning": "laughable, ridiculous, pitiful, contemptible, absurdity"
    },
    {
      "question": "書道",
      "answer": "しょどう",
      "meaning": "calligraphy"
    },
    {
      "question": "効き",
      "answer": "きき",
      "meaning": "effectiveness, efficacy, efficaciousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "刻み",
      "answer": "きざみ",
      "meaning": "shredded tobacco, notch, nick"
    },
    {
      "question": "判断ミス",
      "answer": "はんだんミス",
      "meaning": "error of judgment, miscalculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "山地",
      "answer": "さんち,やまち",
      "meaning": "mountainous district"
    },
    {
      "question": "名状",
      "answer": "めいじょう",
      "meaning": "description, describing, depicting"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶刃",
      "answer": "きょうじん",
      "meaning": "assassin's dagger"
    },
    {
      "question": "結実",
      "answer": "けつじつ",
      "meaning": "fruition, fructification, bearing fruit, bearing fruit (of efforts, plans, etc.), coming to fruition"
    },
    {
      "question": "哉",
      "answer": "かな",
      "meaning": "how!, what!, alas!"
    },
    {
      "question": "禍",
      "answer": "わざわい,まが,か",
      "meaning": "disaster, calamity, misfortune, trouble, woes, wickedness, evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "就ける",
      "answer": "つける",
      "meaning": "to install (a king, emperor, etc.), to appoint (to a post), to promote, to assign (to study under)"
    },
    {
      "question": "時期尚早",
      "answer": "じきしょうそう",
      "meaning": "premature"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆砕",
      "answer": "ばくさい",
      "meaning": "blasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵師",
      "answer": "えし",
      "meaning": "painter, artist, painter supported by patron"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び入り",
      "answer": "とびいり",
      "meaning": "taking part on the spur of the moment, participating without registering beforehand, last-minute ent"
    },
    {
      "question": "養子縁組",
      "answer": "ようしえんぐみ",
      "meaning": "adoption (of a person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "留め金",
      "answer": "とめがね",
      "meaning": "clasp, latch, catch, fastener"
    },
    {
      "question": "冗談半分",
      "answer": "じょうだんはんぶん",
      "meaning": "being somewhat (half) joking, half seriously, half in jest, in a jocular vein"
    },
    {
      "question": "本件",
      "answer": "ほんけん",
      "meaning": "this matter, this case"
    },
    {
      "question": "新大陸",
      "answer": "しんたいりく",
      "meaning": "New World (esp. the Americas, but also Australasia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "表出",
      "answer": "ひょうしゅつ",
      "meaning": "expression, presentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "希少価値",
      "answer": "きしょうかち",
      "meaning": "scarcity value, rarity value, preciousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸送機",
      "answer": "ゆそうき",
      "meaning": "transport aircraft, transport plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "三十路",
      "answer": "みそじ",
      "meaning": "age thirty, one's thirties"
    },
    {
      "question": "一丁前",
      "answer": "いっちょまえ,いっちょうまえ",
      "meaning": "adult, grown-up, person who has come of age, fully fledged, established, qualified"
    },
    {
      "question": "化粧水",
      "answer": "けしょうすい,けしょうみず",
      "meaning": "skin lotion, face lotion, water offered to wrestlers just prior to a bout, fresh water used when mak"
    },
    {
      "question": "護身",
      "answer": "ごしん",
      "meaning": "self-protection"
    },
    {
      "question": "物見",
      "answer": "ものみ",
      "meaning": "sightseeing, scout, patrol, watchtower, lookout"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝謁",
      "answer": "はいえつ",
      "meaning": "having an audience with someone of very high social standing (e.g. the emperor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "挺",
      "answer": "ちょう",
      "meaning": "counter for long and narrow things such as guns, scissors, spades, hoes, inksticks, palanquins, cand"
    },
    {
      "question": "国益",
      "answer": "こくえき",
      "meaning": "national interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "強行軍",
      "answer": "きょうこうぐん",
      "meaning": "forced march, doing something on a very strict schedule"
    },
    {
      "question": "肯く",
      "answer": "うなずく,うなづく",
      "meaning": "to nod, to bow one's head in assent, to agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜け穴",
      "answer": "ぬけあな",
      "meaning": "secret passage, underground passage, loophole"
    },
    {
      "question": "操縦桿",
      "answer": "そうじゅうかん",
      "meaning": "control column, yoke, joystick"
    },
    {
      "question": "仔細",
      "answer": "しさい",
      "meaning": "reasons, circumstances, significance, particulars, hindrance, obstruction, interference"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝帰り",
      "answer": "あさがえり",
      "meaning": "coming home in the morning (after staying out all night)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き分け",
      "answer": "ききわけ",
      "meaning": "reasonableness (esp. of children), obedience"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡礼",
      "answer": "じゅんれい",
      "meaning": "pilgrimage, pilgrim"
    },
    {
      "question": "近代的",
      "answer": "きんだいてき",
      "meaning": "modern"
    },
    {
      "question": "口コミ",
      "answer": "くちコミ",
      "meaning": "word of mouth, comments written online (about a product, service, etc.), online reviews"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦役",
      "answer": "せんえき",
      "meaning": "military campaign, battle, war"
    },
    {
      "question": "高音",
      "answer": "こうおん,たかね",
      "meaning": "high-pitched tone, soprano"
    },
    {
      "question": "眠り込む",
      "answer": "ねむりこむ",
      "meaning": "to fall asleep, to sleep deeply"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み倒す",
      "answer": "ふみたおす",
      "meaning": "to trample down, to crush underfoot, to kick down, to avoid paying (e.g. a debt), to jump (a bill),"
    },
    {
      "question": "消沈",
      "answer": "しょうちん",
      "meaning": "depression, low spirits, dejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲光",
      "answer": "いなびかり",
      "meaning": "(flash of) lightning"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち読み",
      "answer": "たちよみ",
      "meaning": "reading while standing (in a bookstore, etc.), browsing (i.e. reading an item but not buying it)"
    },
    {
      "question": "重箱",
      "answer": "じゅうばこ",
      "meaning": "jūbako, multi-tiered food box"
    },
    {
      "question": "雛鳥",
      "answer": "ひなどり",
      "meaning": "chick, baby bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦績",
      "answer": "せんせき",
      "meaning": "war or military record, score, military achievements, results"
    },
    {
      "question": "童心",
      "answer": "どうしん",
      "meaning": "child's mind, childlike innocence, naivete"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒療治",
      "answer": "あらりょうじ",
      "meaning": "drastic measure or treatment"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅入る",
      "answer": "めいる",
      "meaning": "to feel depressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "神具",
      "answer": "しんぐ,じんぐ",
      "meaning": "votive objects for a home shrine, ritual article"
    },
    {
      "question": "講釈",
      "answer": "こうしゃく",
      "meaning": "explanation (of a text, phrase, etc.), lecture, exposition, explanation (in a pompous fashion), (lon"
    },
    {
      "question": "真鍮",
      "answer": "しんちゅう",
      "meaning": "brass"
    },
    {
      "question": "風流",
      "answer": "ふうりゅう,ふりゅう",
      "meaning": "elegance, taste, refinement"
    },
    {
      "question": "親代わり",
      "answer": "おやがわり",
      "meaning": "(one acting as a) foster parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "子供心",
      "answer": "こどもごころ",
      "meaning": "childlike mind, judgment as a child (judgement)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一一",
      "answer": "いちいち",
      "meaning": "one-by-one, separately, every single, each and every, without omission, fully, in detail"
    },
    {
      "question": "補欠",
      "answer": "ほけつ",
      "meaning": "filling a vacancy, supplementation, substitute, deputy, alternate, spare"
    },
    {
      "question": "昂揚",
      "answer": "こうよう",
      "meaning": "elevation (of spirits), raising (of morale), uplift, upsurge"
    },
    {
      "question": "動物的",
      "answer": "どうぶつてき",
      "meaning": "animal, beastly, carnal, sensual, brute"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し支え",
      "answer": "さしつかえ",
      "meaning": "hindrance, impediment"
    },
    {
      "question": "二重人格",
      "answer": "にじゅうじんかく",
      "meaning": "dual personality, split personality"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕分け",
      "answer": "しわけ",
      "meaning": "classification, assortment, assortment journalizing (in bookkeeping)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活環境",
      "answer": "せいかつかんきょう",
      "meaning": "one's (living) environment"
    },
    {
      "question": "身を削る",
      "answer": "みをけずる",
      "meaning": "to undergo great hardships, to waste away from great effort and worry"
    },
    {
      "question": "白百合",
      "answer": "しらゆり",
      "meaning": "white lily"
    },
    {
      "question": "身を焼く",
      "answer": "みをやく",
      "meaning": "to burn (with jealousy, desire, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "数珠",
      "answer": "じゅず,ずず,じゅじゅ",
      "meaning": "rosary, string of prayer beads"
    },
    {
      "question": "正視",
      "answer": "せいし",
      "meaning": "looking straight ahead, looking in the face, looking squarely at (e.g. a problem), facing (e.g. the"
    },
    {
      "question": "補導",
      "answer": "ほどう",
      "meaning": "guidance, protective custody"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞍替え",
      "answer": "くらがえ",
      "meaning": "changing (one's job, loyalties, stance, etc.), switching over, changing quarters (geisha, prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "小生意気",
      "answer": "こなまいき",
      "meaning": "impudence, cheekiness, impertinence"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛禽類",
      "answer": "もうきんるい",
      "meaning": "birds of prey (of order Falconiformes or Strigiformes), raptors"
    },
    {
      "question": "探り出す",
      "answer": "さぐりだす",
      "meaning": "to spy out, to smell out"
    },
    {
      "question": "獣医",
      "answer": "じゅうい",
      "meaning": "veterinarian, veterinary surgeon, vet"
    },
    {
      "question": "休眠",
      "answer": "きゅうみん",
      "meaning": "idle, dormant"
    },
    {
      "question": "武骨",
      "answer": "ぶこつ",
      "meaning": "boorish, unrefined, rustic, uncouth, clumsy, brusque"
    },
    {
      "question": "重要度",
      "answer": "じゅうようど",
      "meaning": "importance, priority"
    },
    {
      "question": "手荒い",
      "answer": "てあらい",
      "meaning": "violent, rough"
    },
    {
      "question": "移籍",
      "answer": "いせき",
      "meaning": "transfer (of one's name into another family register), transfer (to another team, company, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り込み",
      "answer": "はりこみ",
      "meaning": "stakeout, ambush, cordon, lookout, watch, paste-up, collage"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞典",
      "answer": "じてん,ことばてん",
      "meaning": "dictionary, lexicon"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い戻す",
      "answer": "かいもどす",
      "meaning": "to buy back, to redeem"
    },
    {
      "question": "究極的",
      "answer": "きゅうきょくてき",
      "meaning": "ultimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "素面",
      "answer": "すめん,しらふ",
      "meaning": "not wearing a mask (in kendo, noh, etc.), sober face, sobriety, face with no make-up, unpainted face"
    },
    {
      "question": "美容師",
      "answer": "びようし",
      "meaning": "beautician, cosmetician, hairdresser, hair stylist"
    },
    {
      "question": "高ぶり",
      "answer": "たかぶり",
      "meaning": "excitement, stimulation, agitation, arousal, pride, haughtiness, arrogance"
    },
    {
      "question": "海鳥",
      "answer": "うみどり,かいちょう",
      "meaning": "sea bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "開業",
      "answer": "かいぎょう",
      "meaning": "opening a business, opening a practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "水深",
      "answer": "すいしん",
      "meaning": "depth of water"
    },
    {
      "question": "減じる",
      "answer": "げんじる",
      "meaning": "to decrease, to be reduced, to grow less, to abate, to reduce, to lessen, to cut down, to mitigate,"
    },
    {
      "question": "艶々",
      "answer": "つやつや",
      "meaning": "glossy, bright, slick"
    },
    {
      "question": "後を引く",
      "answer": "あとをひく",
      "meaning": "to be moreish, to have a quality that encourages you to eat (drink) more of them after, to have ling"
    },
    {
      "question": "水銀",
      "answer": "すいぎん",
      "meaning": "mercury (Hg)"
    },
    {
      "question": "開墾",
      "answer": "かいこん",
      "meaning": "cultivating new land, clearing, reclamation"
    },
    {
      "question": "袂",
      "answer": "たもと",
      "meaning": "sleeve (esp. of a kimono), pocket of sleeve, vicinity (esp. of a bridge), foot of a mountain, base o"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕出かす",
      "answer": "しでかす",
      "meaning": "to make a mess, to perpetrate, to do, to finish up, to be guilty of"
    },
    {
      "question": "白身",
      "answer": "しろみ",
      "meaning": "egg white, white-fleshed fish (e.g. tai, hirame, karei), white meat, fatty meat, sapwood"
    },
    {
      "question": "海洋",
      "answer": "かいよう",
      "meaning": "ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "試験管",
      "answer": "しけんかん",
      "meaning": "test tube"
    },
    {
      "question": "立入禁止",
      "answer": "たちいりきんし",
      "meaning": "No Entry, No Trespassing, No Admittance, Off Limits, Keep Out, Keep Off, off-limits, restricted, for"
    },
    {
      "question": "身じろぐ",
      "answer": "みじろぐ",
      "meaning": "to stir, to move"
    },
    {
      "question": "強迫観念",
      "answer": "きょうはくかんねん",
      "meaning": "obsession, unreasonable but compulsive idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "口を慎む",
      "answer": "くちをつつしむ",
      "meaning": "to be careful in speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "菫",
      "answer": "すみれ",
      "meaning": "violet (any flower of genus Viola, esp. the Fuji dawn, Viola mandshurica)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇術",
      "answer": "きじゅつ",
      "meaning": "magic, conjuring, sleight of hand, legerdemain"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗教団体",
      "answer": "しゅうきょうだんたい",
      "meaning": "religious group"
    },
    {
      "question": "間も無く",
      "answer": "まもなく",
      "meaning": "soon, shortly, before long, in a short time, in a little while, having no time to ..., with no time"
    },
    {
      "question": "学区",
      "answer": "がっく",
      "meaning": "school district, school area"
    },
    {
      "question": "冴え",
      "answer": "さえ",
      "meaning": "clearness, clarity, skillfulness (skilfulness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "番地",
      "answer": "ばんち",
      "meaning": "house number, address"
    },
    {
      "question": "密約",
      "answer": "みつやく",
      "meaning": "secret agreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "引け目",
      "answer": "ひけめ",
      "meaning": "sense of inferiority, one's weak point"
    },
    {
      "question": "工面",
      "answer": "くめん,ぐめん",
      "meaning": "contrivance, managing (to raise money), one's financial condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "出雲",
      "answer": "いずも",
      "meaning": "Izumo (former province located in the east of present-day Shimane Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧民",
      "answer": "ひんみん",
      "meaning": "poor people"
    },
    {
      "question": "ごり押し",
      "answer": "ごりおし",
      "meaning": "pushing though, bulldozing, doing something by force, arm twisting"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き死に",
      "answer": "いきしに",
      "meaning": "life and death, life or death"
    },
    {
      "question": "共同体",
      "answer": "きょうどうたい",
      "meaning": "cooperative body, cooperative system, collective, community"
    },
    {
      "question": "時機",
      "answer": "じき",
      "meaning": "opportunity, chance, time, occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "大家族",
      "answer": "だいかぞく",
      "meaning": "large family, extended family"
    },
    {
      "question": "散見",
      "answer": "さんけん",
      "meaning": "being seen here and there, appearing in various places"
    },
    {
      "question": "口利き",
      "answer": "くちきき",
      "meaning": "mediation, good offices, intervention, mediator, middleman, influential person, person of influence,"
    },
    {
      "question": "札幌",
      "answer": "さっぽろ",
      "meaning": "Sapporo (city in Hokkaido)"
    },
    {
      "question": "豚汁",
      "answer": "とんじる,ぶたじる",
      "meaning": "pork miso soup, miso soup with pork and vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "翌週",
      "answer": "よくしゅう",
      "meaning": "the following week, the next week"
    },
    {
      "question": "当座",
      "answer": "とうざ",
      "meaning": "for the time being, for the present, temporarily, for a time, immediate, present, current, for some"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅々",
      "answer": "ちち",
      "meaning": "slow, lagging, tardy"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪合戦",
      "answer": "ゆきがっせん",
      "meaning": "snowball fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "証左",
      "answer": "しょうさ",
      "meaning": "evidence, proof, witness"
    },
    {
      "question": "諺",
      "answer": "ことわざ",
      "meaning": "proverb, saying, aphorism, maxim"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁ずる",
      "answer": "きんずる",
      "meaning": "to forbid, to suppress"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒ぶ",
      "answer": "すさぶ",
      "meaning": "to grow wild, to run to waste, to become degenerate, to become rough (of art, craft, etc.), to lose"
    },
    {
      "question": "剪定",
      "answer": "せんてい",
      "meaning": "pruning"
    },
    {
      "question": "原子",
      "answer": "げんし",
      "meaning": "atom"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛り狂う",
      "answer": "たけりくるう",
      "meaning": "to rage, to rampage"
    },
    {
      "question": "旭",
      "answer": "あさひ",
      "meaning": "morning sun"
    },
    {
      "question": "滞空",
      "answer": "たいくう",
      "meaning": "staying in the air, remaining airborne"
    },
    {
      "question": "空き巣",
      "answer": "あきす",
      "meaning": "empty nest, empty house, empty home, burglary (of an empty house), burglar (who targets empty houses"
    },
    {
      "question": "平屋",
      "answer": "ひらや",
      "meaning": "bungalow, one-story house"
    },
    {
      "question": "掠め取る",
      "answer": "かすめとる",
      "meaning": "to snatch, to steal"
    },
    {
      "question": "肘掛け",
      "answer": "ひじかけ",
      "meaning": "armrest (of a chair), elbow rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "敏腕",
      "answer": "びんわん",
      "meaning": "ability, capability, competence, skill"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗する",
      "answer": "こうする",
      "meaning": "to resist, to defy"
    },
    {
      "question": "四つ目",
      "answer": "よつめ",
      "meaning": "four-eyed, pattern of four squares"
    },
    {
      "question": "不作",
      "answer": "ふさく",
      "meaning": "poor crop, bad harvest, crop failure, low quality (e.g. of literary works)"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄っぺら",
      "answer": "うすっぺら",
      "meaning": "very thin, flimsy, cheap, shallow"
    },
    {
      "question": "団欒",
      "answer": "だんらん",
      "meaning": "sitting together in a circle, happy circle, harmony"
    },
    {
      "question": "決議",
      "answer": "けつぎ",
      "meaning": "resolution, vote, decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "島田",
      "answer": "しまだ",
      "meaning": "pompadour-like hair style, popular for unmarried women in the Edo period, shimada coiffure"
    },
    {
      "question": "大損",
      "answer": "おおぞん,だいそん,たいそん",
      "meaning": "heavy loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "整地",
      "answer": "せいち",
      "meaning": "levelling of ground (for construction), preparation of soil (for planting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "見え",
      "answer": "みえ",
      "meaning": "airs, pretensions, show, ostentation, display, appearance, vanity, charm"
    },
    {
      "question": "穿る",
      "answer": "ほじる,ほじくる",
      "meaning": "to dig up, to dig out, to pick (nose, teeth, etc.), to clean (ears), to pry into, to examine closely"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜き去る",
      "answer": "ぬきさる",
      "meaning": "to pass, to overtake, to leave behind, to pull out, to extract, to remove, to take away"
    },
    {
      "question": "榊",
      "answer": "さかき",
      "meaning": "sakaki (species of evergreen sacred to Shinto, Cleyera japonica), evergreen (esp. one planted or use"
    },
    {
      "question": "二桁",
      "answer": "ふたけた",
      "meaning": "two-digit number, 'tens' column, two digits, double figures"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を切る",
      "answer": "てをきる",
      "meaning": "to cut off (a relationship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "瑞",
      "answer": "みず,ずい",
      "meaning": "youth, freshness, purity, luster (lustre), beauty, good omen, Sweden, Switzerland"
    },
    {
      "question": "人魂",
      "answer": "ひとだま",
      "meaning": "disembodied soul, supernatural fiery ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "無比",
      "answer": "むひ",
      "meaning": "peerless, unparalleled, unparallelled"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹を切る",
      "answer": "はらをきる",
      "meaning": "to commit seppuku, to commit harakiri, to take responsibility (and resign), to laugh until one split"
    },
    {
      "question": "常習犯",
      "answer": "じょうしゅうはん",
      "meaning": "habitual criminal, recidivist, recidivism, habitual criminal activity"
    },
    {
      "question": "皐月",
      "answer": "さつき",
      "meaning": "fifth month of the lunar calendar, satsuki azalea (Rhododendron indicum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "退部",
      "answer": "たいぶ",
      "meaning": "leaving a club, quitting a club"
    },
    {
      "question": "内通",
      "answer": "ないつう",
      "meaning": "secret understanding, collusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "小手調べ",
      "answer": "こてしらべ",
      "meaning": "preliminary test or trial, tryout"
    },
    {
      "question": "生姜",
      "answer": "しょうが,しょうきょう",
      "meaning": "ginger (Zingiber officinale), dried ginger root (trad. medicine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "埼玉",
      "answer": "さいたま",
      "meaning": "Saitama (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "売人",
      "answer": "ばいにん",
      "meaning": "trader, smuggler, pusher, drug dealer, drug runner"
    },
    {
      "question": "崩御",
      "answer": "ほうぎょ",
      "meaning": "death (of an emperor), demise"
    },
    {
      "question": "体外",
      "answer": "たいがい",
      "meaning": "ectogenesis, outside the body"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸縮",
      "answer": "しんしゅく",
      "meaning": "expansion and contraction, elasticity, flexibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "余裕綽々",
      "answer": "よゆうしゃくしゃく",
      "meaning": "calm and collected, with composure, having enough and to spare"
    },
    {
      "question": "学校行事",
      "answer": "がっこうぎょうじ",
      "meaning": "school event"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇む",
      "answer": "いさむ",
      "meaning": "to be in high spirits, to be encouraged, to be lively, to cheer up"
    },
    {
      "question": "火遊び",
      "answer": "ひあそび",
      "meaning": "playing with fire, playing with something dangerous, dangerous act, playing around (with someone), f"
    },
    {
      "question": "一新",
      "answer": "いっしん",
      "meaning": "complete change, reform, restoration, remodeling, remodelling, renewal"
    },
    {
      "question": "苗木",
      "answer": "なえぎ",
      "meaning": "seedling, sapling, young tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "受",
      "answer": "じゅ",
      "meaning": "vedana (sensation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "新聞記事",
      "answer": "しんぶんきじ",
      "meaning": "newspaper story (article, account)"
    },
    {
      "question": "何とやら",
      "answer": "なんとやら",
      "meaning": "for some reason or other, somehow, whatsitsname, what-you-call-it, Mr. so-and-so, and so on, and you"
    },
    {
      "question": "他領",
      "answer": "たりょう",
      "meaning": "another fief"
    },
    {
      "question": "平定",
      "answer": "へいてい",
      "meaning": "suppression, repression, subjugation"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り振り",
      "answer": "わりふり",
      "meaning": "allocation, assignment, allotment"
    },
    {
      "question": "恭順",
      "answer": "きょうじゅん",
      "meaning": "allegiance, obedience, submission"
    },
    {
      "question": "中東",
      "answer": "ちゅうとう",
      "meaning": "Middle East"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍馬",
      "answer": "ぐんば",
      "meaning": "warhorse, army horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟",
      "answer": "なん",
      "meaning": "soft"
    },
    {
      "question": "中途",
      "answer": "ちゅうと",
      "meaning": "halfway, midway, partway, mid-course"
    },
    {
      "question": "狙い目",
      "answer": "ねらいめ",
      "meaning": "one's chance, the right time, target, objective"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩年",
      "answer": "ばんねん",
      "meaning": "one's later years, final years (in life)"
    },
    {
      "question": "固体",
      "answer": "こたい",
      "meaning": "solid (body), solid matter, solid-state"
    },
    {
      "question": "火が付く",
      "answer": "ひがつく",
      "meaning": "to catch fire, to provoke, to catch fire from, to be ignited"
    },
    {
      "question": "来る日",
      "answer": "くるひ",
      "meaning": "the coming days"
    },
    {
      "question": "知る権利",
      "answer": "しるけんり",
      "meaning": "right to know, right to access information"
    },
    {
      "question": "動乱",
      "answer": "どうらん",
      "meaning": "disturbance, agitation, commotion, upheaval, riot"
    },
    {
      "question": "融解",
      "answer": "ゆうかい",
      "meaning": "fusion, melting, liquefaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "標識",
      "answer": "ひょうしき",
      "meaning": "sign, mark, flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚着",
      "answer": "あつぎ",
      "meaning": "wearing thick clothes, dressing warmly"
    },
    {
      "question": "同封",
      "answer": "どうふう",
      "meaning": "enclosing (e.g. with a letter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "武神",
      "answer": "ぶしん",
      "meaning": "god of military arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂言",
      "answer": "きょうげん",
      "meaning": "kyogen, farce presented between noh plays or during the interlude of a noh play, kabuki play, kabuki"
    },
    {
      "question": "風当たり",
      "answer": "かぜあたり",
      "meaning": "exposure to wind, severe criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "神主",
      "answer": "かんぬし,かむぬし",
      "meaning": "Shinto priest, chief Shinto priest (of a shrine), Welsh onion, pun in Buddhist monk jargon"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆鱗",
      "answer": "げきりん",
      "meaning": "one's superior's anger, imperial wrath"
    },
    {
      "question": "権勢",
      "answer": "けんせい",
      "meaning": "power, influence"
    },
    {
      "question": "必定",
      "answer": "ひつじょう",
      "meaning": "inevitably, certainly"
    },
    {
      "question": "部内",
      "answer": "ぶない",
      "meaning": "the staff, inside the department"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸断",
      "answer": "すんだん",
      "meaning": "cutting to pieces, tearing to pieces"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙飛行機",
      "answer": "かみひこうき",
      "meaning": "paper airplane (aeroplane)"
    },
    {
      "question": "求む",
      "answer": "もとむ",
      "meaning": "to want, to wish for, to request, to demand, to seek, to search for, to pursue (pleasure), to hunt ("
    },
    {
      "question": "大筋",
      "answer": "おおすじ",
      "meaning": "outline, summary, gist, basic points"
    },
    {
      "question": "壁越し",
      "answer": "かべごし",
      "meaning": "through a wall, on the other side of a wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "着心地",
      "answer": "きごこち",
      "meaning": "(good or bad) feel when wearing something"
    },
    {
      "question": "浸ける",
      "answer": "つける",
      "meaning": "to soak (in), to steep, to dip, to dunk"
    },
    {
      "question": "指定席",
      "answer": "していせき",
      "meaning": "reserved seat"
    },
    {
      "question": "名士",
      "answer": "めいし",
      "meaning": "celebrity, personage"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈伸",
      "answer": "くっしん",
      "meaning": "bending and stretching (exercise), flexing and extending"
    },
    {
      "question": "火加減",
      "answer": "ひかげん",
      "meaning": "condition of fire, heat level, fire strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "義務教育",
      "answer": "ぎむきょういく",
      "meaning": "compulsory education"
    },
    {
      "question": "古く",
      "answer": "ふるく",
      "meaning": "anciently, formerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "肌着",
      "answer": "はだぎ",
      "meaning": "underwear, underclothes, lingerie, chemise, singlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒味",
      "answer": "どくみ",
      "meaning": "tasting (food or drink) for poison, checking the taste (of a dish), seeing how something tastes"
    },
    {
      "question": "観覧",
      "answer": "かんらん",
      "meaning": "viewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "生産性",
      "answer": "せいさんせい",
      "meaning": "productivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "小分け",
      "answer": "こわけ",
      "meaning": "subdivision"
    },
    {
      "question": "注意力",
      "answer": "ちゅういりょく",
      "meaning": "attentiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖霊",
      "answer": "せいれい,しょうりょう",
      "meaning": "the Holy Ghost, the Holy Spirit, spirit of the deceased"
    },
    {
      "question": "和装",
      "answer": "わそう",
      "meaning": "Japanese clothing, being dressed in a kimono, Japanese-style bookbinding"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒雲",
      "answer": "くろくも,こくうん",
      "meaning": "dark clouds, black clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "諦念",
      "answer": "ていねん",
      "meaning": "understanding and acceptance, spiritual awakening, a heart that understands truth, (feeling of) resi"
    },
    {
      "question": "開け放す",
      "answer": "あけはなす",
      "meaning": "to open wide (doors, windows, etc.), to fling open"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷める",
      "answer": "いためる",
      "meaning": "to hurt, to injure, to cause pain, to harm, to damage, to spoil, to worry, to bother, to be grieved"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷雪",
      "answer": "ひょうせつ",
      "meaning": "ice and snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "荷担",
      "answer": "かたん",
      "meaning": "support, participation, assistance, complicity, conspiracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "相伴",
      "answer": "しょうばん",
      "meaning": "partaking, participating, taking part in, sharing (something with someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水車",
      "answer": "すいしゃ,みずぐるま",
      "meaning": "water wheel, water turbine, hydraulic turbine, violent wielding of weapons"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍び笑い",
      "answer": "しのびわらい",
      "meaning": "stifled laugh, chuckling, snickering"
    },
    {
      "question": "保全",
      "answer": "ほぜん",
      "meaning": "preservation, integrity, conservation, maintenance"
    },
    {
      "question": "心地好い",
      "answer": "ここちよい",
      "meaning": "comfortable, pleasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "喚起",
      "answer": "かんき",
      "meaning": "arousal, excitation, awakening, evocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "捜し物",
      "answer": "さがしもの",
      "meaning": "looking for something, searching for something, object being sought"
    },
    {
      "question": "水位",
      "answer": "すいい",
      "meaning": "water level"
    },
    {
      "question": "入道雲",
      "answer": "にゅうどうぐも",
      "meaning": "cumulonimbus, gigantic columns of clouds (in summer), thunderhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "真髄",
      "answer": "しんずい",
      "meaning": "essence, quintessence, spirit, soul, heart, pith, pith and marrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪漢",
      "answer": "あっかん",
      "meaning": "rascal, villain, scoundrel, ruffian, crook"
    },
    {
      "question": "塞ぎ込む",
      "answer": "ふさぎこむ",
      "meaning": "to mope, to brood, to be in low spirits, to have the blues"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛行艇",
      "answer": "ひこうてい",
      "meaning": "flying boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "水門",
      "answer": "すいもん",
      "meaning": "sluice gate, water gate, flood gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "給与",
      "answer": "きゅうよ",
      "meaning": "pay, salary, wages, allowance, grant, supply, providing with"
    },
    {
      "question": "文芸",
      "answer": "ぶんげい",
      "meaning": "literature, the arts, art and literature, liberal arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "不作法",
      "answer": "ぶさほう",
      "meaning": "ill-mannered, rude"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り抜く",
      "answer": "きりぬく",
      "meaning": "to cut out, to clip from, to extract"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り込み",
      "answer": "きりこみ",
      "meaning": "cut, notch, raid, attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "再燃",
      "answer": "さいねん",
      "meaning": "recurrence, revival, resuscitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "失点",
      "answer": "しってん",
      "meaning": "lost point (in a game), point given away, conceded goal, run charged to the pitcher, blunder, mistak"
    },
    {
      "question": "粋がる",
      "answer": "いきがる",
      "meaning": "to be pretentious, to put on airs, to try to appear smart, to act brave, to try to look cool"
    },
    {
      "question": "預言",
      "answer": "よげん",
      "meaning": "prophecy"
    },
    {
      "question": "実話",
      "answer": "じつわ",
      "meaning": "true story"
    },
    {
      "question": "特権階級",
      "answer": "とっけんかいきゅう",
      "meaning": "privileged class"
    },
    {
      "question": "誉め言葉",
      "answer": "ほめことば",
      "meaning": "words of praise, eulogy, compliment"
    },
    {
      "question": "禿頭",
      "answer": "はげあたま,とくとう",
      "meaning": "bald head, baldness"
    },
    {
      "question": "猿轡",
      "answer": "さるぐつわ",
      "meaning": "(mouth) gag"
    },
    {
      "question": "啼く",
      "answer": "なく",
      "meaning": "to make sound (of an animal), to call, to cry, to whine, to sing, to chirp"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽霊船",
      "answer": "ゆうれいせん",
      "meaning": "ghost ship, phantom ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "当り前",
      "answer": "あたりまえ",
      "meaning": "natural, reasonable, obvious, usual, common, ordinary, commonplace, the norm"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳輪",
      "answer": "にゅうりん",
      "meaning": "areola mammae (circular area around nipple), areola"
    },
    {
      "question": "横っ面",
      "answer": "よこっつら",
      "meaning": "side of face"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝露",
      "answer": "あさつゆ,ちょうろ",
      "meaning": "morning dew"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍術",
      "answer": "にんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "ninjutsu, combat and stealth techniques used by ninja for espionage, sabotage, assassination, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "川岸",
      "answer": "かわぎし",
      "meaning": "riverbank, riverside"
    },
    {
      "question": "政界",
      "answer": "せいかい",
      "meaning": "(world of) politics, political world, political circles"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓道",
      "answer": "きゅうどう",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) archery"
    },
    {
      "question": "如何せん",
      "answer": "いかんせん",
      "meaning": "to one's regret, regrettably, unfortunately, what can be done about ..., ... cannot be helped"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷や冷や",
      "answer": "ひやひや",
      "meaning": "feeling chilly, nervous, anxious, frightened"
    },
    {
      "question": "開錠",
      "answer": "かいじょう",
      "meaning": "unlocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬湯",
      "answer": "やくとう,くすりゆ,やくゆ",
      "meaning": "medicated bath, (medical) decoction, infusion, medicinal hot spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜着",
      "answer": "よぎ",
      "meaning": "night-clothes, heavy kimono-like quilt"
    },
    {
      "question": "色紙",
      "answer": "いろがみ,しきし",
      "meaning": "coloured paper, colored paper, square fancy cardboard, used for autographs, poetry, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "咎人",
      "answer": "とがにん",
      "meaning": "offender, criminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "渾名",
      "answer": "あだな,こんめい",
      "meaning": "nickname"
    },
    {
      "question": "高圧",
      "answer": "こうあつ",
      "meaning": "high voltage, high pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "怨み",
      "answer": "うらみ",
      "meaning": "resentment, grudge, malice, bitterness, matter for regret, regret"
    },
    {
      "question": "場外",
      "answer": "じょうがい",
      "meaning": "outside the hall (or stadium, market, etc.), off the grounds, off the premises, off-track"
    },
    {
      "question": "野山",
      "answer": "のやま",
      "meaning": "hills and fields, hill and dale"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺骸",
      "answer": "いがい,ゆいがい",
      "meaning": "remains, corpse, body"
    },
    {
      "question": "影絵",
      "answer": "かげえ",
      "meaning": "shadow picture, silhouette, shadowgraph"
    },
    {
      "question": "邸内",
      "answer": "ていない",
      "meaning": "grounds, premises"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹精",
      "answer": "たんせい",
      "meaning": "working earnestly, sincerity, diligence, effort, pains"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒涼",
      "answer": "こうりょう",
      "meaning": "desolate, dreary, bleak"
    },
    {
      "question": "創世",
      "answer": "そうせい",
      "meaning": "creation of the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋上",
      "answer": "ようじょう",
      "meaning": "on the sea, on the ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "即断",
      "answer": "そくだん",
      "meaning": "prompt decision, snap judgement, snap judgment"
    },
    {
      "question": "閑静",
      "answer": "かんせい",
      "meaning": "quiet (e.g. neighbourhood), peaceful, tranquil"
    },
    {
      "question": "棲息",
      "answer": "せいそく",
      "meaning": "inhabiting, living"
    },
    {
      "question": "集中攻撃",
      "answer": "しゅうちゅうこうげき",
      "meaning": "(making, launching) concentrated attack (on, against)"
    },
    {
      "question": "難所",
      "answer": "なんしょ",
      "meaning": "perilous pass (on a route or journey), rough spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "特売",
      "answer": "とくばい",
      "meaning": "special sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "山登り",
      "answer": "やまのぼり",
      "meaning": "mountain climbing, mountaineering"
    },
    {
      "question": "収容所",
      "answer": "しゅうようじょ",
      "meaning": "internment camp, detention facility, POW camp, refugee camp"
    },
    {
      "question": "義足",
      "answer": "ぎそく",
      "meaning": "artificial leg"
    },
    {
      "question": "永",
      "answer": "とこしえ,なが",
      "meaning": "eternity, permanence, perpetuity, long"
    },
    {
      "question": "予",
      "answer": "よ",
      "meaning": "I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "園長",
      "answer": "えんちょう",
      "meaning": "head of a garden, kindergarten principal, nursery school principal, park director, zoo director, hea"
    },
    {
      "question": "退職金",
      "answer": "たいしょくきん",
      "meaning": "severance payment, retirement money (usu. lump-sum), redundancy payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "惣菜",
      "answer": "そうざい",
      "meaning": "small dish (served as a part of an ordinary household meal), side dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "能がない",
      "answer": "のうがない",
      "meaning": "incompetent, have no merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "共演",
      "answer": "きょうえん",
      "meaning": "appearing together, co-acting, co-starring"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ盛り",
      "answer": "まっさかり",
      "meaning": "height of, middle of, full bloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "東京湾",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "如し",
      "answer": "ごとし",
      "meaning": "like, as if, the same as"
    },
    {
      "question": "印鑑",
      "answer": "いんかん",
      "meaning": "stamp, seal"
    },
    {
      "question": "煤ける",
      "answer": "すすける",
      "meaning": "to be sooty, to be stained"
    },
    {
      "question": "人心地",
      "answer": "ひとごこち",
      "meaning": "consciousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "寮長",
      "answer": "りょうちょう",
      "meaning": "dormitory leader, dormitory superintendent"
    },
    {
      "question": "手指",
      "answer": "てゆび,しゅし",
      "meaning": "finger"
    },
    {
      "question": "選手権",
      "answer": "せんしゅけん",
      "meaning": "championship, title (of champion)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不定期",
      "answer": "ふていき",
      "meaning": "irregular, indeterminate, tramp (steamer)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小銃",
      "answer": "しょうじゅう",
      "meaning": "rifle, small arms"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓守",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "擽る",
      "answer": "くすぐる,こそぐる",
      "meaning": "to tickle, to tickle (one's curiosity, vanity, etc.), to arouse, to appeal to, to flatter, to make l"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳震盪",
      "answer": "のうしんとう",
      "meaning": "concussion (of the brain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬が合う",
      "answer": "うまがあう",
      "meaning": "to get on well (with a person), to be a good match with one's horse (e.g. of a rider)"
    },
    {
      "question": "騎手",
      "answer": "きしゅ",
      "meaning": "horseman, rider, jockey"
    },
    {
      "question": "山肌",
      "answer": "やまはだ",
      "meaning": "mountain's surface, bare surface of a mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "一群",
      "answer": "いちぐん",
      "meaning": "group, flock, crowd, herd, wide expanse (of flowers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "通ずる",
      "answer": "つうずる",
      "meaning": "to be open (to traffic), to lead to, to communicate (with), to flow (liquid, current), to pass, to g"
    },
    {
      "question": "王政",
      "answer": "おうせい",
      "meaning": "monarchy, imperial rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚め",
      "answer": "あつめ",
      "meaning": "thick (esp. paper, cloth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "会館",
      "answer": "かいかん",
      "meaning": "meeting hall, assembly hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "五指",
      "answer": "ごし",
      "meaning": "the five fingers, leading five, top five"
    },
    {
      "question": "主戦",
      "answer": "しゅせん",
      "meaning": "advocacy of war"
    },
    {
      "question": "連なり",
      "answer": "つらなり",
      "meaning": "series (of something), range (e.g. of mountains)"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗面器",
      "answer": "せんめんき",
      "meaning": "wash basin, wash bowl (incl. portable bowl in a public bath)"
    },
    {
      "question": "社交性",
      "answer": "しゃこうせい",
      "meaning": "sociability"
    },
    {
      "question": "片田舎",
      "answer": "かたいなか",
      "meaning": "back country, remote countryside"
    },
    {
      "question": "襲名",
      "answer": "しゅうめい",
      "meaning": "succession to another's professional name"
    },
    {
      "question": "大吉",
      "answer": "だいきち",
      "meaning": "excellent luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "消火器",
      "answer": "しょうかき",
      "meaning": "fire extinguisher"
    },
    {
      "question": "翼竜",
      "answer": "よくりゅう",
      "meaning": "pterosaur"
    },
    {
      "question": "見参",
      "answer": "けんざん,げんざん",
      "meaning": "seeing, meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "外回り",
      "answer": "そとまわり",
      "meaning": "circumference, perimeter, work outside the office, outer tracks (in a loop or curve)"
    },
    {
      "question": "義賊",
      "answer": "ぎぞく",
      "meaning": "chivalrous thief"
    },
    {
      "question": "配偶者",
      "answer": "はいぐうしゃ",
      "meaning": "spouse, wife, husband, partner"
    },
    {
      "question": "第一人者",
      "answer": "だいいちにんしゃ",
      "meaning": "leading person, foremost figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "最たる",
      "answer": "さいたる",
      "meaning": "prime, conspicuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "致死",
      "answer": "ちし",
      "meaning": "lethal, fatal"
    },
    {
      "question": "列挙",
      "answer": "れっきょ",
      "meaning": "enumeration, list"
    },
    {
      "question": "紛い",
      "answer": "まがい",
      "meaning": "imitation, sham, -like"
    },
    {
      "question": "大敵",
      "answer": "たいてき",
      "meaning": "great rival, powerful enemy, archenemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "海産物",
      "answer": "かいさんぶつ",
      "meaning": "marine products"
    },
    {
      "question": "透明人間",
      "answer": "とうめいにんげん",
      "meaning": "invisible person (in science fiction, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "断裂",
      "answer": "だんれつ",
      "meaning": "snapping apart"
    },
    {
      "question": "行先",
      "answer": "いきさき,ゆきさき",
      "meaning": "destination, whereabouts, future, prospects"
    },
    {
      "question": "到る",
      "answer": "いたる",
      "meaning": "to arrive at (e.g. a decision), to reach (a stage), to attain, to lead to (a place), to get to, in t"
    },
    {
      "question": "心の友",
      "answer": "こころのとも",
      "meaning": "one's bosom friend, kindred-spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫い目",
      "answer": "ぬいめ",
      "meaning": "seam, stitch, suture"
    },
    {
      "question": "医院",
      "answer": "いいん",
      "meaning": "doctor's office (surgery), clinic, dispensary"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠れ里",
      "answer": "かくれざと",
      "meaning": "hidden village (esp. hidden retreat for nobles or refuge for soldiers of a defeated army), isolated"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵法",
      "answer": "へいほう,ひょうほう",
      "meaning": "art of war, strategy, tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "三色",
      "answer": "さんしょく",
      "meaning": "three colours, three colors, triple run, winning hand containing the same chow in each of the three"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎の子",
      "answer": "とらのこ",
      "meaning": "tiger cub, one's treasure, precious"
    },
    {
      "question": "深遠",
      "answer": "しんえん",
      "meaning": "profound, deep, unfathomable"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺し殺す",
      "answer": "さしころす",
      "meaning": "to stab to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "油を売る",
      "answer": "あぶらをうる",
      "meaning": "to loaf (particularly on the job), to idle one's time away, to dawdle"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮き彫り",
      "answer": "うきぼり",
      "meaning": "relief, embossed carving, bringing to the fore, throwing something into relief"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い置く",
      "answer": "いいおく",
      "meaning": "to leave word, to leave a message"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶の間",
      "answer": "ちゃのま",
      "meaning": "living room (Japanese-style)"
    },
    {
      "question": "別居",
      "answer": "べっきょ",
      "meaning": "separation, living apart"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち行く",
      "answer": "たちゆく,たちいく",
      "meaning": "to maintain itself, to last, to make itself pay, to make a living, to keep going"
    },
    {
      "question": "随伴",
      "answer": "ずいはん",
      "meaning": "attendance, accompanying, following, adjoint"
    },
    {
      "question": "餡",
      "answer": "あん",
      "meaning": "red bean paste, red bean jam, anko, kudzu sauce, filling (of a dumpling, etc.), filling, stuffing, i"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由落下",
      "answer": "じゆうらっか",
      "meaning": "free fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "男衆",
      "answer": "おとこしゅう,おとこしゅ,おとこし",
      "meaning": "men, manservant, male attendants to an actor"
    },
    {
      "question": "上物",
      "answer": "じょうもの",
      "meaning": "quality goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "走らす",
      "answer": "はしらす",
      "meaning": "to dispatch (someone), to send, to make run, to make go fast (a car, horse, etc.), to drive, to ride"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍耐力",
      "answer": "にんたいりょく",
      "meaning": "fortitude, perseverance, stoicism, patience"
    },
    {
      "question": "柊",
      "answer": "ひいらぎ,ひらぎ",
      "meaning": "holly olive (Osmanthus heterophyllus), false holly, holly, spotnape ponyfish (Leiognathus nuchalis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣り取り",
      "answer": "やりとり",
      "meaning": "giving and taking, exchange (of letters), arguing back and forth, (conversational) exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "定規",
      "answer": "じょうぎ",
      "meaning": "(measuring) ruler"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪奇",
      "answer": "かいき",
      "meaning": "bizarre, strange, weird, mysterious, grotesque"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑問点",
      "answer": "ぎもんてん",
      "meaning": "point of uncertainty, unclarified issue, doubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛玩動物",
      "answer": "あいがんどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "pet (animal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "発祥",
      "answer": "はっしょう",
      "meaning": "origin, appearance of auspicious omen"
    },
    {
      "question": "交ぜる",
      "answer": "まぜる",
      "meaning": "to mix, to stir, to blend"
    },
    {
      "question": "付き物",
      "answer": "つきもの",
      "meaning": "essential part, indispensable part, unavoidable part, accompaniment, appendage, accessory, front and"
    },
    {
      "question": "石柱",
      "answer": "せきちゅう",
      "meaning": "stone pillar"
    },
    {
      "question": "時代錯誤",
      "answer": "じだいさくご",
      "meaning": "anachronism"
    },
    {
      "question": "専売特許",
      "answer": "せんばいとっきょ",
      "meaning": "patent, one's specialty (party piece, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽衣",
      "answer": "はごろも,うい",
      "meaning": "angel's raiment, robe of feathers, wings of birds or insects, plumage of birds, type of bug"
    },
    {
      "question": "受領",
      "answer": "じゅりょう,ずりょう,ずろう",
      "meaning": "receipt (of a letter, money, etc.), acceptance, receiving, provincial governor (from the middle of t"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧師",
      "answer": "ぼくし",
      "meaning": "pastor, minister, clergyman, reverend"
    },
    {
      "question": "白竜",
      "answer": "ペーロン,はくりょう,はくりゅう",
      "meaning": "dragon boat (long 22-person canoe used for racing), races with such boats, white dragon"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖教",
      "answer": "せいきょう",
      "meaning": "sacred teachings, Confucianism, Christianity"
    },
    {
      "question": "老衰",
      "answer": "ろうすい",
      "meaning": "senility, senile decay, infirmity (through age)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小麦色",
      "answer": "こむぎいろ",
      "meaning": "light brown, golden brown, tan"
    },
    {
      "question": "能動的",
      "answer": "のうどうてき",
      "meaning": "active"
    },
    {
      "question": "彷徨",
      "answer": "ほうこう",
      "meaning": "wandering, rambling, roaming"
    },
    {
      "question": "監修",
      "answer": "かんしゅう",
      "meaning": "(editorial) supervision, general editorship, supervising director"
    },
    {
      "question": "南米",
      "answer": "なんべい",
      "meaning": "South America"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇宙服",
      "answer": "うちゅうふく",
      "meaning": "space suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "太夫",
      "answer": "たゆう",
      "meaning": "high-ranking noh actor, head of a school of noh performance, high ranking courtesan (esp. in Yoshiwa"
    },
    {
      "question": "至難",
      "answer": "しなん",
      "meaning": "most difficult, next to impossible"
    },
    {
      "question": "拍",
      "answer": "はく",
      "meaning": "beat, mora"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き物",
      "answer": "かきもの",
      "meaning": "(piece of) writing, document, (act of) writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "魑魅魍魎",
      "answer": "ちみもうりょう",
      "meaning": "evil spirits of rivers and mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "尺度",
      "answer": "しゃくど",
      "meaning": "gauge, standard, measure, criterion, index, length, size, (measuring) rule, scale"
    },
    {
      "question": "木戸",
      "answer": "きど",
      "meaning": "wicket gate, wooden door, entrance to an entertainment venue (i.e. sumo arena, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち直り",
      "answer": "たちなおり",
      "meaning": "recovery, restoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗄れる",
      "answer": "しゃがれる,しわがれる,かれる",
      "meaning": "to become hoarse, to grow hoarse, to become husky"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗り",
      "answer": "ぬり",
      "meaning": "coating (esp. lacquering)"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖",
      "answer": "だん",
      "meaning": "warming, warmth"
    },
    {
      "question": "刮目",
      "answer": "かつもく",
      "meaning": "careful observation, close attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "機能的",
      "answer": "きのうてき",
      "meaning": "functional, efficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "手渡し",
      "answer": "てわたし",
      "meaning": "personal delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "二人三脚",
      "answer": "ににんさんきゃく",
      "meaning": "three-legged race, cooperation with singleness of purpose (e.g. between companies), operating in tan"
    },
    {
      "question": "有難う",
      "answer": "ありがとう",
      "meaning": "thank you, thanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "好色",
      "answer": "こうしょく",
      "meaning": "lasciviousness, lechery, salaciousness, lust, sensuality, lewdness"
    },
    {
      "question": "露払い",
      "answer": "つゆはらい",
      "meaning": "outrider, herald, rikishi who leads the yokozuna to the ring prior to his ring-entering ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "新顔",
      "answer": "しんがお",
      "meaning": "newcomer, new face"
    },
    {
      "question": "衣裳",
      "answer": "いしょう",
      "meaning": "clothing, costume, outfit, garment, dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "単行本",
      "answer": "たんこうぼん",
      "meaning": "tankōbon, (manga) volume, (comic) trade paperback, single book (as opposed to magazine, anthology, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴い",
      "answer": "とうとい,たっとい",
      "meaning": "precious, valuable, priceless, noble, exalted, sacred"
    },
    {
      "question": "飽く",
      "answer": "あく",
      "meaning": "to tire of, to lose interest in, to be satisfied, to enjoy, to do adequately"
    },
    {
      "question": "搦め手",
      "answer": "からめて,からめで",
      "meaning": "rear gate (esp. of castle), back entrance, one who arrests, force attacking the rear of a castle, (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "燦々",
      "answer": "さんさん",
      "meaning": "brilliant, bright"
    },
    {
      "question": "北の方",
      "answer": "きたのかた",
      "meaning": "northward, facing the north, nobleman's true wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "工学",
      "answer": "こうがく",
      "meaning": "engineering"
    },
    {
      "question": "刹那的",
      "answer": "せつなてき",
      "meaning": "ephemeral, transitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "師長",
      "answer": "しちょう",
      "meaning": "teachers, superiors, and men of prominence"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽化",
      "answer": "うか",
      "meaning": "emergence (of insects), eclosion, growing wings"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸糞",
      "answer": "むなくそ,むねくそ",
      "meaning": "chest, breast"
    },
    {
      "question": "北斗",
      "answer": "ほくと",
      "meaning": "the Big Dipper (asterism), the Plough, the Plow"
    },
    {
      "question": "頰杖",
      "answer": "ほおづえ,ほほづえ,つらづえ",
      "meaning": "resting one's chin in one's hands, brace (in construction), angle brace"
    },
    {
      "question": "囀る",
      "answer": "さえずる",
      "meaning": "to sing, to chirp, to twitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷水",
      "answer": "こおりみず,こおりすい,ひみず",
      "meaning": "ice water, shaved ice (usually served with flavored simple syrup)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半熟",
      "answer": "はんじゅく",
      "meaning": "half-cooked, half-done, soft-boiled, half-ripe, unripe"
    },
    {
      "question": "長文",
      "answer": "ちょうぶん",
      "meaning": "long sentence, long piece of writing (e.g. passage, letter, article, telegram)"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち味",
      "answer": "もちあじ",
      "meaning": "inherent flavor, inherent flavour, natural taste, distinctive characteristic (of a person, work, etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "後天的",
      "answer": "こうてんてき",
      "meaning": "a posteriori, acquired"
    },
    {
      "question": "駆逐艦",
      "answer": "くちくかん",
      "meaning": "destroyer (ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "確",
      "answer": "たしか,かく",
      "meaning": "sure, certain, positive, definite, reliable, trustworthy, safe, sound, firm, accurate, correct, exac"
    },
    {
      "question": "留意",
      "answer": "りゅうい",
      "meaning": "heeding, paying attention, bearing in mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "来場",
      "answer": "らいじょう,らいば",
      "meaning": "attendance"
    },
    {
      "question": "空襲",
      "answer": "くうしゅう",
      "meaning": "air-raid"
    },
    {
      "question": "内腿",
      "answer": "うちもも",
      "meaning": "inner thigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "武芸者",
      "answer": "ぶげいしゃ",
      "meaning": "master of martial arts, practitioner of martial arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "駈ける",
      "answer": "かける",
      "meaning": "to run, to dash, to race, to gallop (on horseback), to canter, to advance (against one's enemy), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "膳",
      "answer": "ぜん",
      "meaning": "small dining table (usu. for a single person), serving tray (with legs), meal, food, serving, counte"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠員",
      "answer": "けついん",
      "meaning": "vacancy, vacant position"
    },
    {
      "question": "公立",
      "answer": "こうりつ",
      "meaning": "public (institution)"
    },
    {
      "question": "必中",
      "answer": "ひっちゅう",
      "meaning": "hitting the target"
    },
    {
      "question": "倒",
      "answer": "さかしま,さかさま,さか",
      "meaning": "reverse, inversion, upside down, unreasonable, absurd, wrong, inverted, reversed, back to front, inv"
    },
    {
      "question": "食券",
      "answer": "しょっけん",
      "meaning": "meal ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "通商",
      "answer": "つうしょう",
      "meaning": "commerce, trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "人嫌い",
      "answer": "ひとぎらい",
      "meaning": "misanthropy, misanthrope"
    },
    {
      "question": "政敵",
      "answer": "せいてき",
      "meaning": "political opponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "個々人",
      "answer": "ここじん",
      "meaning": "an individual, individual people"
    },
    {
      "question": "倒木",
      "answer": "とうぼく",
      "meaning": "fallen tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "御名",
      "answer": "ぎょめい,みな",
      "meaning": "name of the emperor, name of God (esp. in Christian contexts), name of Christ"
    },
    {
      "question": "前言",
      "answer": "ぜんげん",
      "meaning": "previous remarks"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び半分",
      "answer": "あそびはんぶん",
      "meaning": "half in fun"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵌め込む",
      "answer": "はめこむ",
      "meaning": "to inlay, to insert, to set, to plug in (to a formula), to immerse, to trick, to deceive"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫合",
      "answer": "ほうごう",
      "meaning": "sewing together, stitching up (a wound), suture"
    },
    {
      "question": "標準的",
      "answer": "ひょうじゅんてき",
      "meaning": "standard, standardized, average, normal, ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪商",
      "answer": "ごうしょう",
      "meaning": "wealthy merchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "本筋",
      "answer": "ほんすじ",
      "meaning": "main thread (of a story)"
    },
    {
      "question": "魂魄",
      "answer": "こんぱく",
      "meaning": "soul, spirit, ghost"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛髪",
      "answer": "もうはつ",
      "meaning": "hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "趨勢",
      "answer": "すうせい",
      "meaning": "tendency, trend"
    },
    {
      "question": "非常食",
      "answer": "ひじょうしょく",
      "meaning": "emergency rations"
    },
    {
      "question": "果実酒",
      "answer": "かじつしゅ",
      "meaning": "fruit wine (e.g. cider, wine, plum liquor), fruit liqueur"
    },
    {
      "question": "確信犯",
      "answer": "かくしんはん",
      "meaning": "crime of conscience, premeditated crime, act carried out while knowing that it should not be"
    },
    {
      "question": "手広い",
      "answer": "てびろい",
      "meaning": "spacious, roomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "警笛",
      "answer": "けいてき",
      "meaning": "horn, alarm, whistle, foghorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "注意書き",
      "answer": "ちゅういがき",
      "meaning": "notes, instructions"
    },
    {
      "question": "内科",
      "answer": "ないか",
      "meaning": "internal medicine, i.e. treatment by medical procedures rather than surgical procedures, department"
    },
    {
      "question": "瑠璃色",
      "answer": "るりいろ",
      "meaning": "lapis lazuli blue, bright blue, azure"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩り場",
      "answer": "かりば",
      "meaning": "hunting ground, hunting preserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "習熟",
      "answer": "しゅうじゅく",
      "meaning": "proficiency, mastery, becoming proficient (in)"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶々",
      "answer": "ちゃちゃ",
      "meaning": "interruption (e.g. of a conversation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "刷る",
      "answer": "する",
      "meaning": "to print, to color or pattern fabric using a wooden mold"
    },
    {
      "question": "間借り",
      "answer": "まがり",
      "meaning": "renting a room"
    },
    {
      "question": "降らす",
      "answer": "ふらす",
      "meaning": "to send (rain), to shed"
    },
    {
      "question": "時間潰し",
      "answer": "じかんつぶし",
      "meaning": "timewasting, killing time"
    },
    {
      "question": "曳く",
      "answer": "ひく",
      "meaning": "to pull, to tug, to lead (e.g. a horse), to draw (attention, sympathy, etc.), to attract (e.g. inter"
    },
    {
      "question": "海路",
      "answer": "かいろ,うみじ,うなじ",
      "meaning": "sea route"
    },
    {
      "question": "不定形",
      "answer": "ふていけい",
      "meaning": "indeterminate form, undefined, indefinite, unstructured, protean, amorphous"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒好き",
      "answer": "さけずき",
      "meaning": "love of drink, fondness for alcohol, person who likes to drink, drinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "花婿",
      "answer": "はなむこ",
      "meaning": "bridegroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "低温",
      "answer": "ていおん",
      "meaning": "low temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "目礼",
      "answer": "もくれい",
      "meaning": "nodding, greeting (with eyes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い被る",
      "answer": "かいかぶる",
      "meaning": "to overestimate (someone), to overrate, to think too highly of, to make too much of, to give (someon"
    },
    {
      "question": "光子",
      "answer": "こうし",
      "meaning": "photon"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕官",
      "answer": "しかん",
      "meaning": "government service, entering government service, (of a ronin) finding a new lord or master to serve"
    },
    {
      "question": "期末",
      "answer": "きまつ",
      "meaning": "end of term"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞任",
      "answer": "じにん",
      "meaning": "resignation (from a position)"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸送船",
      "answer": "ゆそうせん",
      "meaning": "transport ship, troop ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "口止め料",
      "answer": "くちどめりょう",
      "meaning": "hush money"
    },
    {
      "question": "押入れ",
      "answer": "おしいれ",
      "meaning": "closet"
    },
    {
      "question": "偶々",
      "answer": "たまたま",
      "meaning": "occasionally, once in a while, seldom, casually, unexpectedly, accidentally, by chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "積年",
      "answer": "せきねん",
      "meaning": "(many) years, long-standing (esp. hatred, grudge), ancient"
    },
    {
      "question": "運び屋",
      "answer": "はこびや",
      "meaning": "courier, smuggler, carrier (e.g. of illegal drugs), trafficker"
    },
    {
      "question": "表裏一体",
      "answer": "ひょうりいったい",
      "meaning": "the two views (of an object) referring to the same thing, being inseparable like the two sides of an"
    },
    {
      "question": "拒否る",
      "answer": "きょひる",
      "meaning": "to refuse, to reject, to deny"
    },
    {
      "question": "着地点",
      "answer": "ちゃくちてん",
      "meaning": "landing place (for aircraft), common ground, compromise, agreement, conclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "物証",
      "answer": "ぶっしょう",
      "meaning": "evidence, exhibit"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠",
      "answer": "あくび,けつ",
      "meaning": "yawn, yawning, kanji 'yawning' radical (radical 76), lack, deficiency, vacancy, absence, non-attenda"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴れ初め",
      "answer": "なれそめ",
      "meaning": "start of a romance, beginning of love"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩的",
      "answer": "してき",
      "meaning": "poetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "千差万別",
      "answer": "せんさばんべつ,せんさまんべつ",
      "meaning": "an infinite variety of, multifarious, being extremely varied and wide-ranging"
    },
    {
      "question": "簀巻き",
      "answer": "すまき",
      "meaning": "wrapping something in a bamboo mat, wrapping somebody in a bamboo mat and throwing him in a river (E"
    },
    {
      "question": "陳情",
      "answer": "ちんじょう",
      "meaning": "petition, appeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "大和撫子",
      "answer": "やまとなでしこ",
      "meaning": "large pink (Dianthus superbus var. longicalycinus), woman who displays the feminine virtues of old J"
    },
    {
      "question": "異端者",
      "answer": "いたんしゃ",
      "meaning": "heathen, heretic, pagan, nonconformist, freethinker, iconoclast, rebel"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑炊",
      "answer": "ぞうすい",
      "meaning": "rice gruel containing vegetables, fish, etc., and seasoned with miso or soy sauce"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み",
      "answer": "くみ",
      "meaning": "set (of items), group (of people), class (of students), company (esp. construction), family (i.e. ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "揉み消す",
      "answer": "もみけす",
      "meaning": "to stub out (e.g. a cigarette), to crush out, to smother (fire), to hush up, to cover up, to stifle,"
    },
    {
      "question": "手直し",
      "answer": "てなおし",
      "meaning": "adjustment, tweaking, improvement, modification, tinkering, minor alteration, correction"
    },
    {
      "question": "藻",
      "answer": "も",
      "meaning": "algae, waterweed, seaweed, duckweed"
    },
    {
      "question": "比する",
      "answer": "ひする",
      "meaning": "to compare"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐肉",
      "answer": "ふにく",
      "meaning": "carrion, decaying flesh, tainted meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "別棟",
      "answer": "べつむね,べっとう",
      "meaning": "separate building, outbuilding, outhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "青み",
      "answer": "あおみ",
      "meaning": "blueness, greenness, tinge of blue, tinge of green, (vegetable) garnish"
    },
    {
      "question": "特産",
      "answer": "とくさん",
      "meaning": "being produced in a particular region, local specialty"
    },
    {
      "question": "捧ぐ",
      "answer": "ささぐ",
      "meaning": "to lift up, to hold up, to hold above eye level, to give, to offer, to consecrate, to devote, to sac"
    },
    {
      "question": "時季",
      "answer": "じき",
      "meaning": "season, time of year"
    },
    {
      "question": "多幸感",
      "answer": "たこうかん",
      "meaning": "euphoria, eudemonia, euphoric"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰投",
      "answer": "きとう",
      "meaning": "return to base (of soldiers, military aircraft or ships)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追憶",
      "answer": "ついおく",
      "meaning": "recollection, reminiscence"
    },
    {
      "question": "尿意",
      "answer": "にょうい",
      "meaning": "urge to urinate"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由度",
      "answer": "じゆうど",
      "meaning": "degree of freedom"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴れん坊",
      "answer": "あばれんぼう",
      "meaning": "rambunctious kid, wild kid, hooligan, rowdy, roughneck, a rough"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉行",
      "answer": "ぶぎょう",
      "meaning": "magistrate, shogunate administrator"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾劾",
      "answer": "だんがい",
      "meaning": "impeachment, denunciation, accusation, censure, arraignment"
    },
    {
      "question": "年少",
      "answer": "ねんしょう",
      "meaning": "young, juvenile"
    },
    {
      "question": "替え玉",
      "answer": "かえだま",
      "meaning": "proxy, ringer, substitute, double, second serving of noodles (to add to previously purchased ramen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "食中毒",
      "answer": "しょくちゅうどく",
      "meaning": "food poisoning"
    },
    {
      "question": "力作",
      "answer": "りきさく,りょくさく",
      "meaning": "painstaking piece of work, work of great effort, tour de force, outstanding work, toil, labor, labou"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い値",
      "answer": "いいね",
      "meaning": "asking price"
    },
    {
      "question": "相貌",
      "answer": "そうぼう",
      "meaning": "looks, features"
    },
    {
      "question": "野次",
      "answer": "やじ",
      "meaning": "hooting, jeering, heckling"
    },
    {
      "question": "不合理",
      "answer": "ふごうり",
      "meaning": "irrational, illogical, unreasonable, absurd, inconsistent"
    },
    {
      "question": "見す",
      "answer": "めす",
      "meaning": "to see, to look, to watch, to rule, to govern"
    },
    {
      "question": "利害関係",
      "answer": "りがいかんけい",
      "meaning": "interests, stake"
    },
    {
      "question": "換え",
      "answer": "かえ,がえ",
      "meaning": "change, alteration, substitute, spare, replacement, proxy, rate of exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖人君子",
      "answer": "せいじんくんし",
      "meaning": "person of lofty virtue, man of noble character, perfect person, saint"
    },
    {
      "question": "息の根",
      "answer": "いきのね",
      "meaning": "life"
    },
    {
      "question": "深奥",
      "answer": "しんおう",
      "meaning": "esoteric doctrines, mysteries"
    },
    {
      "question": "チャラ男",
      "answer": "チャラお",
      "meaning": "shallow playboy, frivolous lad, good-time Charlie"
    },
    {
      "question": "他殺",
      "answer": "たさつ",
      "meaning": "murder"
    },
    {
      "question": "三十日",
      "answer": "さんじゅうにち,みそか",
      "meaning": "thirtieth day of the month, thirty days, last day of the month"
    },
    {
      "question": "礫",
      "answer": "こいし,つぶて",
      "meaning": "pebble, stone (used for throwing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "比べ物",
      "answer": "くらべもの",
      "meaning": "something worthy of comparison, something being compared"
    },
    {
      "question": "築",
      "answer": "ちく",
      "meaning": "... years since construction, ... years old (of a building), built in ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "南無",
      "answer": "なむ",
      "meaning": "amen, hail"
    },
    {
      "question": "手拍子",
      "answer": "てびょうし",
      "meaning": "beating time with one's hands, clapping to the beat, making a careless move (in go, shogi, etc.), re"
    },
    {
      "question": "供する",
      "answer": "きょうする",
      "meaning": "to offer, to present, to submit, to supply, to serve (food and drink), to offer (to the gods), to se"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑居ビル",
      "answer": "ざっきょビル",
      "meaning": "multi-tenant building, building containing a mixture of businesses, shops and residential apartments"
    },
    {
      "question": "町内会",
      "answer": "ちょうないかい",
      "meaning": "neighborhood association, neighbourhood association"
    },
    {
      "question": "彫り込む",
      "answer": "ほりこむ",
      "meaning": "to carve into, to cut into, to engrave into, to inscribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神論",
      "answer": "せいしんろん",
      "meaning": "spiritualism, idealism"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い繕う",
      "answer": "いいつくろう",
      "meaning": "to explain away (a mistake, failure, etc.), to make excuses for, to gloss over, to talk one's way ou"
    },
    {
      "question": "海流",
      "answer": "かいりゅう",
      "meaning": "ocean current"
    },
    {
      "question": "金融",
      "answer": "きんゆう",
      "meaning": "finance, financing, credit transacting, loaning of money, circulation of money, monetary, financial,"
    },
    {
      "question": "定",
      "answer": "さだ,じょう",
      "meaning": "certainly, truly, certainty, reality, actuality, regular, permanent, samadhi (state of intense conce"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟らかい",
      "answer": "やわらかい",
      "meaning": "soft, tender, pliant, supple, limber, limp, gentle, mild, mellow, informal, light, flexible (e.g. th"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け合い",
      "answer": "かけあい",
      "meaning": "negotiations, bargaining, dialogue, duet"
    },
    {
      "question": "電光",
      "answer": "でんこう",
      "meaning": "lightning, electric illumination, light from an electric source"
    },
    {
      "question": "星明かり",
      "answer": "ほしあかり",
      "meaning": "starlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "塵芥",
      "answer": "じんかい,ちりあくた,ごみあくた",
      "meaning": "rubbish, trash, garbage, refuse, worthless thing"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼け付く",
      "answer": "やけつく",
      "meaning": "to burn"
    },
    {
      "question": "絢爛",
      "answer": "けんらん",
      "meaning": "gorgeous, brilliant, dazzling, ornate, gaudy, flowery"
    },
    {
      "question": "忘れ形見",
      "answer": "わすれがたみ",
      "meaning": "memento (from a dead person), souvenir, keepsake, orphan, posthumous child"
    },
    {
      "question": "眺め回す",
      "answer": "ながめまわす",
      "meaning": "to look around, to take a view of"
    },
    {
      "question": "立食",
      "answer": "りっしょく",
      "meaning": "stand-up meal, buffet"
    },
    {
      "question": "若旦那",
      "answer": "わかだんな",
      "meaning": "young master, young gentleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "操り",
      "answer": "あやつり",
      "meaning": "manipulation, puppet"
    },
    {
      "question": "色付く",
      "answer": "いろづく",
      "meaning": "to change color (esp. leaves, fruit, flowers) (colour), to turn crimson (e.g. leaves in autumn), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "石頭",
      "answer": "いしあたま",
      "meaning": "obstinate person, stubbornness, pigheadedness, hard head (like a rock)"
    },
    {
      "question": "木綿",
      "answer": "もめん,きわた,ゆう",
      "meaning": "cotton (material), red silk-cotton tree (Bombax ceiba), string made of cut steamed, soaked mulberry"
    },
    {
      "question": "天女",
      "answer": "てんにょ",
      "meaning": "heavenly nymph, celestial maiden, beautiful and kind woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "癌",
      "answer": "がん",
      "meaning": "cancer"
    },
    {
      "question": "磯",
      "answer": "いそ",
      "meaning": "(rocky) beach, seashore"
    },
    {
      "question": "消防車",
      "answer": "しょうぼうしゃ",
      "meaning": "fire engine, fire truck"
    },
    {
      "question": "人的",
      "answer": "じんてき",
      "meaning": "human, personal"
    },
    {
      "question": "代用品",
      "answer": "だいようひん",
      "meaning": "substitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "音頭",
      "answer": "おんど",
      "meaning": "lead (in a cheer, toast, song, etc.), (someone's) lead, folk song and dance performed by a group, le"
    },
    {
      "question": "模擬店",
      "answer": "もぎてん",
      "meaning": "refreshment booth, refreshment stand, snack bar"
    },
    {
      "question": "武功",
      "answer": "ぶこう",
      "meaning": "military exploits"
    },
    {
      "question": "国際問題",
      "answer": "こくさいもんだい",
      "meaning": "international problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "体罰",
      "answer": "たいばつ",
      "meaning": "corporal punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "供え物",
      "answer": "そなえもの",
      "meaning": "offering (e.g. to the gods), votive offering"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴国",
      "answer": "きこく",
      "meaning": "your country"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒する",
      "answer": "どくする",
      "meaning": "to be a bad influence (on something), to corrupt, to poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "活動的",
      "answer": "かつどうてき",
      "meaning": "active, dynamic, energetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "病名",
      "answer": "びょうめい",
      "meaning": "name of a disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "槍使い",
      "answer": "やりつかい",
      "meaning": "spearman"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭事",
      "answer": "さいじ",
      "meaning": "festival, rites, ritual"
    },
    {
      "question": "妖術",
      "answer": "ようじゅつ",
      "meaning": "black magic, black art, witchcraft, sorcery"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽曲",
      "answer": "がっきょく",
      "meaning": "musical composition, tune"
    },
    {
      "question": "柔い",
      "answer": "やわい,やっこい",
      "meaning": "soft, weak"
    },
    {
      "question": "甥っ子",
      "answer": "おいっこ",
      "meaning": "nephew"
    },
    {
      "question": "必然性",
      "answer": "ひつぜんせい",
      "meaning": "necessity, inevitability"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤立無援",
      "answer": "こりつむえん",
      "meaning": "being isolated and helpless, fighting (struggling) alone and unassisted"
    },
    {
      "question": "地中海",
      "answer": "ちちゅうかい",
      "meaning": "Mediterranean Sea, Mediterranean sea (oceanography)"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄味",
      "answer": "うすあじ",
      "meaning": "light seasoning, mild flavour, bland taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "褪せる",
      "answer": "あせる",
      "meaning": "to fade, to discolor, to discolour, to diminish, to fade (e.g. of a memory)"
    },
    {
      "question": "染み入る",
      "answer": "しみいる",
      "meaning": "to soak into, to permeate"
    },
    {
      "question": "品切れ",
      "answer": "しなぎれ",
      "meaning": "out of stock, sold out"
    },
    {
      "question": "流し台",
      "answer": "ながしだい",
      "meaning": "sink, washstand"
    },
    {
      "question": "摺る",
      "answer": "する",
      "meaning": "to print, to color or pattern fabric using a wooden mold"
    },
    {
      "question": "只中",
      "answer": "ただなか",
      "meaning": "middle"
    },
    {
      "question": "武装解除",
      "answer": "ぶそうかいじょ",
      "meaning": "disarmament"
    },
    {
      "question": "有り金",
      "answer": "ありがね",
      "meaning": "money on hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃いめ",
      "answer": "こいめ",
      "meaning": "strongish, somewhat strong"
    },
    {
      "question": "空欄",
      "answer": "くうらん",
      "meaning": "blank column, blank space"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄人",
      "answer": "てつじん",
      "meaning": "iron man, strong man"
    },
    {
      "question": "精錬",
      "answer": "せいれん",
      "meaning": "refining, refinement, smelting, training"
    },
    {
      "question": "太子",
      "answer": "たいし",
      "meaning": "crown prince, Prince Shōtoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "冒険家",
      "answer": "ぼうけんか",
      "meaning": "adventurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿毛",
      "answer": "わたげ,めんもう",
      "meaning": "down, fuzz, fluff"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻梁",
      "answer": "びりょう",
      "meaning": "bridge of the nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "収支",
      "answer": "しゅうし",
      "meaning": "income and expenditure"
    },
    {
      "question": "出揃う",
      "answer": "でそろう",
      "meaning": "to appear all together, to be all present"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛸",
      "answer": "たこ",
      "meaning": "octopus"
    },
    {
      "question": "布袋",
      "answer": "ぬのぶくろ,ふたい,ほてい",
      "meaning": "cloth bag, Hotei, Budai, god of contentment, depicted as a pot-bellied monk who carries a large clot"
    },
    {
      "question": "目潰し",
      "answer": "めつぶし",
      "meaning": "sand, ash, etc., thrown in the eyes to blind someone, throwing something at someone's eyes to blind"
    },
    {
      "question": "世に出る",
      "answer": "よにでる",
      "meaning": "to become famous, to go out into the world, to make one's way in the world, to appear, to be publish"
    },
    {
      "question": "火矢",
      "answer": "ひや",
      "meaning": "fire arrow, incendiary arrow, rocket"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄宿舎",
      "answer": "きしゅくしゃ",
      "meaning": "boarding house, school dormitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "撲滅",
      "answer": "ぼくめつ",
      "meaning": "eradication, extermination, destruction, suppression"
    },
    {
      "question": "主題歌",
      "answer": "しゅだいか",
      "meaning": "theme song"
    },
    {
      "question": "速報",
      "answer": "そくほう",
      "meaning": "news flash, prompt report, bulletin, quick announcement"
    },
    {
      "question": "死臭",
      "answer": "ししゅう",
      "meaning": "putrid smell of a corpse"
    },
    {
      "question": "七分",
      "answer": "しちぶん",
      "meaning": "type of baggy tobi trousers with the baggy part taking up seven-tenths of the full length of the tro"
    },
    {
      "question": "不文律",
      "answer": "ふぶんりつ",
      "meaning": "unwritten law, common law, unwritten rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "這い寄る",
      "answer": "はいよる",
      "meaning": "to crawl towards, to creep up to"
    },
    {
      "question": "四神",
      "answer": "しじん",
      "meaning": "four Taoist gods said to reign over the four directions, four gods said to reign over the four seaso"
    },
    {
      "question": "捜査本部",
      "answer": "そうさほんぶ",
      "meaning": "(criminal) investigation headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "堅気",
      "answer": "かたぎ",
      "meaning": "honest, respectable, respectable occupation (i.e. not yakuza, prostitute, etc.), person in a respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "国庫",
      "answer": "こっこ",
      "meaning": "national treasury"
    },
    {
      "question": "百発百中",
      "answer": "ひゃっぱつひゃくちゅう",
      "meaning": "always hitting the bull's-eye, infallible"
    },
    {
      "question": "岸辺",
      "answer": "きしべ",
      "meaning": "shore, bank (of a body of water)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然災害",
      "answer": "しぜんさいがい",
      "meaning": "natural disaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "私財",
      "answer": "しざい",
      "meaning": "private funds, own funds, private property"
    },
    {
      "question": "若",
      "answer": "わか,もころ",
      "meaning": "youth, child (esp. of the young son of someone of high social standing), young, new, like, similar t"
    },
    {
      "question": "啖呵",
      "answer": "たんか",
      "meaning": "caustic words"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰痛",
      "answer": "ようつう",
      "meaning": "lower back (or hip) pain, lumbago"
    },
    {
      "question": "手櫛",
      "answer": "てぐし",
      "meaning": "using one's fingers as a comb, combing one's hand through one's hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱情",
      "answer": "ねつじょう",
      "meaning": "ardour (ardor), passion"
    },
    {
      "question": "転向",
      "answer": "てんこう",
      "meaning": "conversion, shift, about-face, switch"
    },
    {
      "question": "今晩は",
      "answer": "こんばんは",
      "meaning": "good evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "安住",
      "answer": "あんじゅう",
      "meaning": "living in peace, living a quiet life, being content with one's present position, being satisfied wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "大天使",
      "answer": "だいてんし",
      "meaning": "archangel"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り付け",
      "answer": "ふりつけ",
      "meaning": "choreography, dance composition, dance coaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "臣民",
      "answer": "しんみん",
      "meaning": "subject, national"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け皿",
      "answer": "うけざら",
      "meaning": "saucer, person (group, institution, etc.) to take over a position or matter, receptacle (e.g. of fun"
    },
    {
      "question": "別れ話",
      "answer": "わかればなし",
      "meaning": "talk about divorce or separation"
    },
    {
      "question": "後釜",
      "answer": "あとがま",
      "meaning": "successor, replacement, second wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "先ず",
      "answer": "まず",
      "meaning": "first (of all), firstly, to begin with, before anything else, probably, most likely, almost certainl"
    },
    {
      "question": "親子丼",
      "answer": "おやこどん,おやこどんぶり",
      "meaning": "oyakodon, chicken and egg on rice, threesome including a mother and her daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "即応",
      "answer": "そくおう",
      "meaning": "compliance, conformance, adaptation, (immediate) response, (rapid) reaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "高等学校",
      "answer": "こうとうがっこう",
      "meaning": "senior high school, high school"
    },
    {
      "question": "自陣",
      "answer": "じじん",
      "meaning": "one's own ground, one's own position, one's own area of the field (soccer, rugby, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "懐刀",
      "answer": "ふところがたな",
      "meaning": "dagger, stiletto, confidant, right-hand man"
    },
    {
      "question": "血糊",
      "answer": "ちのり",
      "meaning": "clotted blood, gore, sticky clots of blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "老獪",
      "answer": "ろうかい",
      "meaning": "cunning, crafty, wily, sly"
    },
    {
      "question": "階上",
      "answer": "かいじょう",
      "meaning": "upper floor, upstairs, top of the stairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "八分",
      "answer": "はっぷん,はちぶ",
      "meaning": "eight minutes, triangular-swept clerical script (clerical script whose horizontal lines end in a not"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ二つ",
      "answer": "まっぷたつ",
      "meaning": "in two equal parts"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き",
      "answer": "たたき,はたき",
      "meaning": "finely chopped fish or meat (sometimes seared first), mince, hitting (e.g. a drum), striking, beatin"
    },
    {
      "question": "羊毛",
      "answer": "ようもう",
      "meaning": "wool"
    },
    {
      "question": "手拭い",
      "answer": "てぬぐい",
      "meaning": "(hand) towel"
    },
    {
      "question": "間諜",
      "answer": "かんちょう",
      "meaning": "spy, secret agent"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅白",
      "answer": "こうはく",
      "meaning": "red and white, colours for festive or auspicious occasions (colors), two teams, two groups, Red and"
    },
    {
      "question": "初っ端",
      "answer": "しょっぱな",
      "meaning": "(very) beginning, start"
    },
    {
      "question": "女遊び",
      "answer": "おんなあそび",
      "meaning": "chasing after women, womanizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋を通す",
      "answer": "すじをとおす",
      "meaning": "to proceed in a logical manner, to go through the proper channels"
    },
    {
      "question": "下顎",
      "answer": "したあご,かがく",
      "meaning": "lower jaw, mandible"
    },
    {
      "question": "上海",
      "answer": "シャンハイ",
      "meaning": "Shanghai (China)"
    },
    {
      "question": "研磨",
      "answer": "けんま",
      "meaning": "grinding, polishing, refining (skill, knowledge, etc.), striving to master something"
    },
    {
      "question": "成否",
      "answer": "せいひ",
      "meaning": "success or failure, outcome, result"
    },
    {
      "question": "居合",
      "answer": "いあい",
      "meaning": "iai, art of drawing one's sword, cutting down one's opponent and sheathing the sword afterwards"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り勘",
      "answer": "わりかん",
      "meaning": "splitting the cost, Dutch treat"
    },
    {
      "question": "一辺",
      "answer": "いっぺん",
      "meaning": "side of a geometric shape (e.g. triangle or rectangle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "散弾銃",
      "answer": "さんだんじゅう",
      "meaning": "shotgun"
    },
    {
      "question": "善い",
      "answer": "よい,えい",
      "meaning": "good, excellent, fine, nice, pleasant, agreeable, sufficient, enough, ready, prepared, profitable (d"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝辞",
      "answer": "しゅくじ",
      "meaning": "congratulatory address"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒草",
      "answer": "どくそう",
      "meaning": "poisonous plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "中段",
      "answer": "ちゅうだん",
      "meaning": "half-way up a slope or stairway, landing, center of three (horizontal) columns (of print) (centre)"
    },
    {
      "question": "顕れる",
      "answer": "あらわれる",
      "meaning": "to appear, to come in sight, to become visible, to come out, to embody, to materialize, to materiali"
    },
    {
      "question": "町人",
      "answer": "ちょうにん,まちにん",
      "meaning": "chōnin (Edo-period social class of town-dwelling commoners, esp. landowning merchants), townspeople,"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り換え",
      "answer": "のりかえ",
      "meaning": "transfer (trains, buses, etc.), change, connection, switch (to another ideology, party, system, meth"
    },
    {
      "question": "物乞い",
      "answer": "ものごい",
      "meaning": "beggar, begging"
    },
    {
      "question": "同型",
      "answer": "どうけい",
      "meaning": "isomorphism, same shape, same type, same pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣立つ",
      "answer": "すだつ",
      "meaning": "to leave the nest, to go out into the world, to become independent (of one's parents), to graduate ("
    },
    {
      "question": "飛車",
      "answer": "ひしゃ",
      "meaning": "rook, hisha"
    },
    {
      "question": "悦",
      "answer": "えつ",
      "meaning": "self-satisfaction, rejoicing"
    },
    {
      "question": "船着き場",
      "answer": "ふなつきば",
      "meaning": "harbour, harbor, landing place, wharf, anchorage"
    },
    {
      "question": "納期",
      "answer": "のうき",
      "meaning": "appointed day of delivery, time for payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "傑物",
      "answer": "けつぶつ",
      "meaning": "great man, heroic figure, remarkable character"
    },
    {
      "question": "他力本願",
      "answer": "たりきほんがん",
      "meaning": "salvation by faith in Amitabha, relying on others, depending on others"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘受",
      "answer": "かんじゅ",
      "meaning": "submitting to (a demand, one's fate, etc.), putting up with, resigning oneself to, accepting (withou"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵員",
      "answer": "へいいん",
      "meaning": "military strength, military personnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝覚め",
      "answer": "ねざめ",
      "meaning": "awaken"
    },
    {
      "question": "神族",
      "answer": "しんぞく",
      "meaning": "family of gods, clan of gods, tribe of gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "料理屋",
      "answer": "りょうりや",
      "meaning": "restaurant"
    },
    {
      "question": "拾",
      "answer": "じゅう",
      "meaning": "ten"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉微塵",
      "answer": "こなみじん,こみじん",
      "meaning": "in very small pieces"
    },
    {
      "question": "平伏",
      "answer": "へいふく",
      "meaning": "falling prostrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "神髄",
      "answer": "しんずい",
      "meaning": "essence, quintessence, spirit, soul, heart, pith, pith and marrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "高学年",
      "answer": "こうがくねん",
      "meaning": "upper grades of primary school (sixth, fifth, and sometimes fourth grades)"
    },
    {
      "question": "放射線",
      "answer": "ほうしゃせん",
      "meaning": "radiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟女",
      "answer": "じゅくじょ",
      "meaning": "(sexually) attractive older woman, mature woman, MILF"
    },
    {
      "question": "低空飛行",
      "answer": "ていくうひこう",
      "meaning": "low-altitude flying"
    },
    {
      "question": "画材",
      "answer": "がざい",
      "meaning": "subject matter of a painting, art supplies, art materials"
    },
    {
      "question": "長子",
      "answer": "ちょうし,えこ",
      "meaning": "eldest child, oldest child, first child, eldest son, oldest son"
    },
    {
      "question": "共同戦線",
      "answer": "きょうどうせんせん",
      "meaning": "common front, united front"
    },
    {
      "question": "果肉",
      "answer": "かにく",
      "meaning": "flesh of fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "同数",
      "answer": "どうすう",
      "meaning": "same number"
    },
    {
      "question": "主語",
      "answer": "しゅご",
      "meaning": "subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "囲碁",
      "answer": "いご",
      "meaning": "go, board game of capturing territory"
    },
    {
      "question": "陵",
      "answer": "みささぎ,みはか,りょう",
      "meaning": "imperial mausoleum, Emperor's tomb, big hill"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦慄く",
      "answer": "わななく",
      "meaning": "to tremble, to shiver, to shake"
    },
    {
      "question": "休校",
      "answer": "きゅうこう",
      "meaning": "(temporary) closure of school"
    },
    {
      "question": "真ん前",
      "answer": "まんまえ",
      "meaning": "right in front, just opposite, under the nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "大志",
      "answer": "たいし",
      "meaning": "ambition, aspiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "再編成",
      "answer": "さいへんせい",
      "meaning": "reorganization, reorganisation, reshuffle"
    },
    {
      "question": "偲ぶ",
      "answer": "しのぶ",
      "meaning": "to recollect, to remember, to reminisce, to be nostalgic for, to imagine, to guess, to infer"
    },
    {
      "question": "大敗",
      "answer": "たいはい",
      "meaning": "crushing defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼け野原",
      "answer": "やけのはら",
      "meaning": "burnt field, burnt area"
    },
    {
      "question": "室温",
      "answer": "しつおん",
      "meaning": "room temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "入り用",
      "answer": "いりよう",
      "meaning": "need, want, necessity, costs, expenses"
    },
    {
      "question": "新記録",
      "answer": "しんきろく",
      "meaning": "new record (in sports, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "以てする",
      "answer": "もってする",
      "meaning": "to do by the use of"
    },
    {
      "question": "臥せる",
      "answer": "ふせる",
      "meaning": "to lie down, to retire, to go to bed (with an illness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "長丁場",
      "answer": "ながちょうば",
      "meaning": "long stretch, long haul, marathon, time-consuming work, long scene (in a play), long act"
    },
    {
      "question": "曹長",
      "answer": "そうちょう",
      "meaning": "master sergeant, sergeant major (JSDF)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤字",
      "answer": "ごじ",
      "meaning": "misprint, misspelling, typo, typographical error, erratum"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆説的",
      "answer": "ぎゃくせつてき",
      "meaning": "paradoxical"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦列",
      "answer": "せんれつ",
      "meaning": "line of battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "支点",
      "answer": "してん",
      "meaning": "fulcrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "風見",
      "answer": "かざみ",
      "meaning": "weather vane"
    },
    {
      "question": "尾張",
      "answer": "おわり",
      "meaning": "Owari (former province located in the west of present-day Aichi Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "草食",
      "answer": "そうしょく",
      "meaning": "herbivorous, plant-eating, graminivorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚気る",
      "answer": "のろける",
      "meaning": "to go on about (one's love affairs), to speak proudly of (one's spouse, girlfriend, etc.), to speak"
    },
    {
      "question": "転売",
      "answer": "てんばい",
      "meaning": "resale"
    },
    {
      "question": "山場",
      "answer": "やまば",
      "meaning": "climax, turning point"
    },
    {
      "question": "小包",
      "answer": "こづつみ",
      "meaning": "parcel, package"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠犬",
      "answer": "ちゅうけん",
      "meaning": "faithful dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "後生",
      "answer": "こうせい,ごしょう",
      "meaning": "younger people, future generations, afterlife"
    },
    {
      "question": "角が立つ",
      "answer": "かどがたつ,つのがたつ",
      "meaning": "to cause offense"
    },
    {
      "question": "後夜祭",
      "answer": "こうやさい",
      "meaning": "closing party, closing event of a school, etc. festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "一所懸命",
      "answer": "いっしょけんめい",
      "meaning": "very hard, with utmost effort, with all one's might, desperately, frantically, for dear life, all-ou"
    },
    {
      "question": "運動量",
      "answer": "うんどうりょう",
      "meaning": "momentum, amount of exercise"
    },
    {
      "question": "救命",
      "answer": "きゅうめい",
      "meaning": "lifesaving"
    },
    {
      "question": "商社",
      "answer": "しょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "trading company"
    },
    {
      "question": "人界",
      "answer": "にんがい,じんかい",
      "meaning": "spiritual realm of humanity, world of man"
    },
    {
      "question": "眷族",
      "answer": "けんぞく",
      "meaning": "(one's) family, dependents, household, follower, retainer, underling"
    },
    {
      "question": "掘削",
      "answer": "くっさく",
      "meaning": "digging out, excavation"
    },
    {
      "question": "内職",
      "answer": "ないしょく",
      "meaning": "side job (outside of one's main employment), side gig, side hustle, part job (carried out at home),"
    },
    {
      "question": "三下",
      "answer": "さんした",
      "meaning": "petty underling, small fry"
    },
    {
      "question": "工芸品",
      "answer": "こうげいひん",
      "meaning": "handicraft, industrial art object"
    },
    {
      "question": "力業",
      "answer": "ちからわざ",
      "meaning": "heavy work, manual labour, feat of strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "癒る",
      "answer": "いる",
      "meaning": "to calm down"
    },
    {
      "question": "上り坂",
      "answer": "のぼりざか",
      "meaning": "ascent, uphill, upward slope, (gradual) upturn, increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "追伸",
      "answer": "ついしん",
      "meaning": "postscript, post scriptum, PS, P.S."
    },
    {
      "question": "燐",
      "answer": "りん",
      "meaning": "phosphorus (P)"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦犯",
      "answer": "せんぱん",
      "meaning": "war criminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬣",
      "answer": "たてがみ",
      "meaning": "mane (of a horse, lion, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "買出し",
      "answer": "かいだし",
      "meaning": "going out to shop, going shopping, buying in quantity, buying wholesale, bulk purchasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "学び",
      "answer": "まなび",
      "meaning": "learning, study"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍味",
      "answer": "ちんみ",
      "meaning": "delicacy, dainties"
    },
    {
      "question": "覇道",
      "answer": "はどう",
      "meaning": "military rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩水",
      "answer": "しおみず,えんすい",
      "meaning": "salt water, brine"
    },
    {
      "question": "人込み",
      "answer": "ひとごみ",
      "meaning": "crowd of people"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚考",
      "answer": "ぐこう",
      "meaning": "foolish thought, (one's own) thought, (one's own) idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "急ピッチ",
      "answer": "きゅうピッチ",
      "meaning": "quick pace"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾国",
      "answer": "けいこく",
      "meaning": "beauty, siren, courtesan, prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "俯ける",
      "answer": "うつむける",
      "meaning": "to turn upside down, to turn (face) downward"
    },
    {
      "question": "開設",
      "answer": "かいせつ",
      "meaning": "establishment, opening, setting up, inauguration"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱腰",
      "answer": "よわごし",
      "meaning": "weak attitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡桃",
      "answer": "くるみ",
      "meaning": "walnut (Juglans spp., esp. Juglans regia)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手品師",
      "answer": "てじなし",
      "meaning": "magician, conjurer, illusionist"
    },
    {
      "question": "忸怩",
      "answer": "じくじ",
      "meaning": "bashful, shameful, ashamed"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い違い",
      "answer": "くいちがい",
      "meaning": "discrepancy, different or conflicting opinions"
    },
    {
      "question": "綱引き",
      "answer": "つなひき",
      "meaning": "tug of war (orig. a form of divination to predict whether the year will be favourable or unfavourabl"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹林",
      "answer": "ちくりん,たけばやし",
      "meaning": "bamboo thicket, bamboo grove"
    },
    {
      "question": "小市民",
      "answer": "しょうしみん",
      "meaning": "petty bourgeois, lower middle class"
    },
    {
      "question": "在りし日",
      "answer": "ありしひ",
      "meaning": "past days, bygone days, days of yore, the olden days, while still alive, during one's lifetime"
    },
    {
      "question": "独創的",
      "answer": "どくそうてき",
      "meaning": "creative, original"
    },
    {
      "question": "託宣",
      "answer": "たくせん",
      "meaning": "oracle"
    },
    {
      "question": "果樹園",
      "answer": "かじゅえん",
      "meaning": "orchard, fruit farm"
    },
    {
      "question": "成形",
      "answer": "せいけい",
      "meaning": "cast, mold, mould, casting, molding, moulding, compacting (e.g. in metallurgy), forming, shaping, fa"
    },
    {
      "question": "来年度",
      "answer": "らいねんど",
      "meaning": "next year, next fiscal year"
    },
    {
      "question": "支出",
      "answer": "ししゅつ",
      "meaning": "expenditure, disbursement, expenses"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫を被る",
      "answer": "ねこをかぶる",
      "meaning": "to feign friendliness, to play the hypocrite"
    },
    {
      "question": "代案",
      "answer": "だいあん",
      "meaning": "alternate plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "積荷",
      "answer": "つみに",
      "meaning": "load, freight, cargo"
    },
    {
      "question": "産み",
      "answer": "うみ",
      "meaning": "production, bringing into the world, (physical) birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "前列",
      "answer": "ぜんれつ",
      "meaning": "front row"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾",
      "answer": "ほし,けん,いぬい",
      "meaning": "drying, dried, qian (one of the trigrams of the I Ching: heaven, northwest), northwest"
    },
    {
      "question": "大上段",
      "answer": "だいじょうだん",
      "meaning": "holding a sword above one's head (kendo posture), haughty attitude, overbearing manner"
    },
    {
      "question": "道行き",
      "answer": "みちゆき",
      "meaning": "going down the road, travelling, traveling, lyric composition describing scenery a traveler sees on"
    },
    {
      "question": "再来年",
      "answer": "さらいねん",
      "meaning": "year after next"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒革",
      "answer": "くろかわ",
      "meaning": "black-dyed leather, leather dyed in deep indigo, edible mushroom in the Thelephoraceae family"
    },
    {
      "question": "水素",
      "answer": "すいそ",
      "meaning": "hydrogen (H)"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄目押し",
      "answer": "だめおし",
      "meaning": "making doubly sure, insurance run (baseball), points scored for good measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕舞い",
      "answer": "しまい,じまい",
      "meaning": "end, close, finish, termination, ending, quitting, closing, ending before one had time to do somethi"
    },
    {
      "question": "古巣",
      "answer": "ふるす",
      "meaning": "old haunts, former homes"
    },
    {
      "question": "飾り気",
      "answer": "かざりけ",
      "meaning": "affectation, showing off"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋸",
      "answer": "のこぎり",
      "meaning": "saw, musical saw"
    },
    {
      "question": "天の川",
      "answer": "あまのがわ,あまのかわ",
      "meaning": "Milky Way, luminous band corresponding to the plane of the galaxy"
    },
    {
      "question": "神の使い",
      "answer": "かみのつかい",
      "meaning": "divine messenger, messenger of a god (esp. an animal messenger)"
    },
    {
      "question": "都度",
      "answer": "つど",
      "meaning": "each (every) time, whenever"
    },
    {
      "question": "二の句",
      "answer": "にのく",
      "meaning": "next (spoken) word"
    },
    {
      "question": "金策",
      "answer": "きんさく",
      "meaning": "(means of) raising money"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び越す",
      "answer": "とびこす",
      "meaning": "to leap over"
    },
    {
      "question": "原価",
      "answer": "げんか",
      "meaning": "cost price"
    },
    {
      "question": "席巻",
      "answer": "せっけん",
      "meaning": "sweeping conquest, sweeping over, conquering, invading"
    },
    {
      "question": "窮状",
      "answer": "きゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "distress, wretched condition"
    },
    {
      "question": "面妖",
      "answer": "めんよう",
      "meaning": "weird, strange, mysterious"
    },
    {
      "question": "小芝居",
      "answer": "こしばい",
      "meaning": "small theatre, kabuki performed in a small theatre, little performance, short acted scene, act, rout"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧政",
      "answer": "あっせい",
      "meaning": "oppressive rule, tyrannical regime, despotism"
    },
    {
      "question": "考え付く",
      "answer": "かんがえつく",
      "meaning": "to think of, to come up with"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い置き",
      "answer": "かいおき",
      "meaning": "stock (of goods), reserve, supply"
    },
    {
      "question": "麻雀",
      "answer": "マージャン",
      "meaning": "mahjong, mah-jongg"
    },
    {
      "question": "戴冠式",
      "answer": "たいかんしき",
      "meaning": "coronation ceremony, enthronement"
    },
    {
      "question": "大学病院",
      "answer": "だいがくびょういん",
      "meaning": "university hospital, teaching hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "随行",
      "answer": "ずいこう",
      "meaning": "attendant, follower"
    },
    {
      "question": "融和",
      "answer": "ゆうわ",
      "meaning": "harmony, reconciliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "越後",
      "answer": "えちご",
      "meaning": "Echigo (former province located in present-day Niigata Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽す",
      "answer": "つくす",
      "meaning": "to exhaust, to run out, to devote, to serve (a person), to befriend, to do to exhaustion"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏壇",
      "answer": "ぶつだん",
      "meaning": "Buddhist (household) altar"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜在",
      "answer": "せんざい",
      "meaning": "potentiality, dormancy, latency"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯牙",
      "answer": "しが",
      "meaning": "teeth (and tusks)"
    },
    {
      "question": "悠々自適",
      "answer": "ゆうゆうじてき",
      "meaning": "living a life of leisure with dignity, living quietly and comfortably free from worldly cares, otium"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊賀",
      "answer": "いが",
      "meaning": "Iga (former province located in the west of present-day Mie Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒風",
      "answer": "かんぷう",
      "meaning": "cold wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "気立て",
      "answer": "きだて",
      "meaning": "disposition, nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "列強",
      "answer": "れっきょう",
      "meaning": "major powers of the world, great powers"
    },
    {
      "question": "反駁",
      "answer": "はんばく,はんぱく",
      "meaning": "refutation, rebuttal, retort"
    },
    {
      "question": "原色",
      "answer": "げんしょく",
      "meaning": "primary colour, primary color, pure color, unmixed color, striking color, original color (of a paint"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧姓",
      "answer": "きゅうせい",
      "meaning": "one's original family name, maiden name"
    },
    {
      "question": "文法",
      "answer": "ぶんぽう",
      "meaning": "grammar"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸裸",
      "answer": "まるはだか",
      "meaning": "being stark-naked, having no possessions, losing all one's belongings"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛し子",
      "answer": "いとしご",
      "meaning": "beloved child, dear child"
    },
    {
      "question": "勤め先",
      "answer": "つとめさき",
      "meaning": "place of work"
    },
    {
      "question": "問題外",
      "answer": "もんだいがい",
      "meaning": "unthinkable, out of the question"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳",
      "answer": "げん",
      "meaning": "strict, stern"
    },
    {
      "question": "門下生",
      "answer": "もんかせい",
      "meaning": "pupil, disciple, follower"
    },
    {
      "question": "八重歯",
      "answer": "やえば",
      "meaning": "double tooth, protruding tooth (like a fang), high canine"
    },
    {
      "question": "一等地",
      "answer": "いっとうち",
      "meaning": "prime location (for offices, housing, etc.), best district (in town), excellent piece of land"
    },
    {
      "question": "共和",
      "answer": "きょうわ",
      "meaning": "republican, cooperative"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ",
      "answer": "ひっ",
      "meaning": "goes before a verb to strengthen its meaning or to add emphasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "不恰好",
      "answer": "ぶかっこう,ふかっこう",
      "meaning": "unshapely, ill-formed, misshapen, awkward, clumsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "文字盤",
      "answer": "もじばん",
      "meaning": "dial (on timepiece, meter, etc.), letter board (e.g. on typewriter, writing aide for the disabled, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "上位互換",
      "answer": "じょういごかん",
      "meaning": "downward compatible, backward compatible, compatible with input or components intended for lower tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "国旗",
      "answer": "こっき",
      "meaning": "national flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "人工呼吸",
      "answer": "じんこうこきゅう",
      "meaning": "artificial respiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "拗れる",
      "answer": "こじれる,ねじれる",
      "meaning": "to get complicated, to grow worse, to turn sour, to get twisted, to get crooked, to get warped, to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "真性",
      "answer": "しんせい",
      "meaning": "inborn nature, genuine, intrinsic, essential"
    },
    {
      "question": "私欲",
      "answer": "しよく",
      "meaning": "self-interest, selfish desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲信",
      "answer": "もうしん",
      "meaning": "blind acceptance, blind belief, credulity"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏期",
      "answer": "かき",
      "meaning": "summer term (e.g. school), summer period"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活指導",
      "answer": "せいかつしどう",
      "meaning": "civic guidance, non-curricular educational guidance, medical guidance"
    },
    {
      "question": "利息",
      "answer": "りそく",
      "meaning": "interest (on a loan, deposit, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯形",
      "answer": "はがた",
      "meaning": "impression of the teeth, tooth mold (mould), tooth mark, teeth marks"
    },
    {
      "question": "確定的",
      "answer": "かくていてき",
      "meaning": "definite"
    },
    {
      "question": "錦",
      "answer": "にしき",
      "meaning": "brocade, fine dress, fine clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "路銀",
      "answer": "ろぎん",
      "meaning": "traveling expenses, travelling expenses"
    },
    {
      "question": "働き口",
      "answer": "はたらきぐち",
      "meaning": "position, job, employment, opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "取っ払う",
      "answer": "とっぱらう",
      "meaning": "to clear away, to remove, to demolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "岳",
      "answer": "たけ,だけ",
      "meaning": "peak, mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "防弾",
      "answer": "ぼうだん",
      "meaning": "bulletproof, bombproof"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪景色",
      "answer": "ゆきげしき",
      "meaning": "snow scene, snowscape, snowy landscape"
    },
    {
      "question": "澱",
      "answer": "よどみ,おり,よど",
      "meaning": "stagnation, deposit, sediment, backwater, faltering, hesitation, pause, dregs, lees, grounds, pool ("
    },
    {
      "question": "先取り",
      "answer": "さきどり",
      "meaning": "receiving in advance, taking before others, prefetch, anticipatory completion, finishing another per"
    },
    {
      "question": "積極性",
      "answer": "せっきょくせい",
      "meaning": "assertiveness, positiveness, initiative, spirit of enterprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "異人",
      "answer": "いじん",
      "meaning": "foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), different person"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍛練",
      "answer": "たんれん",
      "meaning": "tempering (metal), annealing, forging, toughening, disciplining, training"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪華絢爛",
      "answer": "ごうかけんらん",
      "meaning": "luxurious and gorgeous, magnificent"
    },
    {
      "question": "電子書籍",
      "answer": "でんししょせき",
      "meaning": "ebook, e-book, electronic book, digital book"
    },
    {
      "question": "花粉症",
      "answer": "かふんしょう",
      "meaning": "hay fever, pollinosis (allergy to pollen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地下水",
      "answer": "ちかすい",
      "meaning": "underground water"
    },
    {
      "question": "福祉",
      "answer": "ふくし,ふくち",
      "meaning": "welfare, well-being, social welfare, social security, social service"
    },
    {
      "question": "個体差",
      "answer": "こたいさ",
      "meaning": "individual difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "下痢",
      "answer": "げり",
      "meaning": "diarrhea, diarrhoea"
    },
    {
      "question": "触れ込み",
      "answer": "ふれこみ",
      "meaning": "(exaggerated) professing to be, passing oneself off as"
    },
    {
      "question": "世も末",
      "answer": "よもすえ",
      "meaning": "the end of the world, the world is beyond saving, there's no hope for the future, this degenerate ag"
    },
    {
      "question": "客船",
      "answer": "きゃくせん",
      "meaning": "passenger boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸留酒",
      "answer": "じょうりゅうしゅ",
      "meaning": "distilled liquor, spirits"
    },
    {
      "question": "異教徒",
      "answer": "いきょうと",
      "meaning": "pagan, heretic, heathen"
    },
    {
      "question": "徐に",
      "answer": "おもむろに",
      "meaning": "suddenly, abruptly, deliberately, slowly, gently"
    },
    {
      "question": "現像",
      "answer": "げんぞう",
      "meaning": "development (of film), photographic processing"
    },
    {
      "question": "音符",
      "answer": "おんぷ",
      "meaning": "musical note, note symbol, phonetic symbol (incl. the kanji and kana-doubling symbols, vowel-lengthe"
    },
    {
      "question": "体幹",
      "answer": "たいかん",
      "meaning": "trunk (of the body), soma"
    },
    {
      "question": "両手に花",
      "answer": "りょうてにはな",
      "meaning": "two blessings at once, flanked by two beautiful women"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠見",
      "answer": "えんけん,とおみ",
      "meaning": "looking into distance, watchtower, distant view"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉子焼き",
      "answer": "たまごやき",
      "meaning": "rolled egg, rolled omelette (omelet), fried egg, frying pan for making rolled eggs"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚本家",
      "answer": "きゃくほんか",
      "meaning": "scriptwriter, playwright, scenario writer"
    },
    {
      "question": "固有名詞",
      "answer": "こゆうめいし",
      "meaning": "proper noun"
    },
    {
      "question": "予定表",
      "answer": "よていひょう",
      "meaning": "schedule, program, programme, itinerary"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢心地",
      "answer": "ゆめごこち",
      "meaning": "dreamy state of mind, ecstasy, trance"
    },
    {
      "question": "喫煙",
      "answer": "きつえん",
      "meaning": "smoking"
    },
    {
      "question": "先進",
      "answer": "せんしん",
      "meaning": "advanced, developed, seniority, senior, superior, elder"
    },
    {
      "question": "珠玉",
      "answer": "しゅぎょく",
      "meaning": "jewel, gem, gem (of a story, essay, etc.), accomplished work, beautiful piece"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍属",
      "answer": "ぐんぞく",
      "meaning": "civilian in military employ"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝立",
      "answer": "ついたて",
      "meaning": "partitioning screen"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕相撲",
      "answer": "うでずもう",
      "meaning": "arm wrestling, Indian wrestling, wrestling relying on brute strength (of the arms), rather than skil"
    },
    {
      "question": "異常気象",
      "answer": "いじょうきしょう",
      "meaning": "abnormal weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "即行",
      "answer": "そっこう",
      "meaning": "immediately carrying out (a plan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "急造",
      "answer": "きゅうぞう",
      "meaning": "hurried construction, hurried production, hasty manufacture, hasty formation"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰回り",
      "answer": "こしまわり",
      "meaning": "measurement round the hips"
    },
    {
      "question": "口開け",
      "answer": "くちあけ",
      "meaning": "opening (of a bottle), broaching, beginning, opening, commencement (e.g. of sales), first sale"
    },
    {
      "question": "三文",
      "answer": "さんもん",
      "meaning": "paltry amount of money, cheapness, worthlessness, three one-mon coins"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸説",
      "answer": "しょせつ",
      "meaning": "various opinions, various theories, various rumors (rumours)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後見",
      "answer": "こうけん",
      "meaning": "guardianship, guardian, (theatrical) assistant, prompter"
    },
    {
      "question": "二次会",
      "answer": "にじかい",
      "meaning": "after-party, second party (of the night), second meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち越す",
      "answer": "もちこす",
      "meaning": "to carry over, to carry forward, to keep (for later), to defer"
    },
    {
      "question": "有機",
      "answer": "ゆうき",
      "meaning": "organic"
    },
    {
      "question": "変化球",
      "answer": "へんかきゅう",
      "meaning": "breaking ball (pitch), curve ball, screwball"
    },
    {
      "question": "九日",
      "answer": "ここのか,ここぬか",
      "meaning": "ninth day of the month, nine days"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆記",
      "answer": "ひっき",
      "meaning": "(taking) notes, copying"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁場",
      "answer": "じば,じじょう",
      "meaning": "magnetic field, ambience, atmosphere, focal point"
    },
    {
      "question": "音程",
      "answer": "おんてい",
      "meaning": "interval, step, pitch, key"
    },
    {
      "question": "病める",
      "answer": "やめる",
      "meaning": "sick, ill, ailing, to hurt, to ache"
    },
    {
      "question": "名産",
      "answer": "めいさん",
      "meaning": "noted product, local specialty"
    },
    {
      "question": "知事",
      "answer": "ちじ",
      "meaning": "prefectural governor"
    },
    {
      "question": "電報",
      "answer": "でんぽう",
      "meaning": "telegram"
    },
    {
      "question": "澪",
      "answer": "みお",
      "meaning": "waterway, channel, wake (of a ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "妹分",
      "answer": "いもうとぶん",
      "meaning": "protegee, someone who one considers as a younger sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "皆の衆",
      "answer": "みなのしゅう",
      "meaning": "everybody"
    },
    {
      "question": "媚を売る",
      "answer": "こびをうる",
      "meaning": "to coquet (of a woman), to entice a customer (of a prostitute), to flatter, to butter up"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱入り娘",
      "answer": "はこいりむすめ",
      "meaning": "girl who has led a sheltered life, pet daughter, naive girl, ingénue, wooden block puzzle, Daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬術",
      "answer": "ばじゅつ",
      "meaning": "horsemanship, equestrian art, (art of) riding"
    },
    {
      "question": "古文",
      "answer": "こぶん,こもん",
      "meaning": "ancient writing (i.e. Edo-period or older), classical literature, ancient Chinese character (pre-Qin"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪傑",
      "answer": "ごうけつ",
      "meaning": "hero, great man"
    },
    {
      "question": "住職",
      "answer": "じゅうしょく",
      "meaning": "chief priest (of a Buddhist temple)"
    },
    {
      "question": "制動",
      "answer": "せいどう",
      "meaning": "braking (mechanism)"
    },
    {
      "question": "不揃い",
      "answer": "ふぞろい,ふそろい",
      "meaning": "uneven, irregular, non-uniform, unsorted, odd, miscellaneous, incomplete (set)"
    },
    {
      "question": "約束事",
      "answer": "やくそくごと",
      "meaning": "promise, vow, engagement, convention, rule, resolution"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報処理",
      "answer": "じょうほうしょり",
      "meaning": "data processing"
    },
    {
      "question": "件数",
      "answer": "けんすう",
      "meaning": "number of events (e.g. accidents, crimes, meetings, housing starts, hits on a web page)"
    },
    {
      "question": "千変万化",
      "answer": "せんぺんばんか",
      "meaning": "innumerable changes, infinite variety"
    },
    {
      "question": "適す",
      "answer": "てきす",
      "meaning": "to fit, to suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "半面",
      "answer": "はんめん",
      "meaning": "half the face, one side, half, the other side, the reverse, the contrary"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤射",
      "answer": "ごしゃ",
      "meaning": "accidental shooting"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄緑色",
      "answer": "おうりょくしょく",
      "meaning": "yellow-green, pea green"
    },
    {
      "question": "置き手紙",
      "answer": "おきてがみ",
      "meaning": "letter left behind by someone who has departed, farewell letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "転写",
      "answer": "てんしゃ",
      "meaning": "transcription (of a text, DNA, RNA, etc.), copying, transfer (printing), transcription, transliterat"
    },
    {
      "question": "急増",
      "answer": "きゅうぞう",
      "meaning": "rapid increase, proliferation, surge, explosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "火口",
      "answer": "かこう,ひぐち,ほくち",
      "meaning": "crater, caldera, burner (e.g. on a furnace), burner, nozzle, origin of a fire, tinder, touchwood, ch"
    },
    {
      "question": "当該",
      "answer": "とうがい",
      "meaning": "appropriate (e.g. authorities), concerned, relevant, said, aforementioned, competent, applicable, re"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧殺",
      "answer": "あっさつ",
      "meaning": "crushing to death, crushing (hope, freedom, etc.), suppression, quashing, stifling"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦れ違う",
      "answer": "すれちがう",
      "meaning": "to pass by one another, to miss meeting each other, to miss each other, to disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "海峡",
      "answer": "かいきょう",
      "meaning": "channel (e.g. between two land masses), strait"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛車",
      "answer": "あいしゃ",
      "meaning": "(one's) beloved car (or motorcycle, bicycle, etc.), (one's) wheels"
    },
    {
      "question": "照り返す",
      "answer": "てりかえす",
      "meaning": "to reflect, to throw back light"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸倉",
      "answer": "むなぐら",
      "meaning": "collar, lapels"
    },
    {
      "question": "値引き",
      "answer": "ねびき",
      "meaning": "price reduction, discount"
    },
    {
      "question": "追記",
      "answer": "ついき",
      "meaning": "PS, postscript, appending, addition (esp. of data, information)"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し挟む",
      "answer": "さしはさむ",
      "meaning": "to insert, to interrupt, to slip in a word, to harbor (e.g. doubts), to harbour, to entertain (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "時間割",
      "answer": "じかんわり",
      "meaning": "timetable (esp. a weekly school timetable), schedule"
    },
    {
      "question": "消防",
      "answer": "しょうぼう",
      "meaning": "fire fighting, fire department, fire brigade"
    },
    {
      "question": "終業",
      "answer": "しゅうぎょう",
      "meaning": "end of work day, end of school term, end of school year"
    },
    {
      "question": "共働き",
      "answer": "ともばたらき",
      "meaning": "(husband and wife) both working, dual income"
    },
    {
      "question": "幼生",
      "answer": "ようせい",
      "meaning": "larva, larvae"
    },
    {
      "question": "里親",
      "answer": "さとおや",
      "meaning": "foster parent, foster parents, (pet) caretaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "中肉中背",
      "answer": "ちゅうにくちゅうぜい",
      "meaning": "medium build"
    },
    {
      "question": "序章",
      "answer": "じょしょう",
      "meaning": "prologue, preface"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃する",
      "answer": "はいする",
      "meaning": "to abolish, to abandon, to repeal, to discontinue, to dethrone, to depose"
    },
    {
      "question": "人の道",
      "answer": "ひとのみち",
      "meaning": "moral way of life, correct path"
    },
    {
      "question": "体軀",
      "answer": "たいく",
      "meaning": "body, physique, build, stature"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃材",
      "answer": "はいざい",
      "meaning": "scrap wood, waste wood, waste, waste material, scrap material"
    },
    {
      "question": "同衾",
      "answer": "どうきん",
      "meaning": "sleeping together, sleeping with, sharing a bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し立て",
      "answer": "かくしだて",
      "meaning": "secrecy, keeping secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "後生大事",
      "answer": "ごしょうだいじ",
      "meaning": "with religious zeal, with utmost devotion, take great care of"
    },
    {
      "question": "借金取り",
      "answer": "しゃっきんとり",
      "meaning": "bill collection, bill collector, dun"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓前",
      "answer": "ぼぜん",
      "meaning": "in front of a grave"
    },
    {
      "question": "母艦",
      "answer": "ぼかん",
      "meaning": "mother ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "大門",
      "answer": "だいもん,おおもん",
      "meaning": "large front gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "著名",
      "answer": "ちょめい",
      "meaning": "well-known, noted, celebrated"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇降",
      "answer": "しょうこう",
      "meaning": "ascending and descending, going up and down"
    },
    {
      "question": "調理台",
      "answer": "ちょうりだい",
      "meaning": "kitchen table, kitchen counter, working surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "愉快犯",
      "answer": "ゆかいはん",
      "meaning": "crime committed for fun, criminal who takes delight in people's reaction to his crimes"
    },
    {
      "question": "彼岸",
      "answer": "ひがん",
      "meaning": "equinoctial week (when Buddhist services are held), Buddhist services during the equinoctial week, n"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳び",
      "answer": "とび",
      "meaning": "flying, leaping, flight, leap, zero, naught, oh, flying fish (esp. the Japanese flying fish, Cypselu"
    },
    {
      "question": "短命",
      "answer": "たんめい",
      "meaning": "short life, short lived"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁断症状",
      "answer": "きんだんしょうじょう",
      "meaning": "withdrawal symptoms, abstinence syndrome"
    },
    {
      "question": "怨敵",
      "answer": "おんてき",
      "meaning": "sworn enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き取る",
      "answer": "まきとる",
      "meaning": "to wind (thread, film, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "糊",
      "answer": "のり",
      "meaning": "paste, glue, clothing starch"
    },
    {
      "question": "高地",
      "answer": "こうち",
      "meaning": "high ground, plateau, heights"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛",
      "answer": "かのと,しん",
      "meaning": "8th in rank, eighth sign of the Chinese calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇妃",
      "answer": "こうひ",
      "meaning": "empress, queen"
    },
    {
      "question": "戒",
      "answer": "かい,いんごと",
      "meaning": "admonition, commandment, sila (precept)"
    },
    {
      "question": "父兄",
      "answer": "ふけい",
      "meaning": "guardians, parents, father and older brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "呆れ返る",
      "answer": "あきれかえる",
      "meaning": "to be utterly amazed, to be stunned, to be disgusted"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕置き",
      "answer": "しおき",
      "meaning": "execution, punishment, spanking"
    },
    {
      "question": "英断",
      "answer": "えいだん",
      "meaning": "firm decision, decisive measure, resolute step, excellent decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "座禅",
      "answer": "ざぜん",
      "meaning": "zazen (seated Zen meditation, usu. in a cross-legged position)"
    },
    {
      "question": "布告",
      "answer": "ふこく",
      "meaning": "edict, ordinance, proclamation"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁取り",
      "answer": "ふちどり,へりとり",
      "meaning": "hemming, bordering"
    },
    {
      "question": "土産話",
      "answer": "みやげばなし",
      "meaning": "tales of one's travels"
    },
    {
      "question": "既製品",
      "answer": "きせいひん",
      "meaning": "ready-made goods, off-the-shelf item"
    },
    {
      "question": "花冠",
      "answer": "かかん",
      "meaning": "corolla (of flower), garland, wreath"
    },
    {
      "question": "関税",
      "answer": "かんぜい",
      "meaning": "tariff (import tax), duty, customs"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤熱",
      "answer": "せきねつ,しゃくねつ",
      "meaning": "red hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "外灯",
      "answer": "がいとう",
      "meaning": "outside light"
    },
    {
      "question": "謂う",
      "answer": "いう,ゆう",
      "meaning": "to say, to utter, to declare, to name, to call"
    },
    {
      "question": "路肩",
      "answer": "ろかた,ろけん",
      "meaning": "shoulder (of a road), berm"
    },
    {
      "question": "一助",
      "answer": "いちじょ",
      "meaning": "a help, an aid, some assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗っぽい",
      "answer": "ぞくっぽい",
      "meaning": "vulgar, in poor taste, cheap, low-brow"
    },
    {
      "question": "川崎",
      "answer": "かわさき",
      "meaning": "Kawasaki (city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "騙し討ち",
      "answer": "だましうち",
      "meaning": "surprise attack, sneak attack, foul play"
    },
    {
      "question": "火蓋",
      "answer": "ひぶた",
      "meaning": "apron of a gun, cover for the touch-hole on a cannon or matchlock"
    },
    {
      "question": "神格",
      "answer": "しんかく",
      "meaning": "divinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "著",
      "answer": "ちょ",
      "meaning": "work, book, (a book) by, obvious, striking"
    },
    {
      "question": "付箋",
      "answer": "ふせん",
      "meaning": "tag, slip, label, sticker"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒消し",
      "answer": "どくけし",
      "meaning": "antidote"
    },
    {
      "question": "推力",
      "answer": "すいりょく",
      "meaning": "thrust, driving force, propulsion"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛ほど",
      "answer": "けほど",
      "meaning": "(not even) a little, (not even) a tiny bit"
    },
    {
      "question": "繫げる",
      "answer": "つなげる",
      "meaning": "to connect, to tie, to fasten, to transfer (phone call)"
    },
    {
      "question": "失血",
      "answer": "しっけつ",
      "meaning": "loss of blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "非凡",
      "answer": "ひぼん",
      "meaning": "extraordinary, uncommon, remarkable, unusual, rare, prodigious"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼ね合い",
      "answer": "かねあい",
      "meaning": "equilibrium, good balance, poise"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔が利く",
      "answer": "かおがきく",
      "meaning": "to have a lot of influence, to have clout, to be well known"
    },
    {
      "question": "殉職",
      "answer": "じゅんしょく",
      "meaning": "dying at one's post, being killed in the line of duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "合理性",
      "answer": "ごうりせい",
      "meaning": "rationality, reasonableness"
    },
    {
      "question": "笑い顔",
      "answer": "わらいがお",
      "meaning": "smiling face"
    },
    {
      "question": "過呼吸",
      "answer": "かこきゅう",
      "meaning": "hyperventilation, overbreathing, hyperpnea, overventilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "使わす",
      "answer": "つかわす",
      "meaning": "to send, to dispatch, to despatch, to bestow (favour, etc.), to grant (e.g. pardon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫苑",
      "answer": "しおん",
      "meaning": "aster (Aster tataricus), Tartarian aster, Michaelmas daisy"
    },
    {
      "question": "禊",
      "answer": "みそぎ",
      "meaning": "purification ceremony (performed with water), ritual purification, ablutions"
    },
    {
      "question": "我流",
      "answer": "がりゅう",
      "meaning": "self-taught method, one's own way, one's own style"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛距離",
      "answer": "ひきょり",
      "meaning": "distance (of a ski jump, baseball hit, etc.), carry (of a golf ball), flight (of an arrow)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き取り",
      "answer": "ききとり",
      "meaning": "listening comprehension, aural comprehension, hearing what others say, gathering information, opinio"
    },
    {
      "question": "異色",
      "answer": "いしょく",
      "meaning": "unique, distinctive, novel, singular, unusual, special, different color (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小食",
      "answer": "しょうしょく",
      "meaning": "light eating, spare diet, not eating much"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝泊り",
      "answer": "ねとまり",
      "meaning": "staying the night, lodging (at)"
    },
    {
      "question": "月刊",
      "answer": "げっかん",
      "meaning": "monthly publication, monthly issue"
    },
    {
      "question": "着目",
      "answer": "ちゃくもく",
      "meaning": "attention, giving one's attention, focusing"
    },
    {
      "question": "会戦",
      "answer": "かいせん",
      "meaning": "engagement, battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "入城",
      "answer": "にゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "entry into a castle (by a conquering force)"
    },
    {
      "question": "栗毛",
      "answer": "くりげ",
      "meaning": "chestnut (horse coat color)"
    },
    {
      "question": "専ら",
      "answer": "もっぱら,もはら",
      "meaning": "wholly, solely, entirely, exclusively, devotedly, fixedly, principally, mostly, chiefly, mainly"
    },
    {
      "question": "形無し",
      "answer": "かたなし",
      "meaning": "spoiled, spoilt, ruined, loss of face"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺らめき",
      "answer": "ゆらめき",
      "meaning": "shaking, swaying"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭が重い",
      "answer": "あたまがおもい",
      "meaning": "feeling heavy in the head, heavy-headed, sick with worry"
    },
    {
      "question": "清流",
      "answer": "せいりゅう",
      "meaning": "clear stream"
    },
    {
      "question": "流動",
      "answer": "りゅうどう",
      "meaning": "flow"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛玩",
      "answer": "あいがん",
      "meaning": "caring for (esp. a pet or a small object), cherishing, being fond of, prizing, treasuring"
    },
    {
      "question": "初める",
      "answer": "そめる",
      "meaning": "to begin to"
    },
    {
      "question": "其",
      "answer": "それ,し,そ",
      "meaning": "that, it, then, that point (in time), that time, there, you, oneself, themself, he, she, that person"
    },
    {
      "question": "元祖",
      "answer": "がんそ",
      "meaning": "originator, pioneer, inventor, founder, progenitor, primogenitor, founder of a family line"
    },
    {
      "question": "排他的",
      "answer": "はいたてき",
      "meaning": "exclusive, exclusionary, restrictive, clannish"
    },
    {
      "question": "暫定的",
      "answer": "ざんていてき",
      "meaning": "temporary, provisional, interim"
    },
    {
      "question": "控え",
      "answer": "ひかえ",
      "meaning": "reserve, spare, backup, note, memorandum, duplicate, copy, stub (of a ticket, etc.), waiting one's t"
    },
    {
      "question": "菱",
      "answer": "ひし",
      "meaning": "water caltrop, water chestnut, caltrop (weapon)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大帝",
      "answer": "たいてい",
      "meaning": "great emperor, ... the Great"
    },
    {
      "question": "共学",
      "answer": "きょうがく",
      "meaning": "coeducation"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り糸",
      "answer": "つりいと",
      "meaning": "fishing line"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩赦",
      "answer": "おんしゃ",
      "meaning": "amnesty, pardon"
    },
    {
      "question": "気掛かり",
      "answer": "きがかり",
      "meaning": "worry, anxiety, concern"
    },
    {
      "question": "登用",
      "answer": "とうよう",
      "meaning": "appointment, assignment, promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "上腕",
      "answer": "じょうわん",
      "meaning": "upper arm"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦げ目",
      "answer": "こげめ",
      "meaning": "burn mark, grilled surface (e.g. on a steak)"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽くし",
      "answer": "づくし,ずくし",
      "meaning": "all sorts of, all kinds of"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み込み",
      "answer": "のみこみ",
      "meaning": "swallowing, understanding, apprehension"
    },
    {
      "question": "烈風",
      "answer": "れっぷう",
      "meaning": "gale, violent (strong) wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "商船",
      "answer": "しょうせん",
      "meaning": "merchant ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "先遣隊",
      "answer": "せんけんたい",
      "meaning": "advance party, advance team, advance group, vanguard unit"
    },
    {
      "question": "切除",
      "answer": "せつじょ",
      "meaning": "cut off, cut out, ablation, resection, surgical removal"
    },
    {
      "question": "湧き水",
      "answer": "わきみず",
      "meaning": "spring water"
    },
    {
      "question": "何たる",
      "answer": "なんたる",
      "meaning": "what (e.g. 'what rudeness'), what (something) is like"
    },
    {
      "question": "埒外",
      "answer": "らちがい",
      "meaning": "out of bounds, beyond the pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち込み",
      "answer": "うちこみ",
      "meaning": "driving, pounding in, shooting into, implantation, invasion, falling badly in love, putting (one's h"
    },
    {
      "question": "慇懃無礼",
      "answer": "いんぎんぶれい",
      "meaning": "hypocritical courtesy, superficially polite but rude in intent"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒樽",
      "answer": "さかだる",
      "meaning": "wine cask or barrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "下種",
      "answer": "げす",
      "meaning": "low-life, sleazebag, boor, person of humble rank, humble person, peasant, menial, churl, petty offic"
    },
    {
      "question": "血の雨",
      "answer": "ちのあめ",
      "meaning": "bloodshed"
    },
    {
      "question": "専業主婦",
      "answer": "せんぎょうしゅふ",
      "meaning": "housewife"
    },
    {
      "question": "直線距離",
      "answer": "ちょくせんきょり",
      "meaning": "distance in a straight line"
    },
    {
      "question": "辰",
      "answer": "たつ",
      "meaning": "the Dragon (fifth sign of the Chinese zodiac), hour of the Dragon (around 8am, 7-9am, or 8-10am), ea"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒地",
      "answer": "あれち,こうち",
      "meaning": "wasteland, wilderness, abandoned land, devastated land, The Wasteland (poem by T.S. Eliot)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口伝",
      "answer": "くでん,こうでん",
      "meaning": "oral instruction, passing information by word-of-mouth, oral tradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱反射",
      "answer": "らんはんしゃ",
      "meaning": "diffuse reflection, diffused reflection, irregular reflection"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯れ葉",
      "answer": "かれは",
      "meaning": "dead leaf, dry leaves"
    },
    {
      "question": "括り",
      "answer": "くくり",
      "meaning": "knot, tying, bundle, lumping, conclusion, ending"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄贈",
      "answer": "きぞう,きそう",
      "meaning": "donation, presentation, gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "児戯",
      "answer": "じぎ",
      "meaning": "mere child's play"
    },
    {
      "question": "受身",
      "answer": "うけみ",
      "meaning": "the defensive, passive attitude, passivity, passiveness, the passive, passive voice, ukemi (the art"
    },
    {
      "question": "謝意",
      "answer": "しゃい",
      "meaning": "gratitude, thanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚がる",
      "answer": "あがる",
      "meaning": "to rise, to go up, to come up, to ascend, to be raised, to enter (esp. from outdoors), to come in, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨場感",
      "answer": "りんじょうかん",
      "meaning": "(sense of) presence, realism, ambiance"
    },
    {
      "question": "入札",
      "answer": "にゅうさつ",
      "meaning": "bid, tender, bidding"
    },
    {
      "question": "中位",
      "answer": "ちゅうい,ちゅうくらい,ちゅうぐらい",
      "meaning": "medium, mediocrity, average, about medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "昔馴染み",
      "answer": "むかしなじみ",
      "meaning": "old friend, familiar face"
    },
    {
      "question": "贈呈",
      "answer": "ぞうてい",
      "meaning": "presentation (e.g. of a gift, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が輩",
      "answer": "わがはい",
      "meaning": "I, me, myself, we, us, ourselves"
    },
    {
      "question": "油揚げ",
      "answer": "あぶらあげ,あぶらげ",
      "meaning": "aburaage, thin deep-fried slices of tofu, frying in oil, deep-fried food"
    },
    {
      "question": "宮中",
      "answer": "きゅうちゅう",
      "meaning": "imperial court"
    },
    {
      "question": "二輪",
      "answer": "にりん",
      "meaning": "two wheels, two flowers"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦労人",
      "answer": "くろうにん",
      "meaning": "worldly-wise man"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆発力",
      "answer": "ばくはつりょく",
      "meaning": "explosive power"
    },
    {
      "question": "接戦",
      "answer": "せっせん",
      "meaning": "close combat, close contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "真に迫る",
      "answer": "しんにせまる",
      "meaning": "to be true to nature, to be lifelike"
    },
    {
      "question": "御前試合",
      "answer": "ごぜんじあい",
      "meaning": "game (contest) held in the presence of a lord (daimyo, shogun)"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹上",
      "answer": "じゅじょう",
      "meaning": "up in a tree, in the trees"
    },
    {
      "question": "主題",
      "answer": "しゅだい",
      "meaning": "subject, theme, motif"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が急く",
      "answer": "きがせく",
      "meaning": "to feel under pressure, to feel impatient, to be in a hurry"
    },
    {
      "question": "白夜",
      "answer": "びゃくや,はくや",
      "meaning": "night under the midnight sun, white night (at extreme latitudes), night during which the sun doesn't"
    },
    {
      "question": "怨む",
      "answer": "うらむ",
      "meaning": "to bear a grudge against, to resent, to blame, to curse, to feel bitter towards"
    },
    {
      "question": "土産物",
      "answer": "みやげもの",
      "meaning": "souvenir"
    },
    {
      "question": "増量",
      "answer": "ぞうりょう",
      "meaning": "increased volume or quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "即日",
      "answer": "そくじつ",
      "meaning": "(on) the same day"
    },
    {
      "question": "太守",
      "answer": "たいしゅ",
      "meaning": "viceroy, governor-general"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び蹴り",
      "answer": "とびげり",
      "meaning": "dropkick, flying kick"
    },
    {
      "question": "任期",
      "answer": "にんき",
      "meaning": "term of office"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガン無視",
      "answer": "ガンむし",
      "meaning": "completely disregarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "会する",
      "answer": "かいする",
      "meaning": "to meet, to assemble, to gather, to encounter, to run into"
    },
    {
      "question": "再演",
      "answer": "さいえん",
      "meaning": "another showing (of a play), recapitulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "気球",
      "answer": "ききゅう",
      "meaning": "balloon, blimp"
    },
    {
      "question": "肥沃",
      "answer": "ひよく",
      "meaning": "fertile, rich, productive"
    },
    {
      "question": "人柱",
      "answer": "ひとばしら",
      "meaning": "human pillar, human sacrifice"
    },
    {
      "question": "除名",
      "answer": "じょめい",
      "meaning": "expulsion, excommunication"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪食",
      "answer": "あくじき,あくしょく",
      "meaning": "eating strange food, eating bizarre things, simple diet, plain food, simple food, frugal meal, eatin"
    },
    {
      "question": "二度見",
      "answer": "にどみ",
      "meaning": "double take (esp. out of surprise)"
    },
    {
      "question": "太め",
      "answer": "ふとめ",
      "meaning": "plump, somewhat large"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉月",
      "answer": "はづき",
      "meaning": "eighth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "丹",
      "answer": "に",
      "meaning": "red earth (i.e. containing cinnabar or minium), vermilion"
    },
    {
      "question": "前哨戦",
      "answer": "ぜんしょうせん",
      "meaning": "(preliminary) skirmish, prelude, preliminary encounter, warm-up match (e.g. before a final)"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌触り",
      "answer": "したざわり",
      "meaning": "feel on the tongue (of food or drink), texture"
    },
    {
      "question": "睨めっこ",
      "answer": "にらめっこ",
      "meaning": "staring-out (down) game, game in which two children looking at each other try to make the opponents"
    },
    {
      "question": "画す",
      "answer": "かくす",
      "meaning": "to draw (a line), to demarcate, to mark, to divide, to map out, to plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "南京錠",
      "answer": "なんきんじょう",
      "meaning": "padlock"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨付き",
      "answer": "ほねつき",
      "meaning": "on the bone (meat, etc.), unboned, skeletal system, skeleton"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち合い",
      "answer": "たちあい",
      "meaning": "rising from a crouch to charge, initial charge, face-off"
    },
    {
      "question": "見地",
      "answer": "けんち",
      "meaning": "point of view"
    },
    {
      "question": "人海戦術",
      "answer": "じんかいせんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "human-wave tactics, throwing people at a problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "転属",
      "answer": "てんぞく",
      "meaning": "changing assignments"
    },
    {
      "question": "程近い",
      "answer": "ほどちかい",
      "meaning": "near, nearby, not far off"
    },
    {
      "question": "独",
      "answer": "どく",
      "meaning": "Germany"
    },
    {
      "question": "確実性",
      "answer": "かくじつせい",
      "meaning": "certainty"
    },
    {
      "question": "早変わり",
      "answer": "はやがわり",
      "meaning": "quick change, quick transformation, metamorphosis, turning suddenly into"
    },
    {
      "question": "架",
      "answer": "たるき,か,ませ",
      "meaning": "rafter, rack, mount, stand, short roughly woven fence, divider between boxes (i.e. for box seats) in"
    },
    {
      "question": "大正",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "Taishō era (1912.7.30-1926.12.25), Taisho era"
    },
    {
      "question": "事実無根",
      "answer": "じじつむこん",
      "meaning": "groundless, entirely contrary to fact"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽くめ",
      "answer": "ずくめ,づくめ",
      "meaning": "entirely, completely, all, nothing but"
    },
    {
      "question": "船底",
      "answer": "せんてい,ふなぞこ,ふなそこ",
      "meaning": "ship's bottom, bilge"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠滅",
      "answer": "いんめつ",
      "meaning": "destruction (esp. of evidence), spoliation, suppression, hiding, concealment"
    },
    {
      "question": "与",
      "answer": "むた",
      "meaning": "together with ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "足し算",
      "answer": "たしざん",
      "meaning": "addition"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄与",
      "answer": "きよ",
      "meaning": "contribution, service"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨上がり",
      "answer": "あめあがり,あまあがり",
      "meaning": "after the rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "放し飼い",
      "answer": "はなしがい",
      "meaning": "free range breeding, pasturing, grazing, letting run free (dog, child, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賽銭",
      "answer": "さいせん",
      "meaning": "monetary offering, offertory"
    },
    {
      "question": "木偶",
      "answer": "でく",
      "meaning": "wooden figure, wooden doll, puppet, blockhead, good-for-nothing, fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹立",
      "answer": "じゅりつ",
      "meaning": "establishment, founding, setting (a record)"
    },
    {
      "question": "水曜",
      "answer": "すいよう",
      "meaning": "Wednesday"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴論",
      "answer": "ぼうろん",
      "meaning": "irrational (line of) argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁り",
      "answer": "あさり,すなどり",
      "meaning": "searching, rummaging, fishing, collecting shells, fisherman"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏像",
      "answer": "ぶつぞう",
      "meaning": "statue of Buddha, image of Buddha, Buddhist statue, Buddhist image"
    },
    {
      "question": "留め具",
      "answer": "とめぐ",
      "meaning": "latch, clasp, catch, check, fastener"
    },
    {
      "question": "染め",
      "answer": "そめ",
      "meaning": "dyeing, printing"
    },
    {
      "question": "手酷い",
      "answer": "てひどい",
      "meaning": "severe, harsh"
    },
    {
      "question": "季",
      "answer": "き",
      "meaning": "season, seasonal word or phrase (in haiku), year"
    },
    {
      "question": "社畜",
      "answer": "しゃちく",
      "meaning": "corporate drone, corporate slave"
    },
    {
      "question": "別口",
      "answer": "べつくち",
      "meaning": "different item, different lot"
    },
    {
      "question": "代筆",
      "answer": "だいひつ",
      "meaning": "writing on someone's behalf"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙台",
      "answer": "せんだい",
      "meaning": "Sendai (city in Miyagi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "相討ち",
      "answer": "あいうち",
      "meaning": "simultaneously striking one another (in kendo, etc.), draw, tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "物質的",
      "answer": "ぶっしつてき",
      "meaning": "material, physical"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯剣",
      "answer": "たいけん",
      "meaning": "wearing a sword, being armed with a sword, sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "国民的",
      "answer": "こくみんてき",
      "meaning": "national, nationwide, relevant to all citizens"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘書官",
      "answer": "ひしょかん",
      "meaning": "minister's secretary"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼び水",
      "answer": "よびみず",
      "meaning": "pump-priming, rousing, stimulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻を突く",
      "answer": "はなをつく",
      "meaning": "to assail the nostrils (smell), to go nose-to-nose (with someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "貨物船",
      "answer": "かもつせん",
      "meaning": "freighter (vessel), cargo ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "連合国",
      "answer": "れんごうこく",
      "meaning": "allied nations, the Allies (World War I, World War II)"
    },
    {
      "question": "孔雀",
      "answer": "くじゃく,くざく",
      "meaning": "peafowl (incl. the male peacock, female peahen, and young peachick)"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐輪場",
      "answer": "ちゅうりんじょう",
      "meaning": "parking area for bicycles"
    },
    {
      "question": "山手",
      "answer": "やまて,やまのて",
      "meaning": "place near the mountains, hilly section of a city (e.g. Tokyo, Kobe, Yokohama), hilly section of a c"
    },
    {
      "question": "後学",
      "answer": "こうがく",
      "meaning": "younger scholar, future reference"
    },
    {
      "question": "星屑",
      "answer": "ほしくず",
      "meaning": "stardust"
    },
    {
      "question": "孝行",
      "answer": "こうこう",
      "meaning": "filial piety, showing devotion (to someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "女手",
      "answer": "おんなで",
      "meaning": "female help, female labor, female labour, female worker, woman's handwriting, hiragana"
    },
    {
      "question": "一張羅",
      "answer": "いっちょうら",
      "meaning": "one's (only) good suit (or kimono)"
    },
    {
      "question": "急須",
      "answer": "きゅうす",
      "meaning": "small teapot"
    },
    {
      "question": "一塊",
      "answer": "いっかい,ひとかたまり",
      "meaning": "one lump, one group"
    },
    {
      "question": "弧",
      "answer": "こ",
      "meaning": "arc"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り買い",
      "answer": "うりかい",
      "meaning": "trade, buying and selling"
    },
    {
      "question": "万里",
      "answer": "ばんり",
      "meaning": "thousands of miles"
    },
    {
      "question": "特進",
      "answer": "とくしん",
      "meaning": "special promotion (in rank or grade)"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲門",
      "answer": "ほうもん",
      "meaning": "gunport, embrasure, muzzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "区間",
      "answer": "くかん",
      "meaning": "section (of track, etc.), segment, dimension, interval"
    },
    {
      "question": "写真立て",
      "answer": "しゃしんたて",
      "meaning": "photo frame (with stand)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小高い",
      "answer": "こだかい",
      "meaning": "slightly elevated"
    },
    {
      "question": "鵺",
      "answer": "ぬえ",
      "meaning": "Japanese chimera, mythical creature with a monkey's head, tanuki's body, tiger's limbs, and a snake"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼気",
      "answer": "きき",
      "meaning": "ghastly, dreadful"
    },
    {
      "question": "四位",
      "answer": "しい",
      "meaning": "fourth court rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "地主",
      "answer": "じぬし",
      "meaning": "landowner, landlord, landlady"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞職",
      "answer": "じしょく",
      "meaning": "resignation"
    },
    {
      "question": "首になる",
      "answer": "くびになる",
      "meaning": "to be sacked, to be fired, to be dismissed, to be beheaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴力",
      "answer": "ちょうりょく",
      "meaning": "hearing ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄犬",
      "answer": "だけん",
      "meaning": "mongrel, cur, mutt"
    },
    {
      "question": "法王",
      "answer": "ほうおう",
      "meaning": "Pope, Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "腫瘍",
      "answer": "しゅよう",
      "meaning": "tumor, tumour, neoplasm, neoplasia"
    },
    {
      "question": "増産",
      "answer": "ぞうさん",
      "meaning": "production increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "不義",
      "answer": "ふぎ",
      "meaning": "immorality, injustice, misconduct, impropriety, perfidy, adultery, infidelity, cuckoldry, murdering"
    },
    {
      "question": "特撮",
      "answer": "とくさつ",
      "meaning": "special effects, SFX, tokusatsu (genre of live-action film or television drama that makes heavy use"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄氷",
      "answer": "はくひょう,うすごおり",
      "meaning": "thin ice"
    },
    {
      "question": "総務",
      "answer": "そうむ",
      "meaning": "general affairs, general business, manager, director, adjutant general"
    },
    {
      "question": "利する",
      "answer": "りする",
      "meaning": "to profit, to benefit from, to take advantage of, to make good use of"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠形",
      "answer": "おんぎょう,いんぎょう",
      "meaning": "invisibility (through magic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "音痴",
      "answer": "おんち",
      "meaning": "tone-deafness, amusia, having no ear for music, tone-deaf, off-key, having no sense (of something),"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩透かし",
      "answer": "かたすかし",
      "meaning": "under-shoulder swing-down, technique of grasping the arm of the opponent, the moment he comes forwar"
    },
    {
      "question": "反目",
      "answer": "はんもく",
      "meaning": "enmity, antagonism, hostility"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭が固い",
      "answer": "あたまがかたい",
      "meaning": "thickheaded, obstinate, inflexible, stubborn"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯ける",
      "answer": "おどける,たわける",
      "meaning": "to jest, to joke, to play the fool, to act indecently, to be silly over, to talk foolishly"
    },
    {
      "question": "上客",
      "answer": "じょうきゃく,じょうかく",
      "meaning": "guest of honor, guest of honour, good customer, important customer"
    },
    {
      "question": "小回り",
      "answer": "こまわり",
      "meaning": "tight turn, adaptability, flexibility, maneuverability"
    },
    {
      "question": "適量",
      "answer": "てきりょう",
      "meaning": "proper quantity, suitable amount, proper dose, optimal dose"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶対安静",
      "answer": "ぜったいあんせい",
      "meaning": "complete bed rest, complete rest and quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "腋",
      "answer": "わき",
      "meaning": "armpit, under one's arm, side, flank, beside, close to, near, by, aside, to the side, away, out of t"
    },
    {
      "question": "精強",
      "answer": "せいきょう",
      "meaning": "powerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "権力闘争",
      "answer": "けんりょくとうそう",
      "meaning": "power struggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "急性",
      "answer": "きゅうせい",
      "meaning": "acute (illness)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人道的",
      "answer": "じんどうてき",
      "meaning": "humane"
    },
    {
      "question": "末代",
      "answer": "まつだい",
      "meaning": "forever, in perpetuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "名君",
      "answer": "めいくん",
      "meaning": "wise ruler, enlightened monarch, benevolent lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "断頭台",
      "answer": "だんとうだい",
      "meaning": "(beheading) block, guillotine, scaffold"
    },
    {
      "question": "口髭",
      "answer": "くちひげ",
      "meaning": "moustache, mustache"
    },
    {
      "question": "風評",
      "answer": "ふうひょう",
      "meaning": "rumor, rumour, gossip, report"
    },
    {
      "question": "厄",
      "answer": "やく",
      "meaning": "misfortune, bad luck, evil, disaster, unlucky year, critical year, smallpox"
    },
    {
      "question": "王手",
      "answer": "おうて",
      "meaning": "check"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い付く",
      "answer": "くいつく",
      "meaning": "to bite at, to snap at, to nibble, to get one's teeth into (metaphorically), to get to grips with, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜光",
      "answer": "やこう",
      "meaning": "nocturnal luminescence, noctilucence"
    },
    {
      "question": "真白い",
      "answer": "まっしろい",
      "meaning": "pure white"
    },
    {
      "question": "植民地",
      "answer": "しょくみんち",
      "meaning": "colony, (immigrant) community"
    },
    {
      "question": "説明文",
      "answer": "せつめいぶん",
      "meaning": "explanatory note"
    },
    {
      "question": "構",
      "answer": "かまえ,かじ",
      "meaning": "structure, construction, appearance, posture (e.g. in martial arts), pose, stance, readiness, determ"
    },
    {
      "question": "燕尾服",
      "answer": "えんびふく",
      "meaning": "tailcoat"
    },
    {
      "question": "踊り狂う",
      "answer": "おどりくるう",
      "meaning": "to dance in ecstasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り急ぎ",
      "answer": "とりいそぎ",
      "meaning": "in haste"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸が躍る",
      "answer": "むねがおどる",
      "meaning": "to be excited, to be elated"
    },
    {
      "question": "快",
      "answer": "かい",
      "meaning": "pleasure, delight, enjoyment"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏執",
      "answer": "へんしゅう,へんしつ",
      "meaning": "bias, eccentricity, obstinacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝啓",
      "answer": "はいけい",
      "meaning": "Dear (so and so), Dear Sir, Dear Madam, To Whom It May Concern"
    },
    {
      "question": "八幡",
      "answer": "はちまん",
      "meaning": "Hachiman (God of War), Hachiman shrine, certainly"
    },
    {
      "question": "水際",
      "answer": "みずぎわ,みぎわ",
      "meaning": "beach, water's edge, coastline, national border, before entering the country, shore, waterside"
    },
    {
      "question": "捌ける",
      "answer": "さばける,はける",
      "meaning": "to sell well, to sell out, to be worldly and understanding, to be sensible, to be straightforward, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "成人式",
      "answer": "せいじんしき",
      "meaning": "coming-of-age ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "機能性",
      "answer": "きのうせい",
      "meaning": "functionality"
    },
    {
      "question": "影が薄い",
      "answer": "かげがうすい",
      "meaning": "in the background, not standing out"
    },
    {
      "question": "全知全能",
      "answer": "ぜんちぜんのう",
      "meaning": "omniscience and omnipotence"
    },
    {
      "question": "自撮り",
      "answer": "じどり",
      "meaning": "taking a picture or video of oneself (esp. with a smartphone camera), selfie, video selfie, self-tak"
    },
    {
      "question": "晩酌",
      "answer": "ばんしゃく",
      "meaning": "drink at home with one's evening meal, dinner-time drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "人知",
      "answer": "じんち",
      "meaning": "human intellect, knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "有給",
      "answer": "ゆうきゅう",
      "meaning": "salaried, with pay, vacation, (paid) holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "実母",
      "answer": "じつぼ",
      "meaning": "one's real mother, natural mother, birth mother, biological mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅支度",
      "answer": "たびじたく",
      "meaning": "preparations for a journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "落し物",
      "answer": "おとしもの",
      "meaning": "lost property, something dropped and left behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "免許証",
      "answer": "めんきょしょう",
      "meaning": "licence, license, permit, certificate (of qualification)"
    },
    {
      "question": "着想",
      "answer": "ちゃくそう",
      "meaning": "conception, idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "冴え渡る",
      "answer": "さえわたる",
      "meaning": "to be clear, to be distinct, to be precise, to be skillful, to be skilful, to be deft, to be well-ex"
    },
    {
      "question": "有線",
      "answer": "ゆうせん",
      "meaning": "wired, cabled, communication by wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い叩く",
      "answer": "かいたたく",
      "meaning": "to beat down prices, to strike a hard bargain"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉感的",
      "answer": "にっかんてき,にくかんてき",
      "meaning": "sensual, sexy, voluptuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋愛結婚",
      "answer": "れんあいけっこん",
      "meaning": "love marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "切れ間",
      "answer": "きれま",
      "meaning": "interval, break, rift (in clouds)"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み躙る",
      "answer": "ふみにじる",
      "meaning": "to trample underfoot, to tread on, to crush with a foot"
    },
    {
      "question": "査察",
      "answer": "ささつ",
      "meaning": "inspection (for compliance), investigation (tax, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵性",
      "answer": "てきせい",
      "meaning": "hostile nature, inimical character"
    },
    {
      "question": "後退り",
      "answer": "あとずさり,あとじさり",
      "meaning": "stepping back, drawing back"
    },
    {
      "question": "特番",
      "answer": "とくばん",
      "meaning": "special radio or television programme, television special"
    },
    {
      "question": "臨界点",
      "answer": "りんかいてん",
      "meaning": "critical point (temperature)"
    },
    {
      "question": "贅肉",
      "answer": "ぜいにく",
      "meaning": "excess flesh, surplus fat, flab"
    },
    {
      "question": "槽",
      "answer": "ふね,そう,うけ",
      "meaning": "tank, tub, vat, trough, body (of a biwa), basin"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘",
      "answer": "ねば",
      "meaning": "stickiness, gumminess, sticky material, gummy material, clay"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵站",
      "answer": "へいたん",
      "meaning": "supply train, communications, logistics"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇病",
      "answer": "きびょう",
      "meaning": "strange disease, rare disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚図",
      "answer": "ぐず",
      "meaning": "dullard, indecisive person"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄切り",
      "answer": "うすぎり",
      "meaning": "thin slice, slicing thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "木曜",
      "answer": "もくよう",
      "meaning": "Thursday"
    },
    {
      "question": "難病",
      "answer": "なんびょう",
      "meaning": "incurable disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰毛",
      "answer": "いんもう",
      "meaning": "pubic hair"
    },
    {
      "question": "歌劇",
      "answer": "かげき",
      "meaning": "opera"
    },
    {
      "question": "艶然",
      "answer": "えんぜん",
      "meaning": "sweetly smiling, like the smiling of a beauty, gracious"
    },
    {
      "question": "隙間風",
      "answer": "すきまかぜ",
      "meaning": "draft, draught, cold air entering through the crack of a door or window, cooling off of a relationsh"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋情",
      "answer": "れんじょう,こいなさけ",
      "meaning": "love, attachment, lovesickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "覆い",
      "answer": "おおい",
      "meaning": "cover, mantle, shroud, hood"
    },
    {
      "question": "至り",
      "answer": "いたり",
      "meaning": "utmost limit, extremity, result"
    },
    {
      "question": "佩く",
      "answer": "はく",
      "meaning": "to put on (lower-body clothing, e.g. pants, skirt, footwear), to wear, to affix (a sword to one's hi"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁業",
      "answer": "ぎょぎょう",
      "meaning": "fishing (industry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎ら",
      "answer": "まばら",
      "meaning": "sparse, thin, scattered, straggling, sporadic"
    },
    {
      "question": "照会",
      "answer": "しょうかい",
      "meaning": "inquiry, enquiry, query, reference"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪辱",
      "answer": "せつじょく",
      "meaning": "vindication of honour, vindication of honor, making up for loss, revenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "麒麟",
      "answer": "きりん",
      "meaning": "giraffe (Giraffa camelopardalis), qilin (Chinese unicorn), Kirin (brand of beer)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弩",
      "answer": "いしゆみ,ど",
      "meaning": "crossbow (incl. large models operated by a number of people), netted apparatus atop a wall containin"
    },
    {
      "question": "木工",
      "answer": "もっこう",
      "meaning": "woodworking, woodworker, carpenter"
    },
    {
      "question": "下手人",
      "answer": "げしゅにん",
      "meaning": "offender, criminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "創始者",
      "answer": "そうししゃ",
      "meaning": "originator, founder"
    },
    {
      "question": "主軸",
      "answer": "しゅじく",
      "meaning": "main spindle, main shaft, linchpin, pivot, principal axis, main axis"
    },
    {
      "question": "頑",
      "answer": "かたくな",
      "meaning": "obstinate, stubborn, mulish, die-hard, bigoted"
    },
    {
      "question": "躍進",
      "answer": "やくしん",
      "meaning": "making rapid progress, making great advances, rush, dash, onslaught"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き消す",
      "answer": "ふきけす",
      "meaning": "to blow out (a flame)"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠語",
      "answer": "いんご",
      "meaning": "secret language, jargon, cant, argot, slang"
    },
    {
      "question": "石川",
      "answer": "いしかわ",
      "meaning": "Ishikawa (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飽和",
      "answer": "ほうわ",
      "meaning": "saturation, satiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "撤廃",
      "answer": "てっぱい",
      "meaning": "annulment, abolition, repeal, rescission"
    },
    {
      "question": "目の毒",
      "answer": "めのどく",
      "meaning": "tempting thing, (too much of a) temptation, something that shouldn't be seen, the last thing one nee"
    },
    {
      "question": "真名",
      "answer": "まな,まんな",
      "meaning": "kanji (as opposed to kana), printed style (of writing Chinese characters), square style, block style"
    },
    {
      "question": "連帯責任",
      "answer": "れんたいせきにん",
      "meaning": "collective responsibility, joint liability"
    },
    {
      "question": "小腹",
      "answer": "こばら",
      "meaning": "belly, abdomen"
    },
    {
      "question": "出仕",
      "answer": "しゅっし",
      "meaning": "attendance, serving"
    },
    {
      "question": "美意識",
      "answer": "びいしき",
      "meaning": "sense of beauty, aesthetic sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "達筆",
      "answer": "たっぴつ",
      "meaning": "good handwriting, skillful penmanship, speedy writing, vigorous writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "手掛ける",
      "answer": "てがける",
      "meaning": "to handle, to manage, to deal with, to work with, to have experience with, to rear, to look after"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗜虐",
      "answer": "しぎゃく",
      "meaning": "sadism"
    },
    {
      "question": "野性的",
      "answer": "やせいてき",
      "meaning": "wild (plants, animals, etc.), uncouth, rough, unpolished"
    },
    {
      "question": "造花",
      "answer": "ぞうか",
      "meaning": "artificial flower, imitation flower, artificial flower making"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬人化",
      "answer": "ぎじんか",
      "meaning": "personification, anthropomorphization"
    },
    {
      "question": "舌足らず",
      "answer": "したたらず",
      "meaning": "lisping, poorly expressed, unclear (wording), imprecise (expression), inadequate (explanation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "八重",
      "answer": "やえ",
      "meaning": "multilayered, doubled"
    },
    {
      "question": "閨",
      "answer": "ねや",
      "meaning": "bedroom (esp. one used by a married couple), sleeping quarters, inner room, room at the back of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "夕立",
      "answer": "ゆうだち",
      "meaning": "(sudden) evening shower (rain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連綿",
      "answer": "れんめん",
      "meaning": "unbroken, uninterrupted, on and on, continuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "貞淑",
      "answer": "ていしゅく",
      "meaning": "chastity, virtue, fidelity, feminine modesty"
    },
    {
      "question": "逼迫",
      "answer": "ひっぱく",
      "meaning": "tightness (of money, financial conditions, etc.), pressure, stringency, being strained (of a situati"
    },
    {
      "question": "障り",
      "answer": "さわり",
      "meaning": "hindrance, obstacle, harm, bad effect, sickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "年賀状",
      "answer": "ねんがじょう",
      "meaning": "New Year's card"
    },
    {
      "question": "男子校",
      "answer": "だんしこう",
      "meaning": "boys' school"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑車",
      "answer": "かっしゃ",
      "meaning": "pulley, block, tackle"
    },
    {
      "question": "検診",
      "answer": "けんしん",
      "meaning": "physical examination, medical examination, health checkup, health screening"
    },
    {
      "question": "享楽",
      "answer": "きょうらく",
      "meaning": "enjoyment, pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "何時頃",
      "answer": "いつごろ",
      "meaning": "about when, about what time, how soon"
    },
    {
      "question": "成体",
      "answer": "せいたい",
      "meaning": "adult organism, imago"
    },
    {
      "question": "換わる",
      "answer": "かわる",
      "meaning": "to succeed, to relieve, to replace, to take the place of, to substitute for, to take over for, to re"
    },
    {
      "question": "父方",
      "answer": "ちちかた",
      "meaning": "father's side of family, paternal (grandfather, uncle, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "外皮",
      "answer": "がいひ",
      "meaning": "skin, outer skin, integument, husk, hull, shell, crust, rind, envelope, exodermis, pellicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "上背",
      "answer": "うわぜい",
      "meaning": "stature, height"
    },
    {
      "question": "玄人",
      "answer": "くろうと,くろと",
      "meaning": "expert, professional, master, connoisseur, woman in the nightlife business, demimondaine, geisha and"
    },
    {
      "question": "反証",
      "answer": "はんしょう",
      "meaning": "proof to the contrary, disproof, counter-evidence, rebuttal, refutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "総会",
      "answer": "そうかい",
      "meaning": "general meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒らし",
      "answer": "あらし",
      "meaning": "(Internet) troll, disturber, raising havoc, laying waste, trolling, vandalism, robbery, holdup, robb"
    },
    {
      "question": "反り",
      "answer": "そり,かえり",
      "meaning": "warp, curvature, curve, arch, turning over, flipping over, reply, response, marks written alongside"
    },
    {
      "question": "石橋",
      "answer": "いしばし,せっきょう",
      "meaning": "stone bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "支持率",
      "answer": "しじりつ",
      "meaning": "approval rating"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻声",
      "answer": "はなごえ,びせい",
      "meaning": "nasal voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "心安い",
      "answer": "こころやすい",
      "meaning": "intimate, carefree, familiar, friendly"
    },
    {
      "question": "全国的",
      "answer": "ぜんこくてき",
      "meaning": "nationwide, countrywide, national, throughout the country"
    },
    {
      "question": "四畳半",
      "answer": "よじょうはん",
      "meaning": "four and a half tatami mats, four-and-a-half-mat room, small room esp. for assignations"
    },
    {
      "question": "堀",
      "answer": "ほり",
      "meaning": "moat, fosse, canal, ditch"
    },
    {
      "question": "心無い",
      "answer": "こころない",
      "meaning": "thoughtless, inconsiderate, tasteless, cruel"
    },
    {
      "question": "超過",
      "answer": "ちょうか",
      "meaning": "excess, being more than"
    },
    {
      "question": "劫火",
      "answer": "ごうか,こうか",
      "meaning": "world-destroying conflagration"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑走",
      "answer": "かっそう",
      "meaning": "gliding, sliding, skating (on ice), glide, slide, taxiing (aircraft), making a takeoff run"
    },
    {
      "question": "北風",
      "answer": "きたかぜ,ほくふう",
      "meaning": "north wind, northerly wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦わす",
      "answer": "たたかわす",
      "meaning": "to compete, to vie, to contend, to make fight against another (person, animal), to pit against, to s"
    },
    {
      "question": "別館",
      "answer": "べっかん",
      "meaning": "annex (to a building), annexe, extension, supplementary building"
    },
    {
      "question": "生物兵器",
      "answer": "せいぶつへいき",
      "meaning": "biological weapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "亡き後",
      "answer": "なきあと",
      "meaning": "after one's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "大道芸",
      "answer": "だいどうげい",
      "meaning": "street performing"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り結ぶ",
      "answer": "きりむすぶ",
      "meaning": "to cross swords with"
    },
    {
      "question": "消耗戦",
      "answer": "しょうもうせん",
      "meaning": "war of attrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "主観的",
      "answer": "しゅかんてき",
      "meaning": "subjective"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪解け",
      "answer": "ゆきどけ",
      "meaning": "snow thaw, thawing"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬死に",
      "answer": "いぬじに",
      "meaning": "dying in vain, wasteful sacrifice of life"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷雲",
      "answer": "らいうん,いかずちぐも",
      "meaning": "thunder cloud"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝宴",
      "answer": "しゅくえん",
      "meaning": "celebratory banquet, feast"
    },
    {
      "question": "兄弟姉妹",
      "answer": "きょうだいしまい",
      "meaning": "brothers and sisters, siblings"
    },
    {
      "question": "上役",
      "answer": "うわやく",
      "meaning": "one's superior, higher-up, boss, senior"
    },
    {
      "question": "革新的",
      "answer": "かくしんてき",
      "meaning": "innovative, liberal, reformist, progressive"
    },
    {
      "question": "未",
      "answer": "ひつじ,み",
      "meaning": "the Sheep (eighth sign of the Chinese zodiac), the Ram, the Goat, hour of the Sheep (around 2pm, 1-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "除霊",
      "answer": "じょれい",
      "meaning": "exorcism"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝く",
      "answer": "むく",
      "meaning": "to peel, to skin, to pare, to hull, to bare (e.g. fangs), to open wide (e.g. eyes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "組成",
      "answer": "そせい",
      "meaning": "composition, constitution"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷室",
      "answer": "こおりむろ,ひむろ,ひょうしつ",
      "meaning": "ice house, ice room, cold room"
    },
    {
      "question": "白鯨",
      "answer": "はくげい",
      "meaning": "white whale, Moby Dick"
    },
    {
      "question": "取締役",
      "answer": "とりしまりやく",
      "meaning": "company director, board member"
    },
    {
      "question": "土鍋",
      "answer": "どなべ,つちなべ",
      "meaning": "earthenware pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "伸び伸び",
      "answer": "のびのび",
      "meaning": "comfortably, peacefully, with one's mind at ease, calmly, without worries, (growing) quickly"
    },
    {
      "question": "町民",
      "answer": "ちょうみん",
      "meaning": "townspeople"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺留品",
      "answer": "いりゅうひん",
      "meaning": "lost articles"
    },
    {
      "question": "情が移る",
      "answer": "じょうがうつる",
      "meaning": "to become attached, to begin to love"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀しむ",
      "answer": "かなしむ",
      "meaning": "to be sad, to mourn for, to regret"
    },
    {
      "question": "漆喰",
      "answer": "しっくい",
      "meaning": "mortar, plaster, stucco"
    },
    {
      "question": "人当たり",
      "answer": "ひとあたり",
      "meaning": "one's manners, one's attitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "叙勲",
      "answer": "じょくん",
      "meaning": "conferring of decorations"
    },
    {
      "question": "純真無垢",
      "answer": "じゅんしんむく",
      "meaning": "pure, purity"
    },
    {
      "question": "胎",
      "answer": "たい,はら",
      "meaning": "womb"
    },
    {
      "question": "御殿",
      "answer": "ごてん",
      "meaning": "palace, court"
    },
    {
      "question": "結わえる",
      "answer": "ゆわえる",
      "meaning": "to bind, to fasten, to tie up"
    },
    {
      "question": "一族郎党",
      "answer": "いちぞくろうとう",
      "meaning": "one's family and followers, one's whole clan"
    },
    {
      "question": "埒",
      "answer": "らち,らっち",
      "meaning": "bounds, limits, boundary fence (esp. of horse-riding ground)"
    },
    {
      "question": "病原菌",
      "answer": "びょうげんきん",
      "meaning": "pathogenic bacteria, germ, pathogen"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭鉱",
      "answer": "たんこう",
      "meaning": "coal mine, coal pit"
    },
    {
      "question": "幹事",
      "answer": "かんじ",
      "meaning": "executive secretary, coordinator, organizer, person in charge of making arrangements"
    },
    {
      "question": "浸水",
      "answer": "しんすい",
      "meaning": "inundation, submersion, flood"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡り鳥",
      "answer": "わたりどり",
      "meaning": "migratory bird, bird of passage"
    },
    {
      "question": "新雪",
      "answer": "しんせつ",
      "meaning": "fresh snow, new snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "継母",
      "answer": "けいぼ,ままはは",
      "meaning": "stepmother"
    },
    {
      "question": "筆記試験",
      "answer": "ひっきしけん",
      "meaning": "written examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "虜囚",
      "answer": "りょしゅう",
      "meaning": "captive, prisoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "銃殺",
      "answer": "じゅうさつ",
      "meaning": "death by shooting"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡散",
      "answer": "うさん",
      "meaning": "suspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "一条",
      "answer": "いちじょう,ひとすじ",
      "meaning": "a line, a streak, a stripe, a ray (of light), a wisp (of smoke), one item (in an itemized form), one"
    },
    {
      "question": "群青色",
      "answer": "ぐんじょういろ",
      "meaning": "ultramarine colour (color)"
    },
    {
      "question": "他社",
      "answer": "たしゃ",
      "meaning": "another company, other company"
    },
    {
      "question": "無辜",
      "answer": "むこ",
      "meaning": "innocent, blameless, guiltless"
    },
    {
      "question": "波及",
      "answer": "はきゅう",
      "meaning": "spread, extension, influence, aftereffect, ripple"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯応え",
      "answer": "はごたえ",
      "meaning": "chewiness, firmness, feel of food while being chewed, challenge (e.g. work, book), toughness"
    },
    {
      "question": "被写体",
      "answer": "ひしゃたい",
      "meaning": "(photographic) subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "白ワイン",
      "answer": "しろワイン",
      "meaning": "white wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "人気投票",
      "answer": "にんきとうひょう",
      "meaning": "popularity contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷み",
      "answer": "いたみ",
      "meaning": "pain, ache, soreness, grief, distress, damage, injury, wear, bruise, break"
    },
    {
      "question": "生垣",
      "answer": "いけがき",
      "meaning": "hedge"
    },
    {
      "question": "底意地",
      "answer": "そこいじ",
      "meaning": "latent disposition, inner feelings"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼失",
      "answer": "しょうしつ",
      "meaning": "destruction by fire, losing in a fire, being burnt down"
    },
    {
      "question": "二色",
      "answer": "にしょく",
      "meaning": "two-color, two-colour, dichromatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "単価",
      "answer": "たんか",
      "meaning": "unit price, unit cost"
    },
    {
      "question": "拝聴",
      "answer": "はいちょう",
      "meaning": "listening respectfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "片刃",
      "answer": "かたば,かたは",
      "meaning": "single edge (e.g. sword blade)"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽織",
      "answer": "はおり",
      "meaning": "haori (Japanese formal coat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋭",
      "answer": "えい",
      "meaning": "sharpness, sharp weapon, blade, fine soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "早熟",
      "answer": "そうじゅく",
      "meaning": "precocity, early ripening, premature development"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち上げ",
      "answer": "たちあげ",
      "meaning": "starting up (e.g. business, computer)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気付け",
      "answer": "きづけ,きつけ",
      "meaning": "care of (e.g. address on letter), c/o, encouragement, bringing around, resuscitation, stimulant, ton"
    },
    {
      "question": "教典",
      "answer": "きょうてん",
      "meaning": "scriptures, canon, teaching guide"
    },
    {
      "question": "抑止",
      "answer": "よくし",
      "meaning": "check, checkmate, stave off, control, restraint, inhibit, deterrent, deterrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "可決",
      "answer": "かけつ",
      "meaning": "approval, adoption (of a motion, bill, etc.), passage"
    },
    {
      "question": "文集",
      "answer": "ぶんしゅう",
      "meaning": "anthology"
    },
    {
      "question": "次席",
      "answer": "じせき",
      "meaning": "associate, junior, assistant, runner-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "洞察",
      "answer": "どうさつ",
      "meaning": "discernment, insight"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨と皮",
      "answer": "ほねとかわ",
      "meaning": "skin and bones"
    },
    {
      "question": "編纂",
      "answer": "へんさん",
      "meaning": "compilation (esp. dictionary, history, law code), editing"
    },
    {
      "question": "故国",
      "answer": "ここく",
      "meaning": "one's native land"
    },
    {
      "question": "一巡",
      "answer": "いちじゅん",
      "meaning": "beat, round"
    },
    {
      "question": "人口密度",
      "answer": "じんこうみつど",
      "meaning": "population density"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽天的",
      "answer": "らくてんてき",
      "meaning": "optimistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "両替",
      "answer": "りょうがえ",
      "meaning": "change, money exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "有言実行",
      "answer": "ゆうげんじっこう",
      "meaning": "carrying out one's words, being as good as one's word, making good on one's promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "天子",
      "answer": "てんし",
      "meaning": "emperor, ruler (with a heavenly mandate), heavenly being, celestial being"
    },
    {
      "question": "小太刀",
      "answer": "こだち",
      "meaning": "short sword, small sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲海",
      "answer": "うんかい",
      "meaning": "sea of clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "未解決",
      "answer": "みかいけつ",
      "meaning": "unsettled, pending, unresolved"
    },
    {
      "question": "第一線",
      "answer": "だいいっせん",
      "meaning": "the front (of a battlefield), forefront"
    },
    {
      "question": "死す",
      "answer": "しす",
      "meaning": "to die"
    },
    {
      "question": "副将",
      "answer": "ふくしょう",
      "meaning": "second in command (of an army), vice-captain, fourth athlete to compete in a 5-on-5 team competition"
    },
    {
      "question": "風鈴",
      "answer": "ふうりん",
      "meaning": "wind chime, wind bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝がす",
      "answer": "はがす,へがす",
      "meaning": "to tear off, to peel off, to rip off, to strip off, to skin, to flay, to disrobe, to deprive of, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥類",
      "answer": "ちょうるい",
      "meaning": "birds"
    },
    {
      "question": "頸",
      "answer": "くび",
      "meaning": "neck, head, dismissal, discharge, firing (from a job)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番弟子",
      "answer": "いちばんでし",
      "meaning": "the (one's) best pupil, the (one's) top disciple"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂れ幕",
      "answer": "たれまく",
      "meaning": "hanging banner, hanging screen, curtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "啄む",
      "answer": "ついばむ",
      "meaning": "to pick at, to peck at"
    },
    {
      "question": "憂き目",
      "answer": "うきめ",
      "meaning": "bitter experience, misery, distress, grief, sad thoughts, hardship"
    },
    {
      "question": "贔屓目",
      "answer": "ひいきめ",
      "meaning": "seeing things in a favourable light (favorable)"
    },
    {
      "question": "土塊",
      "answer": "つちくれ,どかい",
      "meaning": "lump of earth, clod"
    },
    {
      "question": "出国",
      "answer": "しゅっこく,しゅつごく",
      "meaning": "departure from a country"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘辛い",
      "answer": "あまからい",
      "meaning": "salty-sweet"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫舌",
      "answer": "ねこじた",
      "meaning": "dislike of very hot food or drink, inability to take hot food, cat tongue"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫陽花",
      "answer": "あじさい",
      "meaning": "bigleaf hydrangea (Hydrangea macrophylla), French hydrangea"
    },
    {
      "question": "論法",
      "answer": "ろんぽう",
      "meaning": "logic, reasoning, argument, line of argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己中",
      "answer": "じこちゅう",
      "meaning": "selfishness, egotism, egoism, egocentricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜ばす",
      "answer": "よろこばす",
      "meaning": "to delight, to give pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "麾下",
      "answer": "きか",
      "meaning": "under the command (of), under the banner (of), influenced (by)"
    },
    {
      "question": "手折る",
      "answer": "たおる",
      "meaning": "to break by hand (e.g. a flower), to break off (a twig), to pluck (a flower, a bud), to make a young"
    },
    {
      "question": "三河",
      "answer": "みかわ",
      "meaning": "Mikawa (former province located in the east of present-day Aichi Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶屋",
      "answer": "ちゃや",
      "meaning": "teahouse, (Edo period) rest stop, (geisha) teahouse, establishment where patrons are entertained by"
    },
    {
      "question": "右舷",
      "answer": "うげん",
      "meaning": "starboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "気色ばむ",
      "answer": "けしきばむ",
      "meaning": "to grow angry, to display one's anger"
    },
    {
      "question": "修道士",
      "answer": "しゅうどうし",
      "meaning": "monk, friar"
    },
    {
      "question": "不衛生",
      "answer": "ふえいせい",
      "meaning": "unsanitary condition, lack of hygienic care, inattention to hygiene, unhygienic conditions"
    },
    {
      "question": "投函",
      "answer": "とうかん",
      "meaning": "mailing, posting"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦穴",
      "answer": "たてあな",
      "meaning": "pit, shaft"
    },
    {
      "question": "懲役",
      "answer": "ちょうえき",
      "meaning": "penal servitude, imprisonment with hard labor (hard labour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "即戦力",
      "answer": "そくせんりょく",
      "meaning": "ready fire-power, battle-ready forces, immediate asset (to a team or firm), someone who can be an im"
    },
    {
      "question": "不実",
      "answer": "ふじつ",
      "meaning": "perfidiousness, faithlessness, inconstancy, insincerity, falsehood"
    },
    {
      "question": "民草",
      "answer": "たみくさ,たみぐさ",
      "meaning": "people, populace"
    },
    {
      "question": "充足",
      "answer": "じゅうそく",
      "meaning": "sufficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵将",
      "answer": "てきしょう",
      "meaning": "enemy general"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒液",
      "answer": "どくえき",
      "meaning": "venom"
    },
    {
      "question": "落選",
      "answer": "らくせん",
      "meaning": "election loss, rejection"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛",
      "answer": "かけ,がけ,がかり",
      "meaning": "credit, money owed on an account, bill, hot noodles in broth, proportion (of wholesale price, as ten"
    },
    {
      "question": "液状",
      "answer": "えきじょう",
      "meaning": "liquid state"
    },
    {
      "question": "化学反応",
      "answer": "かがくはんのう",
      "meaning": "chemical reaction, generation of an unexpected result from combining things"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕僚",
      "answer": "ばくりょう",
      "meaning": "staff, staff officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "席替え",
      "answer": "せきがえ",
      "meaning": "moving to new seats, moving to new desks"
    },
    {
      "question": "満更",
      "answer": "まんざら",
      "meaning": "(not) altogether, (not) wholly"
    },
    {
      "question": "割方",
      "answer": "わりかた",
      "meaning": "comparatively, quite, rather, rate, ratio, percentage, proportion"
    },
    {
      "question": "特殊効果",
      "answer": "とくしゅこうか",
      "meaning": "special effects"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬小屋",
      "answer": "いぬごや",
      "meaning": "kennel, dog house"
    },
    {
      "question": "集客",
      "answer": "しゅうきゃく",
      "meaning": "attracting customers"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘する",
      "answer": "ひする",
      "meaning": "to keep secret, to conceal"
    },
    {
      "question": "桃源郷",
      "answer": "とうげんきょう",
      "meaning": "earthly paradise, Shangri-la"
    },
    {
      "question": "狭",
      "answer": "せ,さ",
      "meaning": "narrowness, being cramped, being almost full, narrow, thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "力負け",
      "answer": "ちからまけ",
      "meaning": "losing by being overmatched, being defeated by a stronger opponent, losing by misusing one's powers,"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦慮",
      "answer": "くりょ",
      "meaning": "racking one's brains, worrying oneself, being anxious"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡洋艦",
      "answer": "じゅんようかん",
      "meaning": "cruiser"
    },
    {
      "question": "刊",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "publication, edition (e.g. morning, evening, special), published in (year), publication frequency (e"
    },
    {
      "question": "代謝",
      "answer": "たいしゃ",
      "meaning": "metabolism, renewal, regeneration, replacing the old with the new"
    },
    {
      "question": "全霊",
      "answer": "ぜんれい",
      "meaning": "one's whole soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛り付け",
      "answer": "もりつけ",
      "meaning": "arrangement of food (on a dish), serving of (arranged) food"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖を取る",
      "answer": "だんをとる",
      "meaning": "to warm oneself (e.g. at a fire)"
    },
    {
      "question": "翌々日",
      "answer": "よくよくじつ",
      "meaning": "two days later, day after next, next day but one"
    },
    {
      "question": "心機一転",
      "answer": "しんきいってん",
      "meaning": "changing one's attitude, turning over a new leaf, getting a fresh start"
    },
    {
      "question": "発芽",
      "answer": "はつが",
      "meaning": "germination, sprouting, budding"
    },
    {
      "question": "違くない",
      "answer": "ちがくない",
      "meaning": "isn't it (that) different (from usual, from what one could expect, etc.)?, isn't that wrong?, no, th"
    },
    {
      "question": "滝壺",
      "answer": "たきつぼ",
      "meaning": "plunge basin, waterfall lake, plunge pool, basin under a waterfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "火鉢",
      "answer": "ひばち",
      "meaning": "brazier, hibachi"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴君",
      "answer": "きくん",
      "meaning": "you (primarily used by men in letters to their equals or inferiors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "建",
      "answer": "たて,たける",
      "meaning": "contract, commitment, leader of a fearless tribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "核兵器",
      "answer": "かくへいき",
      "meaning": "nuclear weapon"
    },
    {
      "question": "心拍",
      "answer": "しんぱく",
      "meaning": "heartbeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "情愛",
      "answer": "じょうあい",
      "meaning": "affection, love"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬鹿騒ぎ",
      "answer": "ばかさわぎ",
      "meaning": "horseplay, fooling around"
    },
    {
      "question": "一銭",
      "answer": "いっせん",
      "meaning": "one sen, one-hundredth of a yen, small amount of money"
    },
    {
      "question": "世の常",
      "answer": "よのつね",
      "meaning": "ordinary, run-of-the-mill, usual"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮魂",
      "answer": "ちんこん,たましずめ",
      "meaning": "repose of a soul, ceremony for the repose of a departed soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "吠え声",
      "answer": "ほえごえ",
      "meaning": "bark, howl, roar, bellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "多数派",
      "answer": "たすうは",
      "meaning": "majority group (party, faction)"
    },
    {
      "question": "用立てる",
      "answer": "ようだてる",
      "meaning": "to make use of, to lend money"
    },
    {
      "question": "発電機",
      "answer": "はつでんき",
      "meaning": "dynamo, power generator"
    },
    {
      "question": "優る",
      "answer": "まさる",
      "meaning": "to excel, to surpass, to exceed, to have an edge, to be superior, to outrival, to outweigh, to prepo"
    },
    {
      "question": "円錐",
      "answer": "えんすい,まるぎり",
      "meaning": "cone, round gimlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒宴",
      "answer": "しゅえん",
      "meaning": "drinking party, banquet, feast"
    },
    {
      "question": "空戦",
      "answer": "くうせん",
      "meaning": "air battle, dogfight"
    },
    {
      "question": "判",
      "answer": "はん,ばん",
      "meaning": "seal, stamp, monogram signature, judgment, judgement, size (of paper or books)"
    },
    {
      "question": "球技",
      "answer": "きゅうぎ",
      "meaning": "ball game (e.g. baseball, tennis, soccer)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合わせ技",
      "answer": "あわせわざ",
      "meaning": "combination technique in Judo"
    },
    {
      "question": "茫洋",
      "answer": "ぼうよう",
      "meaning": "vast, limitless, boundless"
    },
    {
      "question": "智慧",
      "answer": "ちえ",
      "meaning": "wisdom, wit, sagacity, sense, intelligence, prajna (insight leading to enlightenment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青い鳥",
      "answer": "あおいとり",
      "meaning": "bluebird of happiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "挙式",
      "answer": "きょしき",
      "meaning": "holding a ceremony, wedding ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "不況",
      "answer": "ふきょう",
      "meaning": "depression, recession, slump"
    },
    {
      "question": "垢抜ける",
      "answer": "あかぬける",
      "meaning": "to be refined, to be polished, to be stylish, to be sophisticated"
    },
    {
      "question": "無欲",
      "answer": "むよく",
      "meaning": "unselfish, disinterested, unavaricious, free of avarice"
    },
    {
      "question": "出発点",
      "answer": "しゅっぱつてん",
      "meaning": "starting point, point of departure"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚弱",
      "answer": "きょじゃく",
      "meaning": "feebleness, weakness, imbecility"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲恋",
      "answer": "ひれん",
      "meaning": "blighted love, disappointed love"
    },
    {
      "question": "初頭",
      "answer": "しょとう",
      "meaning": "beginning (of a century, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞す",
      "answer": "じす",
      "meaning": "to excuse oneself, to take one's leave, to quit, to resign, to retire, to leave post, to decline, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "波に乗る",
      "answer": "なみにのる",
      "meaning": "to go with the flow, to go with the times"
    },
    {
      "question": "神奈川",
      "answer": "かながわ",
      "meaning": "Kanagawa (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が無い",
      "answer": "きがない",
      "meaning": "not feeling like doing ..., having no mind to ..., being in no mood for ..., having no intention of"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄青",
      "answer": "うすあお",
      "meaning": "light blue, pale blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "尽く",
      "answer": "ことごとく,ずく,づく",
      "meaning": "altogether, entirely, relying entirely on ..., using solely ..., with the sole purpose of ..., based"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き直す",
      "answer": "たたきなおす",
      "meaning": "to beat into shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "県警",
      "answer": "けんけい",
      "meaning": "prefectural police"
    },
    {
      "question": "勾配",
      "answer": "こうばい",
      "meaning": "slope, incline, gradient, grade, pitch, slope (of a linear function), gradient (vector calculus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫製",
      "answer": "ほうせい",
      "meaning": "sewing (by machine)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誂える",
      "answer": "あつらえる",
      "meaning": "to give an order, to place an order, to have made to order"
    },
    {
      "question": "便宜",
      "answer": "べんぎ,びんぎ",
      "meaning": "convenience, accommodation, advantage, benefit, expediency"
    },
    {
      "question": "彫り",
      "answer": "ほり,えり",
      "meaning": "carving, engraving, chiselled features"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪遊",
      "answer": "ごうゆう",
      "meaning": "extravagant spree, wild merrymaking, living it up"
    },
    {
      "question": "剝がれる",
      "answer": "はがれる",
      "meaning": "to come unstuck from, to peel off, to come off"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖簾",
      "answer": "のれん,のうれん,のんれん",
      "meaning": "(short) curtain hung at shop entrance, split curtain used to divide spaces in a house, reputation (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "売れ残り",
      "answer": "うれのこり",
      "meaning": "unsold items, leftovers, remainders, remnants, spinster, old maid"
    },
    {
      "question": "商事",
      "answer": "しょうじ",
      "meaning": "commercial affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "慄然",
      "answer": "りつぜん",
      "meaning": "terrified, horrified"
    },
    {
      "question": "人道",
      "answer": "じんどう,にんどう",
      "meaning": "humanity, sidewalk, footpath, human realm"
    },
    {
      "question": "生年月日",
      "answer": "せいねんがっぴ",
      "meaning": "birth date, date of birth, DOB"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き切る",
      "answer": "たたききる",
      "meaning": "to hack, to chop (firewood, meat, etc.), to chop off (e.g. a head)"
    },
    {
      "question": "高説",
      "answer": "こうせつ",
      "meaning": "your opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯曲",
      "answer": "ぎきょく",
      "meaning": "drama, play, Chinese opera"
    },
    {
      "question": "道草",
      "answer": "みちくさ",
      "meaning": "loitering on the way, wayside grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き足す",
      "answer": "かきたす",
      "meaning": "to add to, to insert"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖樹",
      "answer": "せいじゅ",
      "meaning": "holy tree, sacred tree, Christmas tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "質屋",
      "answer": "しちや",
      "meaning": "pawnshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼び掛け",
      "answer": "よびかけ",
      "meaning": "call, appeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "後手",
      "answer": "ごて",
      "meaning": "losing initiative, being forestalled, second move (in go or shogi), moving second, person with the s"
    },
    {
      "question": "再来週",
      "answer": "さらいしゅう",
      "meaning": "week after next"
    },
    {
      "question": "大都会",
      "answer": "だいとかい",
      "meaning": "metropolis, big city"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊撃隊",
      "answer": "ゆうげきたい",
      "meaning": "commando unit"
    },
    {
      "question": "都市国家",
      "answer": "としこっか",
      "meaning": "city-state"
    },
    {
      "question": "左舷",
      "answer": "さげん",
      "meaning": "port (left side of vessel)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熾す",
      "answer": "おこす",
      "meaning": "to build (a fire), to make, to start, to light"
    },
    {
      "question": "在り処",
      "answer": "ありか",
      "meaning": "location (of something), whereabouts, hiding place"
    },
    {
      "question": "信心",
      "answer": "しんじん",
      "meaning": "faith, belief, piety, devotion, godliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "変わり種",
      "answer": "かわりだね",
      "meaning": "something out of the ordinary, variant, variety, exception, novelty, person with an unusual characte"
    },
    {
      "question": "商売敵",
      "answer": "しょうばいがたき",
      "meaning": "business rival, professional jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "局地的",
      "answer": "きょくちてき",
      "meaning": "local (rain, distribution, outbreak, etc.), localized, regional, isolated"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛ばし",
      "answer": "とばし",
      "meaning": "selling or divesting in unwanted stocks, hiding bad loans"
    },
    {
      "question": "人形劇",
      "answer": "にんぎょうげき",
      "meaning": "puppet show"
    },
    {
      "question": "出し抜け",
      "answer": "だしぬけ",
      "meaning": "all of a sudden, unexpected, abrupt, sudden"
    },
    {
      "question": "訥々",
      "answer": "とつとつ",
      "meaning": "halting (speech), faltering, stammering"
    },
    {
      "question": "天体観測",
      "answer": "てんたいかんそく",
      "meaning": "astronomical observation, stargazing"
    },
    {
      "question": "逢い引き",
      "answer": "あいびき",
      "meaning": "(secret) date, clandestine meeting, assignation, tryst, rendezvous"
    },
    {
      "question": "読破",
      "answer": "どくは",
      "meaning": "reading through (a book), finishing (a book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "多感",
      "answer": "たかん",
      "meaning": "sensitive, susceptible, emotional, impressionable, sentimental"
    },
    {
      "question": "厩",
      "answer": "うまや",
      "meaning": "stable, barn"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇人",
      "answer": "きじん",
      "meaning": "queer fellow, odd fellow, eccentric person, crank, oddball, freak"
    },
    {
      "question": "休み休み",
      "answer": "やすみやすみ",
      "meaning": "resting at times, with careful thought, after proper consideration"
    },
    {
      "question": "玄武",
      "answer": "げんぶ,げんむ",
      "meaning": "Black Tortoise (god said to rule over the northern heavens), seven mansions (Chinese constellations)"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠",
      "answer": "ちゅう",
      "meaning": "loyalty, devotion, fidelity, faithfulness, inspector of the Imperial Prosecuting and Investigating O"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷然",
      "answer": "れいぜん",
      "meaning": "indifference, coolness, lukewarmness, cold-heartedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰巾着",
      "answer": "こしぎんちゃく",
      "meaning": "hanger-on, follower, flunky, sycophant, purse strapped round one's waist"
    },
    {
      "question": "男色",
      "answer": "だんしょく,なんしょく",
      "meaning": "male homosexuality, sodomy, male prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "予備軍",
      "answer": "よびぐん",
      "meaning": "reserves (esp. troops), reserve army, potential members of some group (e.g. the elderly), people at"
    },
    {
      "question": "進退",
      "answer": "しんたい,しんだい",
      "meaning": "advance or retreat, moving forwards or backwards, movement, course of action, behaviour, conduct, at"
    },
    {
      "question": "無実の罪",
      "answer": "むじつのつみ",
      "meaning": "false charge"
    },
    {
      "question": "見覚える",
      "answer": "みおぼえる",
      "meaning": "to remember, to recollect, to recognize, to recognise"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮袋",
      "answer": "かわぶくろ",
      "meaning": "leather bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪国",
      "answer": "ゆきぐに",
      "meaning": "snow country"
    },
    {
      "question": "秤",
      "answer": "はかり",
      "meaning": "scales, weighing machine"
    },
    {
      "question": "庇",
      "answer": "ひさし",
      "meaning": "awning (over window, doorway), eaves (of roof), narrow aisle surrounding the core of a temple buildi"
    },
    {
      "question": "色目",
      "answer": "いろめ",
      "meaning": "amorous glance, leer, ogle, shade (of color), tint, hue, ingratiation, sycophancy, toadying"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬り倒す",
      "answer": "きりたおす",
      "meaning": "to cut down, to chop down, to fell"
    },
    {
      "question": "横っ飛び",
      "answer": "よこっとび",
      "meaning": "jumping sideways, flying sideways, running hurriedly (with one's body bent forward)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下書き",
      "answer": "したがき",
      "meaning": "draft, rough copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "実父",
      "answer": "じっぷ",
      "meaning": "one's real father, natural father, biological father"
    },
    {
      "question": "倍返し",
      "answer": "ばいがえし",
      "meaning": "payment of a sum twice the original, giving back a gift double the value of the one received, repayi"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち合う",
      "answer": "たちあう",
      "meaning": "to be matched against (in a sports contest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "単身赴任",
      "answer": "たんしんふにん",
      "meaning": "job transfer away from one's home, taking up a new post leaving one's family behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓮",
      "answer": "はす,はちす",
      "meaning": "sacred lotus (Nelumbo nucifera), Indian lotus, lotus, rose of Sharon (Hibiscus syriacus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "独楽",
      "answer": "こま",
      "meaning": "spinning top"
    },
    {
      "question": "壁掛け",
      "answer": "かべかけ",
      "meaning": "wall-mounted ornament, wall decoration, wall hanging, wall-mounted"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧歌的",
      "answer": "ぼっかてき",
      "meaning": "pastoral, idyllic"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い扶持",
      "answer": "くいぶち",
      "meaning": "cost of one's food, one's board"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒精",
      "answer": "しゅせい",
      "meaning": "(ethyl) alcohol, spirits of wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "哲学者",
      "answer": "てつがくしゃ",
      "meaning": "philosopher"
    },
    {
      "question": "微々",
      "answer": "びび",
      "meaning": "slight, insignificant, small"
    },
    {
      "question": "山城",
      "answer": "やまじろ,さんじょう,やましろ",
      "meaning": "mountain castle, Yamashiro (former province located in the south of present-day Kyoto Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘲弄",
      "answer": "ちょうろう",
      "meaning": "scorn, mockery, ridicule"
    },
    {
      "question": "算術",
      "answer": "さんじゅつ",
      "meaning": "arithmetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷山",
      "answer": "ひょうざん",
      "meaning": "iceberg"
    },
    {
      "question": "時報",
      "answer": "じほう",
      "meaning": "announcement of time, time signal, news report, newsletter"
    },
    {
      "question": "気化",
      "answer": "きか",
      "meaning": "vaporization, vaporisation, evaporation"
    },
    {
      "question": "炒め物",
      "answer": "いためもの",
      "meaning": "stir-fry, fried food (cooked in wok, frying pan, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生娘",
      "answer": "きむすめ",
      "meaning": "virgin, innocent young woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "県内",
      "answer": "けんない",
      "meaning": "within the prefecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "大宮",
      "answer": "おおみや",
      "meaning": "imperial palace, shrine, Grand Empress Dowager, Empress Dowager, woman of imperial lineage who has b"
    },
    {
      "question": "守護霊",
      "answer": "しゅごれい",
      "meaning": "guardian spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "崩し",
      "answer": "くずし",
      "meaning": "simplification (character, hair-style, etc.), unbalancing an opponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "査問",
      "answer": "さもん",
      "meaning": "inquiry, enquiry, hearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "微小",
      "answer": "びしょう",
      "meaning": "microscopic"
    },
    {
      "question": "好々爺",
      "answer": "こうこうや",
      "meaning": "good-natured old man"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳正",
      "answer": "げんせい",
      "meaning": "strict, rigid, exact, fair, impartial"
    },
    {
      "question": "下士官",
      "answer": "かしかん",
      "meaning": "non-commissioned officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "防寒具",
      "answer": "ぼうかんぐ",
      "meaning": "heavy outfit designed to keep out the cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き換え",
      "answer": "かきかえ",
      "meaning": "rewriting (book), renewal, transfer of ownership"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚水",
      "answer": "おすい",
      "meaning": "filthy water, sewage"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が事",
      "answer": "わがこと",
      "meaning": "personal affair, one's own affair"
    },
    {
      "question": "外骨格",
      "answer": "がいこっかく",
      "meaning": "exoskeleton"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り手",
      "answer": "のりて",
      "meaning": "passenger, rider, good rider"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き返す",
      "answer": "まきかえす",
      "meaning": "to rally, to regain one's strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "世界大戦",
      "answer": "せかいたいせん",
      "meaning": "the World War"
    },
    {
      "question": "本書",
      "answer": "ほんしょ",
      "meaning": "text, script, this book"
    },
    {
      "question": "左利き",
      "answer": "ひだりきき",
      "meaning": "left-handedness, left-handed person, left-hander, fondness for alcohol, person who is fond of alcoho"
    },
    {
      "question": "妄信",
      "answer": "ぼうしん,もうしん",
      "meaning": "blind acceptance, blind belief, credulity"
    },
    {
      "question": "三脚",
      "answer": "さんきゃく",
      "meaning": "tripod, three legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "親元",
      "answer": "おやもと",
      "meaning": "one's parents' home"
    },
    {
      "question": "旗色",
      "answer": "はたいろ,きしょく",
      "meaning": "situation, outlook, one's allegiance, affiliation, position"
    },
    {
      "question": "越前",
      "answer": "えちぜん",
      "meaning": "Echizen (former province located in parts of present-day Fukui and Gifu prefectures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自走",
      "answer": "じそう",
      "meaning": "self-propulsion"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚弟",
      "answer": "ぐてい",
      "meaning": "younger brother, stupid younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "手斧",
      "answer": "ておの,ちょうな",
      "meaning": "hatchet, adze, adz"
    },
    {
      "question": "配管",
      "answer": "はいかん",
      "meaning": "plumbing, piping"
    },
    {
      "question": "堰",
      "answer": "せき,いせき,い",
      "meaning": "dam, weir, barrier, sluice"
    },
    {
      "question": "役柄",
      "answer": "やくがら",
      "meaning": "role"
    },
    {
      "question": "柳眉",
      "answer": "りゅうび",
      "meaning": "beautiful eyebrows"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅装",
      "answer": "りょそう",
      "meaning": "travelling clothes, traveling clothes, travelling outfit, traveling outfit"
    },
    {
      "question": "鋭角",
      "answer": "えいかく",
      "meaning": "acute angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭水化物",
      "answer": "たんすいかぶつ",
      "meaning": "carbohydrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "訃報",
      "answer": "ふほう",
      "meaning": "news of someone's death, obituary"
    },
    {
      "question": "気道",
      "answer": "きどう",
      "meaning": "respiratory tract, air duct"
    },
    {
      "question": "土地柄",
      "answer": "とちがら",
      "meaning": "nature of the locality, character of a place, local colour, local color"
    },
    {
      "question": "再出発",
      "answer": "さいしゅっぱつ",
      "meaning": "restart, fresh start"
    },
    {
      "question": "天道",
      "answer": "てんとう,てんどう,あまじ",
      "meaning": "the sun, god of heaven and the earth, laws governing the heavens, celestial path, celestial motion,"
    },
    {
      "question": "水戸",
      "answer": "みと",
      "meaning": "Mito (city in Ibaraki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "長崎",
      "answer": "ながさき",
      "meaning": "Nagasaki (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "両刃",
      "answer": "もろは,りょうば",
      "meaning": "double-edged, double-edged blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "保健体育",
      "answer": "ほけんたいいく",
      "meaning": "health and physical education"
    },
    {
      "question": "等価交換",
      "answer": "とうかこうかん",
      "meaning": "fair exchange, equivalent exchange, exchange of equal value"
    },
    {
      "question": "赦し",
      "answer": "ゆるし",
      "meaning": "pardon, forgiveness, exemption, permission"
    },
    {
      "question": "庭木",
      "answer": "にわき",
      "meaning": "garden tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄る辺",
      "answer": "よるべ",
      "meaning": "place to go, person to turn to or depend on, one's resort"
    },
    {
      "question": "毟る",
      "answer": "むしる",
      "meaning": "to pluck, to pick, to tear"
    },
    {
      "question": "譲り渡す",
      "answer": "ゆずりわたす",
      "meaning": "to hand over, to turn over, to cede"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮足立つ",
      "answer": "うきあしだつ",
      "meaning": "to be prepared to flee, to become restless, to become agitated"
    },
    {
      "question": "予定日",
      "answer": "よていび",
      "meaning": "scheduled date, expected date, due date, estimated date of confinement, expected date of delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "窟",
      "answer": "いわや,やぐら",
      "meaning": "cavern, grotto, caves dug as tombs in and around Kamakura during the Kamakura and Muromachi periods"
    },
    {
      "question": "非ず",
      "answer": "あらず",
      "meaning": "it is not so, no, never mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "若返り",
      "answer": "わかがえり",
      "meaning": "rejuvenation, restoration of youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "酌",
      "answer": "しゃく",
      "meaning": "pouring alcohol, person pouring alcohol (esp. a woman)"
    },
    {
      "question": "時限",
      "answer": "じげん",
      "meaning": "(school) period, period or division of time, time limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "則",
      "answer": "そく",
      "meaning": "counter for rules, rule, regulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬車馬",
      "answer": "ばしゃうま",
      "meaning": "cart-horse, work-horse, doing something wholeheartedly, doing with one's undivided attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "比肩",
      "answer": "ひけん",
      "meaning": "ranking equal with, comparing favourably with, comparing favorably with"
    },
    {
      "question": "一思いに",
      "answer": "ひとおもいに",
      "meaning": "instantly, resolutely"
    },
    {
      "question": "北門",
      "answer": "きたもん,ほくもん",
      "meaning": "north gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘露",
      "answer": "かんろ",
      "meaning": "nectar, sweetness"
    },
    {
      "question": "猟奇的",
      "answer": "りょうきてき",
      "meaning": "curiosity-seeking, bizarre (crime, etc.), grotesque, abnormal"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬莢",
      "answer": "やっきょう",
      "meaning": "(ammunition) cartridge, shell case"
    },
    {
      "question": "定休日",
      "answer": "ていきゅうび",
      "meaning": "regular holiday, fixed day off, regular closing day"
    },
    {
      "question": "致死量",
      "answer": "ちしりょう",
      "meaning": "lethal dose"
    },
    {
      "question": "風景画",
      "answer": "ふうけいが",
      "meaning": "landscape painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "通院",
      "answer": "つういん",
      "meaning": "going to the hospital for regular treatment"
    },
    {
      "question": "迎合",
      "answer": "げいごう,あど",
      "meaning": "ingratiation, pandering, catering (to), going along with (someone or something), accommodating onese"
    },
    {
      "question": "今風",
      "answer": "いまふう",
      "meaning": "modern, current, contemporary, trendy, latest, up-to-date"
    },
    {
      "question": "足掛かり",
      "answer": "あしがかり",
      "meaning": "foothold, footing, toehold, stepping stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵩",
      "answer": "かさ",
      "meaning": "bulk, volume, quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "惨憺",
      "answer": "さんたん",
      "meaning": "miserable, pitiful, tragic, wretched, horrible, terrible, painstaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "門外不出",
      "answer": "もんがいふしゅつ",
      "meaning": "(treasuring something by) never taking (it) off the premises"
    },
    {
      "question": "相似",
      "answer": "そうじ",
      "meaning": "resemblance, likeness, similitude, similarity, analogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝祭",
      "answer": "しゅくさい",
      "meaning": "festivals, feasts"
    },
    {
      "question": "決め台詞",
      "answer": "きめぜりふ",
      "meaning": "signature phrase, signature saying"
    },
    {
      "question": "運気",
      "answer": "うんき",
      "meaning": "fate, fortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "破壊者",
      "answer": "はかいしゃ",
      "meaning": "destroyer"
    },
    {
      "question": "往診",
      "answer": "おうしん",
      "meaning": "doctor's visit, house call"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚泥",
      "answer": "おでい",
      "meaning": "sludge, slime, dregs, mire, hopeless situation, hell, despair"
    },
    {
      "question": "辻",
      "answer": "つじ",
      "meaning": "intersection, crossing, crossroad, street corner, street"
    },
    {
      "question": "名将",
      "answer": "めいしょう",
      "meaning": "great commander, famous commander"
    },
    {
      "question": "求心力",
      "answer": "きゅうしんりょく",
      "meaning": "centripetal force, unifying force, cohesive power"
    },
    {
      "question": "伍長",
      "answer": "ごちょう",
      "meaning": "corporal"
    },
    {
      "question": "成功報酬",
      "answer": "せいこうほうしゅう",
      "meaning": "fee contingent upon success, contingency fee, completion bonus"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴族院",
      "answer": "きぞくいん",
      "meaning": "House of Peers (Japan, Meiji constitution), House of Lords (UK)"
    },
    {
      "question": "林道",
      "answer": "りんどう",
      "meaning": "path through forest, woodland path, logging road"
    },
    {
      "question": "卒",
      "answer": "そつ",
      "meaning": "low-ranking soldier, graduation, outgrowing, moving on (from), low-ranking samurai (1870-1872), deat"
    },
    {
      "question": "縞",
      "answer": "しま",
      "meaning": "stripe, bar, streak, (weaved) stripe pattern (of 2 or more different colors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "プロ野球",
      "answer": "プロやきゅう",
      "meaning": "professional baseball"
    },
    {
      "question": "国賓",
      "answer": "こくひん",
      "meaning": "state guest"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒くれ",
      "answer": "あらくれ",
      "meaning": "rough, rowdy, wild, violent, rough person, rowdy person"
    },
    {
      "question": "詮",
      "answer": "かい,せん",
      "meaning": "effect, result, worth, use, avail, Kai (former province located in present-day Yamanashi Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死亡率",
      "answer": "しぼうりつ",
      "meaning": "death rate, mortality rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "時半",
      "answer": "じはん,ときなか",
      "meaning": "half past (the hour), one hour"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺殺",
      "answer": "しさつ",
      "meaning": "stabbing to death, putting out"
    },
    {
      "question": "不人気",
      "answer": "ふにんき",
      "meaning": "unpopular"
    },
    {
      "question": "投手",
      "answer": "とうしゅ",
      "meaning": "pitcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "親馬鹿",
      "answer": "おやばか",
      "meaning": "over-fond parent, doting parent"
    },
    {
      "question": "どや顔",
      "answer": "どやがお",
      "meaning": "self-satisfied look, triumphant look, smug face, shit-eating grin"
    },
    {
      "question": "業腹",
      "answer": "ごうはら",
      "meaning": "spite, resentment"
    },
    {
      "question": "空々しい",
      "answer": "そらぞらしい",
      "meaning": "false, hypocritical"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲隠れ",
      "answer": "くもがくれ",
      "meaning": "vanishing behind the clouds (e.g. of the moon), vanishing, suddenly disappearing, going into hiding"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁気",
      "answer": "じき",
      "meaning": "magnetism"
    },
    {
      "question": "人死に",
      "answer": "ひとじに",
      "meaning": "accidental death, casualty"
    },
    {
      "question": "一発勝負",
      "answer": "いっぱつしょうぶ",
      "meaning": "contest decided by a single round (bout), contest decided by a single roll of dice, one-shot game (c"
    },
    {
      "question": "染み出る",
      "answer": "しみでる",
      "meaning": "to ooze, to exude, to percolate, to soak through"
    },
    {
      "question": "振舞い",
      "answer": "ふるまい",
      "meaning": "behavior, behaviour, conduct, entertainment, treat, feast, banquet"
    },
    {
      "question": "御馳走",
      "answer": "ごちそう",
      "meaning": "feast, treating (someone), to treat (someone, e.g. to a meal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自死",
      "answer": "じし",
      "meaning": "suicide, apoptosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "気風",
      "answer": "きふう,きっぷ",
      "meaning": "character, traits, ethos, disposition, spirit, temperament"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄養素",
      "answer": "えいようそ",
      "meaning": "nutrient"
    },
    {
      "question": "近海",
      "answer": "きんかい",
      "meaning": "coastal waters, adjacent seas"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭司",
      "answer": "さいし",
      "meaning": "priest"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇降機",
      "answer": "しょうこうき",
      "meaning": "elevator"
    },
    {
      "question": "万雷",
      "answer": "ばんらい",
      "meaning": "heavy thunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "表わす",
      "answer": "あらわす",
      "meaning": "to represent, to signify, to stand for, to reveal, to show, to display, to express, to make widely k"
    },
    {
      "question": "美姫",
      "answer": "びき",
      "meaning": "beautiful maiden, beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "捻れる",
      "answer": "ねじれる",
      "meaning": "to get twisted, to get crooked, to get warped, to become twisted (of a mind, relationship, etc.), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗顔",
      "answer": "せんがん",
      "meaning": "face-washing"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅知恵",
      "answer": "あさぢえ",
      "meaning": "shallow thinking, shallow wit"
    },
    {
      "question": "易しい",
      "answer": "やさしい",
      "meaning": "easy, plain, simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "義勇兵",
      "answer": "ぎゆうへい",
      "meaning": "volunteer soldier"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚れ薬",
      "answer": "ほれぐすり",
      "meaning": "love potion, philter, aphrodisiac"
    },
    {
      "question": "林立",
      "answer": "りんりつ",
      "meaning": "standing close together, bristling (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "参謀本部",
      "answer": "さんぼうほんぶ",
      "meaning": "General Staff Headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "長針",
      "answer": "ちょうしん",
      "meaning": "long hand, minute hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "足手纏い",
      "answer": "あしでまとい,あしてまとい",
      "meaning": "impediment, burden, encumbrance, hindrance, drag"
    },
    {
      "question": "秀麗",
      "answer": "しゅうれい",
      "meaning": "graceful, beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "沸々",
      "answer": "ふつふつ",
      "meaning": "simmer, bubble out, flow out"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊媒",
      "answer": "れいばい",
      "meaning": "spirit medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "柩",
      "answer": "ひつぎ,きゅう",
      "meaning": "coffin, casket"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹芸",
      "answer": "はらげい",
      "meaning": "expressing oneself without words or gestures, force of personality"
    },
    {
      "question": "重篤",
      "answer": "じゅうとく",
      "meaning": "critical (condition), serious"
    },
    {
      "question": "交通機関",
      "answer": "こうつうきかん",
      "meaning": "(means of) transportation, transport, transportation facilities, transportation system, transit syst"
    },
    {
      "question": "相部屋",
      "answer": "あいべや",
      "meaning": "sharing a room, dormitory room, match between wrestlers from the same stable"
    },
    {
      "question": "始発",
      "answer": "しはつ",
      "meaning": "first departure (of the day), first train, first bus, departing one's home station (of a train, bus,"
    },
    {
      "question": "邦",
      "answer": "くに",
      "meaning": "country, state, region, national government, central government, home (i.e. hometown, home country),"
    },
    {
      "question": "軒下",
      "answer": "のきした",
      "meaning": "under the eaves"
    },
    {
      "question": "古着",
      "answer": "ふるぎ",
      "meaning": "old clothes, secondhand clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "現行",
      "answer": "げんこう",
      "meaning": "present, current, in operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "此",
      "answer": "これ,こん",
      "meaning": "this, this one, this person, now, this point (in time), here, used to stress the subject of a senten"
    },
    {
      "question": "身命",
      "answer": "しんめい",
      "meaning": "one's life"
    },
    {
      "question": "奪回",
      "answer": "だっかい",
      "meaning": "recovery, rescue, recapture"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉体関係",
      "answer": "にくたいかんけい",
      "meaning": "sexual relations, physical relations, carnal relations"
    },
    {
      "question": "滂沱",
      "answer": "ぼうだ",
      "meaning": "streaming (of tears), pouring, pouring (of rain or sweat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き立て",
      "answer": "やきたて",
      "meaning": "fresh made, freshly baked, freshly roasted"
    },
    {
      "question": "御霊",
      "answer": "みたま,ごりょう",
      "meaning": "spirit of a deceased person, the Holy Ghost, the Holy Spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃村",
      "answer": "はいそん",
      "meaning": "ghost town, deserted village, village without inhabitants"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨岩",
      "answer": "きょがん",
      "meaning": "huge rock, crag"
    },
    {
      "question": "男の娘",
      "answer": "おとこのこ,おとこのむすめ",
      "meaning": "young man who has a feminine aesthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "対外",
      "answer": "たいがい",
      "meaning": "external, foreign"
    },
    {
      "question": "人懐こい",
      "answer": "ひとなつこい",
      "meaning": "friendly, affable, amiable, sociable, loving company, (animals) taking kindly to men"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ平",
      "answer": "まっぴら",
      "meaning": "(not) by any means, (not) for anything, wouldn't do for anything, had enough, flatly refusing"
    },
    {
      "question": "白蛇",
      "answer": "しろへび,はくじゃ",
      "meaning": "albino Japanese rat snake"
    },
    {
      "question": "球場",
      "answer": "きゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "baseball stadium, ballpark"
    },
    {
      "question": "河口",
      "answer": "かこう,かわぐち",
      "meaning": "mouth of river, estuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "煩悶",
      "answer": "はんもん",
      "meaning": "worry, agony"
    },
    {
      "question": "千鳥",
      "answer": "ちどり",
      "meaning": "plover"
    },
    {
      "question": "積もり",
      "answer": "つもり",
      "meaning": "intention, plan, conviction, belief"
    },
    {
      "question": "罪悪",
      "answer": "ざいあく",
      "meaning": "crime, sin, vice"
    },
    {
      "question": "総崩れ",
      "answer": "そうくずれ",
      "meaning": "rout, collapse"
    },
    {
      "question": "与り知る",
      "answer": "あずかりしる",
      "meaning": "to be aware of, to know about, to be concerned in, to have to do with"
    },
    {
      "question": "流浪",
      "answer": "るろう",
      "meaning": "vagrancy, wandering, nomadism"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝汗",
      "answer": "ねあせ",
      "meaning": "perspiration given off during sleep, sweating while sleeping, night sweats"
    },
    {
      "question": "飴色",
      "answer": "あめいろ",
      "meaning": "amber, yellowish-brown"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き合う",
      "answer": "たたきあう",
      "meaning": "to strike (each other), to come to blows, to fight (each other), to speak (to each other)"
    },
    {
      "question": "汁物",
      "answer": "しるもの",
      "meaning": "soup"
    },
    {
      "question": "配列",
      "answer": "はいれつ",
      "meaning": "arrangement, disposition, array (programming)"
    },
    {
      "question": "平均値",
      "answer": "へいきんち",
      "meaning": "average value, mean value, mean, expectation"
    },
    {
      "question": "特筆",
      "answer": "とくひつ",
      "meaning": "special mention"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち逃げ",
      "answer": "かちにげ",
      "meaning": "quitting while one is ahead"
    },
    {
      "question": "変遷",
      "answer": "へんせん",
      "meaning": "change, transition, vicissitudes"
    },
    {
      "question": "固形",
      "answer": "こけい",
      "meaning": "solid (body)"
    },
    {
      "question": "完封",
      "answer": "かんぷう",
      "meaning": "complete blockade (seal), baseball shutout"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇壮",
      "answer": "ゆうそう",
      "meaning": "heroic, brave, majestic, soul-stirring, lively, gallant"
    },
    {
      "question": "感情論",
      "answer": "かんじょうろん",
      "meaning": "argument based on emotion, sentimental argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "人使い",
      "answer": "ひとづかい",
      "meaning": "handling one's workmen"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸聞こえ",
      "answer": "まるぎこえ",
      "meaning": "being able to hear everything (esp. when one was not intended to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小金",
      "answer": "こがね",
      "meaning": "small sum of money"
    },
    {
      "question": "時限爆弾",
      "answer": "じげんばくだん",
      "meaning": "time bomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞り",
      "answer": "しぼり",
      "meaning": "tie-dye, tie-dyeing, aperture (e.g. camera, iris of the eye), aperture stop, stop, contraction, sque"
    },
    {
      "question": "分校",
      "answer": "ぶんこう",
      "meaning": "branch school"
    },
    {
      "question": "劈く",
      "answer": "つんざく",
      "meaning": "to break, to tear, to pierce, to split, to burst"
    },
    {
      "question": "床屋",
      "answer": "とこや",
      "meaning": "barbershop, barber shop, barber"
    },
    {
      "question": "雄姿",
      "answer": "ゆうし",
      "meaning": "majestic figure, imposing figure, impressive appearance, magnificent appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "表裏",
      "answer": "ひょうり,おもてうら",
      "meaning": "front and back, inside and outside, two sides, both sides, duplicity, double-dealing, being two-face"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き別れ",
      "answer": "いきわかれ",
      "meaning": "lifelong separation"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤銅色",
      "answer": "しゃくどういろ",
      "meaning": "brown, tanned"
    },
    {
      "question": "格付け",
      "answer": "かくづけ,かくずけ",
      "meaning": "rating, classification, allocation, grading"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚飾",
      "answer": "きょしょく",
      "meaning": "ostentation, show, affectation"
    },
    {
      "question": "審理",
      "answer": "しんり",
      "meaning": "trial"
    },
    {
      "question": "凸凹",
      "answer": "でこぼこ,とつおう,だくぼく",
      "meaning": "unevenness, roughness, ruggedness, bumpiness, inequality, imbalance, difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "新進気鋭",
      "answer": "しんしんきえい",
      "meaning": "young and energetic, up-and-coming"
    },
    {
      "question": "上玉",
      "answer": "じょうだま,じょうたま",
      "meaning": "fine jewel, article of excellent quality, beautiful woman, beauty, stunner"
    },
    {
      "question": "微力",
      "answer": "びりょく",
      "meaning": "little power, little influence, (one's) poor ability, limited ability, what little one can do"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚期",
      "answer": "こんき",
      "meaning": "marriageable age, chance of marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "触れ回る",
      "answer": "ふれまわる",
      "meaning": "to go around spreading (news, rumors, etc.), to cry about, to circulate, to broadcast"
    },
    {
      "question": "伏見",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "盗み見",
      "answer": "ぬすみみ",
      "meaning": "surreptitious glance, looking furtively"
    },
    {
      "question": "海の幸",
      "answer": "うみのさち",
      "meaning": "seafood, products of the sea, marine products, fruits of the sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "投薬",
      "answer": "とうやく",
      "meaning": "administration, medication, dosage"
    },
    {
      "question": "談話",
      "answer": "だんわ",
      "meaning": "talk, conversation, dialogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾き",
      "answer": "かたむき",
      "meaning": "slope, inclination, list, tendency, trend, bent, disposition, bias, slope (of a linear function)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一攫千金",
      "answer": "いっかくせんきん",
      "meaning": "getting rich quick, making a killing, making a fortune at a single stroke"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番手",
      "answer": "いちばんて",
      "meaning": "first person (to do), person going first, first place, top position, person in the top position, per"
    },
    {
      "question": "民宿",
      "answer": "みんしゅく",
      "meaning": "pension, guesthouse, bed and breakfast, private home providing lodging for travelers (travellers)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝顔",
      "answer": "あさがお",
      "meaning": "Japanese morning glory (Ipomoea nil), picotee morning glory, ivy morning glory, funnel-shaped object"
    },
    {
      "question": "学祭",
      "answer": "がくさい",
      "meaning": "school festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "女医",
      "answer": "じょい",
      "meaning": "woman doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬り合い",
      "answer": "きりあい",
      "meaning": "crossing swords, fighting with swords, cutting each other (in fighting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "主旨",
      "answer": "しゅし",
      "meaning": "meaning, point (e.g. of a statement), gist, effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "楕円",
      "answer": "だえん",
      "meaning": "ellipse"
    },
    {
      "question": "片言",
      "answer": "かたこと,へんげん",
      "meaning": "prattle, broken language, halting language, baby talk, imperfect speech, smattering, brief remark, f"
    },
    {
      "question": "博する",
      "answer": "はくする",
      "meaning": "to win, to gain, to earn, to spread (one's name, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉丈夫",
      "answer": "いじょうふ",
      "meaning": "great man, great god, hero, big man"
    },
    {
      "question": "然程",
      "answer": "さほど",
      "meaning": "(not) so, (not) particularly, (not) very, (not) that much"
    },
    {
      "question": "先進国",
      "answer": "せんしんこく",
      "meaning": "advanced (developed) country, advanced nations"
    },
    {
      "question": "脂身",
      "answer": "あぶらみ",
      "meaning": "fat (of meat), fatty meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "造作",
      "answer": "ぞうさ,ぞうさく",
      "meaning": "trouble, difficulty, hospitality, treatment, treat, building (esp. a house), house fixture, fitting,"
    },
    {
      "question": "気分屋",
      "answer": "きぶんや",
      "meaning": "moody person"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄面皮",
      "answer": "てつめんぴ",
      "meaning": "impudence, shamelessness, brazenness, arrogance, audacity, effrontery, nerve"
    },
    {
      "question": "山越え",
      "answer": "やまごえ",
      "meaning": "crossing a mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "死別",
      "answer": "しべつ",
      "meaning": "bereavement"
    },
    {
      "question": "盆地",
      "answer": "ぼんち",
      "meaning": "basin (e.g. between mountains)"
    },
    {
      "question": "香料",
      "answer": "こうりょう",
      "meaning": "flavoring, flavouring, spices, fragrance, perfume, incense, condolence gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "別個",
      "answer": "べっこ",
      "meaning": "another, different, separate, discrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "備考",
      "answer": "びこう",
      "meaning": "note (for reference), remarks, N.B."
    },
    {
      "question": "師範代",
      "answer": "しはんだい",
      "meaning": "assistant instructor"
    },
    {
      "question": "事とする",
      "answer": "こととする",
      "meaning": "to devote oneself, to do one thing exclusively, to make a job of, to decide to"
    },
    {
      "question": "源流",
      "answer": "げんりゅう",
      "meaning": "source (e.g. of a river), headwaters, origin of something continuous (language, culture, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠟燭",
      "answer": "ろうそく",
      "meaning": "candle"
    },
    {
      "question": "群体",
      "answer": "ぐんたい",
      "meaning": "colony"
    },
    {
      "question": "被虐",
      "answer": "ひぎゃく",
      "meaning": "suffering (as a result of maltreatment)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳漿",
      "answer": "のうしょう",
      "meaning": "spinal fluid, gray matter, grey matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ叩く",
      "answer": "ひっぱたく",
      "meaning": "to slap, to strike, to spank"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠近",
      "answer": "えんきん,おちこち",
      "meaning": "distance, perspective, far and near, here and there"
    },
    {
      "question": "区分け",
      "answer": "くわけ",
      "meaning": "division, section, demarcation, (traffic) lane, compartment, classification, sorting"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫食い",
      "answer": "むしくい",
      "meaning": "worm-eaten, moth-eaten, holes eaten in clothing, leaves, etc. by caterpillars, moths, etc., leaf war"
    },
    {
      "question": "全治",
      "answer": "ぜんち,ぜんじ",
      "meaning": "complete recovery, healing"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪法",
      "answer": "じゅほう",
      "meaning": "esoteric Buddhist ritual where incantations are chanted, magic"
    },
    {
      "question": "百鬼夜行",
      "answer": "ひゃっきやぎょう,ひゃっきやこう",
      "meaning": "nightly procession of monsters, spirits, etc., veritable pandemonium, large number of people plottin"
    },
    {
      "question": "大地震",
      "answer": "おおじしん,だいじしん",
      "meaning": "major earthquake, large earthquake"
    },
    {
      "question": "値が張る",
      "answer": "ねがはる",
      "meaning": "to be expensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮎",
      "answer": "あゆ,あい",
      "meaning": "sweetfish (Plecoglossus altivelis altivelis), ayu"
    },
    {
      "question": "放蕩",
      "answer": "ほうとう",
      "meaning": "dissipation, prodigality, debauchery"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆知識",
      "answer": "まめちしき",
      "meaning": "trivia, snippet of knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "遮蔽",
      "answer": "しゃへい",
      "meaning": "shielding, sheltering, screening, shading, masking"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘儀",
      "answer": "ひぎ",
      "meaning": "secret ceremony, ritual, sanctum sanctorum"
    },
    {
      "question": "翌",
      "answer": "よく",
      "meaning": "the following, next"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱火",
      "answer": "よわび",
      "meaning": "low flame (cooking), low heat, simmering"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉食系",
      "answer": "にくしょくけい",
      "meaning": "man's man, man aggressively pursuing sex and riches, carnivore"
    },
    {
      "question": "御利益",
      "answer": "ごりやく",
      "meaning": "grace (of God), divine favour, blessing, miracle, answer to a prayer, benefit, efficacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り返し",
      "answer": "おりかえし",
      "meaning": "by return, (call or write back) without delay, lapel, cuff, turn-up, flap, going back, returning, tu"
    },
    {
      "question": "御法度",
      "answer": "ごはっと",
      "meaning": "contraband, taboo, strictly forbidden"
    },
    {
      "question": "番える",
      "answer": "つがえる",
      "meaning": "to nock (an arrow), to fix an arrow to the string"
    },
    {
      "question": "対談",
      "answer": "たいだん",
      "meaning": "talk, dialogue, conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱獲",
      "answer": "らんかく",
      "meaning": "excessive fishing, overfishing, overhunting, excessive taking"
    },
    {
      "question": "人間嫌い",
      "answer": "にんげんぎらい",
      "meaning": "misanthropy, misanthropist"
    },
    {
      "question": "地肌",
      "answer": "じはだ",
      "meaning": "texture, grain, one's skin (lacking makeup, etc.), natural skin, bare skin, scalp, surface of the ea"
    },
    {
      "question": "一字一句",
      "answer": "いちじいっく",
      "meaning": "word for word, verbatim, a single word and a single phrase"
    },
    {
      "question": "碑文",
      "answer": "ひぶん",
      "meaning": "inscription, epitaph, epigraph"
    },
    {
      "question": "残弾",
      "answer": "ざんだん",
      "meaning": "remaining bullets, remaining ammunition"
    },
    {
      "question": "更迭",
      "answer": "こうてつ",
      "meaning": "change (of personnel), reshuffle (e.g. of a cabinet), shake-up, dismissal (e.g. of a minister), repl"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由意志",
      "answer": "じゆういし",
      "meaning": "free will"
    },
    {
      "question": "全焼",
      "answer": "ぜんしょう",
      "meaning": "burned down, entirely destroyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲兵",
      "answer": "ほうへい",
      "meaning": "artillery, gunner"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘爆",
      "answer": "ゆうばく",
      "meaning": "induced explosion, secondary explosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "南端",
      "answer": "なんたん",
      "meaning": "southern tip"
    },
    {
      "question": "数奇",
      "answer": "すうき,さっき,すき",
      "meaning": "misfortune, adverse fortune, hapless fate, checkered (life, career, etc.), varied, eventful, dramati"
    },
    {
      "question": "返",
      "answer": "へん",
      "meaning": "number of times, reply, answer"
    },
    {
      "question": "昂奮",
      "answer": "こうふん",
      "meaning": "excitement, stimulation, agitation, arousal"
    },
    {
      "question": "十文字",
      "answer": "じゅうもんじ",
      "meaning": "cross, cruciform"
    },
    {
      "question": "貨",
      "answer": "たから",
      "meaning": "treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳弾",
      "answer": "ちょうだん",
      "meaning": "ricochet"
    },
    {
      "question": "走破",
      "answer": "そうは",
      "meaning": "running the whole distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "講演",
      "answer": "こうえん",
      "meaning": "lecture, address, speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥部",
      "answer": "ちぶ",
      "meaning": "private parts, privates, genitalia, secret place, disgraceful thing, shame, embarrassment, underbell"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦域",
      "answer": "せんいき",
      "meaning": "war area, battlefield, theater, theatre"
    },
    {
      "question": "討ち死に",
      "answer": "うちじに",
      "meaning": "death in battle, death on the battlefield"
    },
    {
      "question": "延焼",
      "answer": "えんしょう",
      "meaning": "spread of fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "株式",
      "answer": "かぶしき",
      "meaning": "share (in a company), stock"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉館",
      "answer": "へいかん",
      "meaning": "closing (for the day; of a library, museum, cinema, etc.), closing down (of a library, museum, cinem"
    },
    {
      "question": "決裁",
      "answer": "けっさい",
      "meaning": "sanction, approval"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮気者",
      "answer": "うわきもの",
      "meaning": "cheater, unfaithful person, adulterer"
    },
    {
      "question": "目減り",
      "answer": "めべり",
      "meaning": "loss (of weight or volume, e.g. in transit), ullage, outage, decrease (in value), reduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽度",
      "answer": "けいど",
      "meaning": "slight (degree), light"
    },
    {
      "question": "流民",
      "answer": "るみん,りゅうみん",
      "meaning": "refugees"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉芽",
      "answer": "にくが,にくげ",
      "meaning": "granulation, granulation tissue, proud flesh, bulbil"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤",
      "answer": "みなしご,こ",
      "meaning": "orphan, being alone, solitude, loneliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "受容",
      "answer": "じゅよう",
      "meaning": "reception"
    },
    {
      "question": "随所",
      "answer": "ずいしょ",
      "meaning": "everywhere, at every turn"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨漏り",
      "answer": "あまもり",
      "meaning": "roof leak"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝晩",
      "answer": "あさばん",
      "meaning": "morning and evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝い事",
      "answer": "いわいごと",
      "meaning": "celebration, auspicious occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "祈念",
      "answer": "きねん",
      "meaning": "prayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "公家",
      "answer": "くげ,こうか,こうけ",
      "meaning": "court noble, nobility, Imperial Court"
    },
    {
      "question": "因果律",
      "answer": "いんがりつ",
      "meaning": "law of cause and effect, principle of causality"
    },
    {
      "question": "前王",
      "answer": "ぜんのう,ぜんおう",
      "meaning": "former king, late king"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴風雨",
      "answer": "ぼうふうう,あらし",
      "meaning": "rainstorm, storm"
    },
    {
      "question": "総監",
      "answer": "そうかん",
      "meaning": "inspector general, commissioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "神道",
      "answer": "しんとう,しんどう",
      "meaning": "Shinto, Shintoism"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍手",
      "answer": "ぐんて",
      "meaning": "cotton gloves, working gloves"
    },
    {
      "question": "青二才",
      "answer": "あおにさい",
      "meaning": "green youth, immature youth, novice, greenhorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚を衝く",
      "answer": "きょをつく",
      "meaning": "to attack the enemy in his unguarded moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "生卵",
      "answer": "なまたまご",
      "meaning": "raw egg"
    },
    {
      "question": "返す刀",
      "answer": "かえすかたな",
      "meaning": "attacking one opponent then immediately attacking another"
    },
    {
      "question": "独走",
      "answer": "どくそう",
      "meaning": "running alone, running solo, having a large lead (over the others), being far ahead (of everyone els"
    },
    {
      "question": "異分子",
      "answer": "いぶんし",
      "meaning": "outsider, alien elements"
    },
    {
      "question": "耄碌",
      "answer": "もうろく",
      "meaning": "senility, dotage, decrepitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛り返す",
      "answer": "もりかえす",
      "meaning": "to rally, to make a comeback"
    },
    {
      "question": "温暖",
      "answer": "おんだん",
      "meaning": "warm, mild, temperate"
    },
    {
      "question": "一角獣",
      "answer": "いっかくじゅう",
      "meaning": "unicorn, narwhal, qilin (Chinese unicorn)"
    },
    {
      "question": "売女",
      "answer": "ばいた,ばいじょ",
      "meaning": "prostitute, whore, tramp, floozy, slut"
    },
    {
      "question": "危機管理",
      "answer": "ききかんり",
      "meaning": "crisis management"
    },
    {
      "question": "男勝り",
      "answer": "おとこまさり",
      "meaning": "(of a woman) strong-minded, spirited, mannish"
    },
    {
      "question": "番外",
      "answer": "ばんがい",
      "meaning": "exception, supernumerary, extra (theatrical), extra (e.g. performance, item, object, etc.), addition"
    },
    {
      "question": "前部",
      "answer": "ぜんぶ",
      "meaning": "front part, fore, front"
    },
    {
      "question": "名工",
      "answer": "めいこう",
      "meaning": "craftsman, skilled artisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "瑣末",
      "answer": "さまつ",
      "meaning": "trivial, trifling"
    },
    {
      "question": "密売",
      "answer": "みつばい",
      "meaning": "smuggling, bootlegging, illicit trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗唱",
      "answer": "あんしょう",
      "meaning": "recitation, reciting from memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴り出す",
      "answer": "けりだす",
      "meaning": "to kick out (e.g. someone from a house)"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩る",
      "answer": "さする,する",
      "meaning": "to rub, to pat, to stroke, to massage, to chafe, to strike (match), to file, to frost (glass), to lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "付加価値",
      "answer": "ふかかち",
      "meaning": "added value, value added"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛆",
      "answer": "うじ",
      "meaning": "maggot, larva, grub"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐怖症",
      "answer": "きょうふしょう",
      "meaning": "phobia, morbid fear"
    },
    {
      "question": "美酒",
      "answer": "びしゅ",
      "meaning": "high-grade sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き地獄",
      "answer": "いきじごく",
      "meaning": "hell on earth, living hell"
    },
    {
      "question": "剃刀",
      "answer": "かみそり,かみすり,そり",
      "meaning": "razor"
    },
    {
      "question": "共振",
      "answer": "きょうしん",
      "meaning": "resonance, sympathetic vibration"
    },
    {
      "question": "微生物",
      "answer": "びせいぶつ",
      "meaning": "microbe, germ"
    },
    {
      "question": "体得",
      "answer": "たいとく",
      "meaning": "mastery, learning through experience, realization, realisation, comprehension"
    },
    {
      "question": "割高",
      "answer": "わりだか",
      "meaning": "comparatively high, fairly expensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "モテ期",
      "answer": "モテき",
      "meaning": "period (of life) when one is enjoying more romantic attention than usual"
    },
    {
      "question": "堕胎",
      "answer": "だたい",
      "meaning": "abortion, feticide"
    },
    {
      "question": "避暑地",
      "answer": "ひしょち",
      "meaning": "place that is cool in the summer, place one goes to escape the heat of summer, summer retreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯上がり",
      "answer": "ゆあがり",
      "meaning": "after a bath, after taking a bath, large towel used after taking a bath, yukata worn after taking a"
    },
    {
      "question": "善し悪し",
      "answer": "よしあし,よしわるし",
      "meaning": "right or wrong, good or bad, quality, suitability, having both merits and demerits, having both adva"
    },
    {
      "question": "公子",
      "answer": "こうし",
      "meaning": "young nobleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "外法",
      "answer": "そとのり",
      "meaning": "outside measurements"
    },
    {
      "question": "窪地",
      "answer": "くぼち",
      "meaning": "hollow, low ground, basin, pit, dip, depression"
    },
    {
      "question": "本庁",
      "answer": "ほんちょう",
      "meaning": "central government office, this office"
    },
    {
      "question": "間引く",
      "answer": "まびく",
      "meaning": "to thin out (plants, seedlings, crops, etc.), to cull, to run on a curtailed schedule, to cut down,"
    },
    {
      "question": "去勢",
      "answer": "きょせい",
      "meaning": "castration, enervation"
    },
    {
      "question": "多重人格",
      "answer": "たじゅうじんかく",
      "meaning": "multiple personality, split personality"
    },
    {
      "question": "万華鏡",
      "answer": "まんげきょう,ばんかきょう",
      "meaning": "kaleidoscope"
    },
    {
      "question": "脊髄反射",
      "answer": "せきずいはんしゃ",
      "meaning": "spinal reflex"
    },
    {
      "question": "検死",
      "answer": "けんし",
      "meaning": "autopsy, inquest, investigation of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "実験動物",
      "answer": "じっけんどうぶつ",
      "meaning": "laboratory animal, experimental animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "開場",
      "answer": "かいじょう",
      "meaning": "opening (the doors to an event, etc.), inauguration"
    },
    {
      "question": "模造品",
      "answer": "もぞうひん",
      "meaning": "fake goods, imitations"
    },
    {
      "question": "捧げ持つ",
      "answer": "ささげもつ",
      "meaning": "to hold something reverently with both hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "実利",
      "answer": "じつり",
      "meaning": "use, utility, profit, gain"
    },
    {
      "question": "大胆不敵",
      "answer": "だいたんふてき",
      "meaning": "daring, fearless, audacious, bold, dauntless, daredevil"
    },
    {
      "question": "大道具",
      "answer": "おおどうぐ",
      "meaning": "stage setting, scenery, stagehand, sceneshifter"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛腕",
      "answer": "ごうわん",
      "meaning": "strong arm, stout arm, ability to carry out a difficult job, capable person"
    },
    {
      "question": "年取る",
      "answer": "としとる",
      "meaning": "to grow old, to age"
    },
    {
      "question": "侵蝕",
      "answer": "しんしょく",
      "meaning": "encroachment, erosion, corrosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "金箔",
      "answer": "きんぱく",
      "meaning": "gold leaf, beaten gold"
    },
    {
      "question": "後程",
      "answer": "のちほど",
      "meaning": "later on, eventually, afterwards"
    },
    {
      "question": "松葉杖",
      "answer": "まつばづえ",
      "meaning": "crutch, crutches"
    },
    {
      "question": "客商売",
      "answer": "きゃくしょうばい",
      "meaning": "service business (hotel, restaurant, entertainment), service industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "望み薄",
      "answer": "のぞみうす",
      "meaning": "faint hopes, dim prospects, little hope, unlikely (to be successful)"
    },
    {
      "question": "着眼点",
      "answer": "ちゃくがんてん",
      "meaning": "focus of one's attention, what one is looking for, point of view, viewpoint"
    },
    {
      "question": "異端児",
      "answer": "いたんじ",
      "meaning": "nonconformist, dissenter, maverick, enfant terrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "下肢",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "lower limbs, legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "姉君",
      "answer": "あねぎみ",
      "meaning": "(elder) sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "殿様",
      "answer": "とのさま",
      "meaning": "nobleman, dignitary, lord, feudal lord (of the Edo period), daimyō, man brought up away from the wor"
    },
    {
      "question": "類推",
      "answer": "るいすい",
      "meaning": "analogy, analogical reasoning, analogical inference"
    },
    {
      "question": "起用",
      "answer": "きよう",
      "meaning": "appointment (to a position, job, etc.), being used for a role, promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "無期限",
      "answer": "むきげん",
      "meaning": "indefinite"
    },
    {
      "question": "刷り込み",
      "answer": "すりこみ",
      "meaning": "imprinting, stenciling"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛み分け",
      "answer": "いたみわけ",
      "meaning": "match declared drawn due to injury"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹皮",
      "answer": "じゅひ",
      "meaning": "bark (of a tree, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "身重",
      "answer": "みおも",
      "meaning": "pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "改め",
      "answer": "あらため",
      "meaning": "former (e.g. name), previous, changed, examination, inspection, investigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "警察庁",
      "answer": "けいさつちょう",
      "meaning": "National Police Agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "国会",
      "answer": "こっかい",
      "meaning": "National Diet, legislative assembly of Japan (1947-), Imperial Diet, legislative assembly of Japan ("
    },
    {
      "question": "地割れ",
      "answer": "じわれ",
      "meaning": "cracks or fissures in the ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "秒速",
      "answer": "びょうそく",
      "meaning": "per second"
    },
    {
      "question": "出張所",
      "answer": "しゅっちょうじょ",
      "meaning": "branch office, agency, sub-branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "守銭奴",
      "answer": "しゅせんど",
      "meaning": "miser, niggard, cheapskate"
    },
    {
      "question": "指南役",
      "answer": "しなんやく",
      "meaning": "instructor"
    },
    {
      "question": "店構え",
      "answer": "みせがまえ",
      "meaning": "store's appearance (esp. shop front, signs, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "丁寧語",
      "answer": "ていねいご",
      "meaning": "polite language (e.g. masu, desu)"
    },
    {
      "question": "届け出",
      "answer": "とどけで",
      "meaning": "report, notification"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦げ付く",
      "answer": "こげつく",
      "meaning": "to get burned and stuck on (e.g. rice in a pan), to become uncollectable (e.g. debt or loan), to bec"
    },
    {
      "question": "閂",
      "answer": "かんぬき,かんのき",
      "meaning": "bar, bolt (e.g. on door), latch, double-arm lock (wrestling)"
    },
    {
      "question": "実働",
      "answer": "じつどう",
      "meaning": "actual work"
    },
    {
      "question": "新興宗教",
      "answer": "しんこうしゅうきょう",
      "meaning": "new religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "流れ者",
      "answer": "ながれもの",
      "meaning": "stranger, tramp, wanderer"
    },
    {
      "question": "持参金",
      "answer": "じさんきん",
      "meaning": "dowry"
    },
    {
      "question": "前身",
      "answer": "ぜんしん",
      "meaning": "antecedents, ancestor, previous position, previous existence, predecessor organization, predecessor"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪酔い",
      "answer": "わるよい",
      "meaning": "drunken sickness, getting sick from drinking, drunken frenzy, becoming violent or disorderly when dr"
    },
    {
      "question": "自戒",
      "answer": "じかい",
      "meaning": "self-admonition"
    },
    {
      "question": "自己暗示",
      "answer": "じこあんじ",
      "meaning": "autosuggestion, self-suggestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "人喰い",
      "answer": "ひとくい",
      "meaning": "cannibalism, biting (someone), man-eating (e.g. tiger), cannibalistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "戯",
      "answer": "あじゃら,あじゃれ,あざれ",
      "meaning": "pleasantry, joke, tomfoolery"
    },
    {
      "question": "条項",
      "answer": "じょうこう",
      "meaning": "clause, article, stipulations"
    },
    {
      "question": "安宿",
      "answer": "やすやど",
      "meaning": "cheap hotel"
    },
    {
      "question": "不鮮明",
      "answer": "ふせんめい",
      "meaning": "blur, blurred, indistinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "履行",
      "answer": "りこう",
      "meaning": "performance (of a duty), fulfillment (of a promise), fulfilment, execution (of a contract), discharg"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け狙う",
      "answer": "つけねらう",
      "meaning": "to prowl after, to keep watch on"
    },
    {
      "question": "早合点",
      "answer": "はやがてん,はやがってん",
      "meaning": "jumping to a hasty conclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "前期",
      "answer": "ぜんき",
      "meaning": "first term, first half-year, preceding period, early period"
    },
    {
      "question": "壊死",
      "answer": "えし",
      "meaning": "necrosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "創業",
      "answer": "そうぎょう",
      "meaning": "establishment (of a business), founding"
    },
    {
      "question": "手練",
      "answer": "しゅれん,てだれ,てれん",
      "meaning": "skill, dexterity, master hand, means of deceiving another"
    },
    {
      "question": "横っ腹",
      "answer": "よこっぱら",
      "meaning": "side, flank"
    },
    {
      "question": "心理戦",
      "answer": "しんりせん",
      "meaning": "psychological warfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "固定観念",
      "answer": "こていかんねん",
      "meaning": "fixed idea, idée fixe, stereotype, prejudice"
    },
    {
      "question": "炙り出す",
      "answer": "あぶりだす",
      "meaning": "to bring into the open, to reveal, to uncover (e.g. evidence), to bring to light"
    },
    {
      "question": "海戦",
      "answer": "かいせん",
      "meaning": "naval battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "男嫌い",
      "answer": "おとこぎらい",
      "meaning": "misandry, man-hater"
    },
    {
      "question": "創作物",
      "answer": "そうさくぶつ",
      "meaning": "creative work (e.g. artistic, literary)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無軌道",
      "answer": "むきどう",
      "meaning": "trackless, reckless, dissipated"
    },
    {
      "question": "時計回り",
      "answer": "とけいまわり",
      "meaning": "clockwise rotation, CW"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱望",
      "answer": "ねつぼう",
      "meaning": "longing for, burning desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "一夏",
      "answer": "いちげ,ひとなつ",
      "meaning": "one summer (during which a monk attends a summer retreat), one summer"
    },
    {
      "question": "極道",
      "answer": "ごくどう",
      "meaning": "wicked, evil, profligate, immoral, wastrel, scoundrel, villain, organized crime, yakuza, underworld"
    },
    {
      "question": "生育",
      "answer": "せいいく",
      "meaning": "birth and growth, giving birth and raising, development, breeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "小惑星",
      "answer": "しょうわくせい",
      "meaning": "asteroid"
    },
    {
      "question": "再教育",
      "answer": "さいきょういく",
      "meaning": "retraining, re-education"
    },
    {
      "question": "一抱え",
      "answer": "ひとかかえ",
      "meaning": "armful, bundle"
    },
    {
      "question": "炎症",
      "answer": "えんしょう",
      "meaning": "inflammation, irritation"
    },
    {
      "question": "軸足",
      "answer": "じくあし",
      "meaning": "pivot leg"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷や水",
      "answer": "ひやみず",
      "meaning": "cold (drinking) water"
    },
    {
      "question": "用水路",
      "answer": "ようすいろ",
      "meaning": "irrigation channel, irrigation ditch, irrigation canal, flume"
    },
    {
      "question": "日本国",
      "answer": "にほんこく,にっぽんこく",
      "meaning": "Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "間食",
      "answer": "かんしょく",
      "meaning": "eating between meals, snacking"
    },
    {
      "question": "足許",
      "answer": "あしもと",
      "meaning": "at one's feet, underfoot, one's step (as in 'watch your step'), gait, pace, step, most recent, curre"
    },
    {
      "question": "石突き",
      "answer": "いしづき",
      "meaning": "ferrule (of a cane, umbrella, etc.), butt end (of a lance, pike, etc.), hard tip (of a mushroom stem"
    },
    {
      "question": "峰打ち",
      "answer": "みねうち",
      "meaning": "striking with the back of the sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "白線",
      "answer": "はくせん",
      "meaning": "white line, linea alba (anot.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛犬",
      "answer": "あいけん",
      "meaning": "pet dog, beloved dog, love of dogs, fondness for dogs"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐車",
      "answer": "ちゅうしゃ",
      "meaning": "parking (e.g. car)"
    },
    {
      "question": "総身",
      "answer": "そうみ,そうしん",
      "meaning": "one's whole body"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆走",
      "answer": "ぎゃくそう",
      "meaning": "going in the opposite direction, going against the wind, running or operating a machine in reverse ("
    },
    {
      "question": "私事",
      "answer": "しじ,わたくしごと",
      "meaning": "personal affairs, private matter, personal secret, privacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "水と油",
      "answer": "みずとあぶら",
      "meaning": "incompatible, (going together) like oil and water"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚儀",
      "answer": "こんぎ",
      "meaning": "wedding ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "肥満",
      "answer": "ひまん",
      "meaning": "corpulence, fatness, obesity"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り次ぎ",
      "answer": "とりつぎ",
      "meaning": "agency, commission, distributor, intermediation, reception (of guests), conveyance (of messages)"
    },
    {
      "question": "吃驚",
      "answer": "びっくり,きっきょう",
      "meaning": "to be surprised, to be amazed, to be frightened, to be astonished, to get startled, to jump, surpris"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮健",
      "answer": "そうけん",
      "meaning": "healthy, robust"
    },
    {
      "question": "声質",
      "answer": "せいしつ",
      "meaning": "voice quality, type of voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "麦畑",
      "answer": "むぎばたけ",
      "meaning": "wheat field, barley field, cornfield"
    },
    {
      "question": "攪拌",
      "answer": "かくはん,こうはん",
      "meaning": "agitation, stirring, whipping, beating"
    },
    {
      "question": "名刀",
      "answer": "めいとう",
      "meaning": "famous sword, excellent sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴掘り",
      "answer": "あなほり",
      "meaning": "excavation, digging"
    },
    {
      "question": "増減",
      "answer": "ぞうげん",
      "meaning": "increase and decrease, fluctuation"
    },
    {
      "question": "慰問",
      "answer": "いもん",
      "meaning": "visit to console someone, giving comfort (to the sick, injured, etc.), expressing condolences (sympa"
    },
    {
      "question": "牙を剝く",
      "answer": "きばをむく",
      "meaning": "to bare one's fangs, to snarl at"
    },
    {
      "question": "過大",
      "answer": "かだい",
      "meaning": "excessive, too much, unreasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "藪蛇",
      "answer": "やぶへび",
      "meaning": "unnecessary trouble brought upon oneself, stirring up a hornet's nest"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸し焼き",
      "answer": "むしやき",
      "meaning": "baking foods in a covered pan, foods baked in a covered pan"
    },
    {
      "question": "出っ張る",
      "answer": "でっぱる",
      "meaning": "to project, to stand out, to jut out, to protrude"
    },
    {
      "question": "皮膜",
      "answer": "ひまく",
      "meaning": "film, membrane"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹一杯",
      "answer": "はらいっぱい",
      "meaning": "full stomach, bellyful, (eat) heartily, to one's heart's content"
    },
    {
      "question": "減退",
      "answer": "げんたい",
      "meaning": "decline, ebb, failure, decay, decrease, loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "木っ端",
      "answer": "こっぱ",
      "meaning": "wood chip, splinter, worthless thing, worthless person"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴族的",
      "answer": "きぞくてき",
      "meaning": "aristocratic"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁を結ぶ",
      "answer": "えんをむすぶ",
      "meaning": "to become related (through marriage, adoption, etc.), to form a connection (with Buddha)"
    },
    {
      "question": "星辰",
      "answer": "せいしん",
      "meaning": "celestial bodies, stars"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭場",
      "answer": "とば,とじょう",
      "meaning": "gambling den, gambling house"
    },
    {
      "question": "予断",
      "answer": "よだん",
      "meaning": "prediction, prejudgment, presupposition, foregone conclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "二足",
      "answer": "にそく",
      "meaning": "two legs, two feet, two pairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "補助金",
      "answer": "ほじょきん",
      "meaning": "assistance payment, subsidiary aid"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛毅",
      "answer": "ごうき",
      "meaning": "fortitude, firmness of character, hardihood, manliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩集",
      "answer": "ししゅう",
      "meaning": "poetry anthology, collection of poems, collected poems"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭酸水",
      "answer": "たんさんすい",
      "meaning": "carbonated water"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り出す",
      "answer": "ふりだす",
      "meaning": "to shake out, to draw a check (bill, draft, etc.), to issue (e.g. money order), to infuse (e.g. in h"
    },
    {
      "question": "三毛猫",
      "answer": "みけねこ",
      "meaning": "calico cat, tortoiseshell-and-white cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬液",
      "answer": "やくえき",
      "meaning": "liquid medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "草履",
      "answer": "ぞうり,じょうり",
      "meaning": "zōri, traditional Japanese thonged sandals"
    },
    {
      "question": "散",
      "answer": "ばら",
      "meaning": "loose articles (not packaged with other things), bulk items, individual items, coins, small change"
    },
    {
      "question": "重石",
      "answer": "おもし",
      "meaning": "stone weight (as used on pickle-tub covers), weight (as used in balances)"
    },
    {
      "question": "村民",
      "answer": "そんみん",
      "meaning": "villager"
    },
    {
      "question": "退廃",
      "answer": "たいはい",
      "meaning": "degeneration, decadence, deterioration, laxness, corruption"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き物",
      "answer": "やきもの",
      "meaning": "earthenware, pottery, porcelain, china, yakimono, flame-broiled food (esp. fish), tempered blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "願掛け",
      "answer": "がんかけ,がんがけ",
      "meaning": "making a prayer (to a god or Buddha)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲料水",
      "answer": "いんりょうすい",
      "meaning": "drinking water"
    },
    {
      "question": "主殿",
      "answer": "しゅでん",
      "meaning": "main building (of a villa, palace, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "社務所",
      "answer": "しゃむしょ",
      "meaning": "shrine office, office of a Shinto shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬り合う",
      "answer": "きりあう",
      "meaning": "to fight with swords, to cross swords"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び道具",
      "answer": "あそびどうぐ",
      "meaning": "plaything, toy"
    },
    {
      "question": "合衆国",
      "answer": "がっしゅうこく",
      "meaning": "federal state, United States of America"
    },
    {
      "question": "自動化",
      "answer": "じどうか",
      "meaning": "automation"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏切",
      "answer": "ふみきり",
      "meaning": "railway crossing, railroad crossing, train crossing, level crossing, starting line, scratch, determi"
    },
    {
      "question": "野鳥",
      "answer": "やちょう",
      "meaning": "wild bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "代弁者",
      "answer": "だいべんしゃ",
      "meaning": "spokesperson, speaker (for someone), mouthpiece, voice (e.g. for the ordinary citizen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "模様替え",
      "answer": "もようがえ",
      "meaning": "rearranging, remodeling, remodelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "義眼",
      "answer": "ぎがん",
      "meaning": "artificial eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "明り",
      "answer": "あかり",
      "meaning": "light, illumination, glow, gleam, lamp"
    },
    {
      "question": "展覧会",
      "answer": "てんらんかい",
      "meaning": "exhibition"
    },
    {
      "question": "英会話",
      "answer": "えいかいわ",
      "meaning": "English conversation, school for English conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い走り",
      "answer": "つかいばしり,つかいはしり",
      "meaning": "running errands (for someone else), errand boy, gofer, dogsbody"
    },
    {
      "question": "試運転",
      "answer": "しうんてん",
      "meaning": "trial run, test run"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち壊す",
      "answer": "ぶちこわす,うちこわす",
      "meaning": "to destroy, to crush, to break by striking, to wreck, to spoil, to ruin"
    },
    {
      "question": "端子",
      "answer": "たんし",
      "meaning": "terminal (electricity), pin (on a semiconductor or microcontroller), port (e.g. LAN port)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鏖殺",
      "answer": "おうさつ",
      "meaning": "massacre, extermination"
    },
    {
      "question": "山野",
      "answer": "さんや",
      "meaning": "hills and fields, countryside"
    },
    {
      "question": "違くて",
      "answer": "ちがくて,ちがうくて",
      "meaning": "different (from), not the same (as)"
    },
    {
      "question": "地続き",
      "answer": "じつづき",
      "meaning": "adjoining land"
    },
    {
      "question": "母性本能",
      "answer": "ぼせいほんのう",
      "meaning": "maternal instinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝刊",
      "answer": "ちょうかん",
      "meaning": "morning newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "身を以て",
      "answer": "みをもって",
      "meaning": "with one's own body, by one's own action, through one's own experience, firsthand"
    },
    {
      "question": "原っぱ",
      "answer": "はらっぱ",
      "meaning": "open field, empty lot, plain"
    },
    {
      "question": "若草色",
      "answer": "わかくさいろ",
      "meaning": "bright green, chartreuse green"
    },
    {
      "question": "前借り",
      "answer": "まえがり",
      "meaning": "getting an advance (on one's salary)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無用心",
      "answer": "ぶようじん",
      "meaning": "insecurity, carelessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "川底",
      "answer": "かわぞこ",
      "meaning": "riverbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "非公開",
      "answer": "ひこうかい",
      "meaning": "private, exclusive, secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "水神",
      "answer": "すいじん",
      "meaning": "a water god"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱世",
      "answer": "らんせい",
      "meaning": "troubled times, turbulent times"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱帯",
      "answer": "ねったい",
      "meaning": "tropics"
    },
    {
      "question": "試算",
      "answer": "しさん",
      "meaning": "trial calculation, preliminary calculation, estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪族",
      "answer": "ごうぞく",
      "meaning": "powerful family, powerful clan"
    },
    {
      "question": "六体",
      "answer": "りくたい,ろくたい",
      "meaning": "the six historical styles of writing kanji: large seal, small seal, clerical, triangular-swept cleri"
    },
    {
      "question": "不老",
      "answer": "ふろう",
      "meaning": "perennial youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "岸壁",
      "answer": "がんぺき",
      "meaning": "quay, wharf, jetty, steep cliff, cliff wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "中華料理",
      "answer": "ちゅうかりょうり",
      "meaning": "Chinese cooking, Chinese food"
    },
    {
      "question": "一寸",
      "answer": "いっすん,ちょっと,ちょと",
      "meaning": "one sun (approx. 3.03 cm), little bit (of time, distance, etc.), a little, a bit, slightly, just a m"
    },
    {
      "question": "居着く",
      "answer": "いつく",
      "meaning": "to settle down, to stay (for good), to stay long, to stay on"
    },
    {
      "question": "大作",
      "answer": "たいさく",
      "meaning": "large-scale work, voluminous work, monumental work, great work, masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "秦",
      "answer": "しん",
      "meaning": "Qin dynasty (China, 221-207 BCE), Ch'in dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "短編",
      "answer": "たんぺん",
      "meaning": "short (e.g. story, film)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大学院",
      "answer": "だいがくいん",
      "meaning": "graduate school"
    },
    {
      "question": "衣替え",
      "answer": "ころもがえ",
      "meaning": "seasonal change of clothing, changing one's dress for the season, renovation, facelift, redesign, re"
    },
    {
      "question": "撫ぜる",
      "answer": "なぜる",
      "meaning": "to brush gently, to stroke, to caress"
    },
    {
      "question": "小波",
      "answer": "さざなみ,こなみ",
      "meaning": "ripple (on water), wavelets, ripple (e.g. of uneasiness), unrest, disturbance"
    },
    {
      "question": "目を剝く",
      "answer": "めをむく",
      "meaning": "to open one's eyes wide (in anger, surprise, etc.), to goggle at"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦功",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "distinguished war service, merit of war"
    },
    {
      "question": "袈裟",
      "answer": "けさ",
      "meaning": "kasaya, monk's stole, wearing an article of clothing in the same manner as a kasaya (i.e. draped ove"
    },
    {
      "question": "説法",
      "answer": "せっぽう",
      "meaning": "lecture, sermon, preaching, moralizing, moralising"
    },
    {
      "question": "飼い殺し",
      "answer": "かいごろし",
      "meaning": "keeping a domestic animal beyond its useful life, keeping a person on the payroll without utilizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆死",
      "answer": "ばくし",
      "meaning": "death from explosion, death from bombing, bombing (in sales), flopping"
    },
    {
      "question": "触角",
      "answer": "しょっかく",
      "meaning": "feeler, antenna"
    },
    {
      "question": "演者",
      "answer": "えんじゃ",
      "meaning": "presenter, speaker, performer, actor, participant (in a TV show or TV panel)"
    },
    {
      "question": "悩殺",
      "answer": "のうさつ",
      "meaning": "fascinate, bewitch, enchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "機雷",
      "answer": "きらい",
      "meaning": "(sea) mine"
    },
    {
      "question": "投球",
      "answer": "とうきゅう",
      "meaning": "pitching, throwing a ball, bowling (in cricket), pitched ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘶く",
      "answer": "いななく",
      "meaning": "to neigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び切り",
      "answer": "とびきり",
      "meaning": "best, extra-fine, superfine, unequalled, exceptionally, extraordinarily, by far, jumping and slashin"
    },
    {
      "question": "五位",
      "answer": "ごい",
      "meaning": "fifth court rank, black-crowned night heron (Nycticorax nycticorax), night heron, five ranks, five s"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き役",
      "answer": "ききやく",
      "meaning": "listener's role"
    },
    {
      "question": "操舵",
      "answer": "そうだ",
      "meaning": "steering (of a boat), steerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "産卵",
      "answer": "さんらん",
      "meaning": "egg-laying, spawning"
    },
    {
      "question": "無手",
      "answer": "むて",
      "meaning": "empty-handed, unarmed, lacking funds"
    },
    {
      "question": "平和主義",
      "answer": "へいわしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "pacifism"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕枕",
      "answer": "うでまくら",
      "meaning": "using one's arms as a pillow"
    },
    {
      "question": "自責",
      "answer": "じせき",
      "meaning": "self-condemnation, self-reproach, self-accusation"
    },
    {
      "question": "過熱",
      "answer": "かねつ",
      "meaning": "superheating, overheating"
    },
    {
      "question": "詩歌",
      "answer": "しいか,しか",
      "meaning": "Japanese and Chinese poetry, poetry, poems"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱打",
      "answer": "らんだ",
      "meaning": "hitting, battering"
    },
    {
      "question": "同性愛",
      "answer": "どうせいあい",
      "meaning": "homosexual love"
    },
    {
      "question": "一夜漬け",
      "answer": "いちやづけ",
      "meaning": "last-minute cramming, overnight cramming, (vegetables) salted just overnight"
    },
    {
      "question": "賑わす",
      "answer": "にぎわす",
      "meaning": "to enliven, to liven up, to cause a stir in (e.g. the newspapers), to hit (the front page, headlines"
    },
    {
      "question": "迎賓館",
      "answer": "げいひんかん",
      "meaning": "reception hall (esp. for visiting state dignitaries), guest house, State Guest House (esp. Akasaka p"
    },
    {
      "question": "名剣",
      "answer": "めいけん",
      "meaning": "famous sword, excellent sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "空転",
      "answer": "くうてん",
      "meaning": "racing (an engine), idling (an engine), going in circles (esp. argument, discussion, etc.), spinning"
    },
    {
      "question": "植物園",
      "answer": "しょくぶつえん",
      "meaning": "botanical garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙吹雪",
      "answer": "かみふぶき",
      "meaning": "confetti, ticker tape"
    },
    {
      "question": "西洋風",
      "answer": "せいようふう",
      "meaning": "western style"
    },
    {
      "question": "物忘れ",
      "answer": "ものわすれ",
      "meaning": "forgetfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち得る",
      "answer": "かちえる",
      "meaning": "to achieve, to win, to gain, to attain"
    },
    {
      "question": "選り好み",
      "answer": "よりごのみ,えりごのみ",
      "meaning": "being particular about, fastidious"
    },
    {
      "question": "詞",
      "answer": "ことば,し",
      "meaning": "language, dialect, word, words, phrase, term, expression, remark, speech, (manner of) speaking, lear"
    },
    {
      "question": "急死",
      "answer": "きゅうし",
      "meaning": "sudden death"
    },
    {
      "question": "来襲",
      "answer": "らいしゅう",
      "meaning": "raid, attack, invasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "匂い立つ",
      "answer": "においたつ",
      "meaning": "to be fragrant, to give out a smell, to be enveloped in a smell, to be radiant, to be attractive"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶番劇",
      "answer": "ちゃばんげき",
      "meaning": "burlesque, low comedy, farce"
    },
    {
      "question": "乾き",
      "answer": "かわき",
      "meaning": "drying, dryness"
    },
    {
      "question": "年の功",
      "answer": "としのこう",
      "meaning": "wisdom of age, sagacity of one's years, old-man's wisdom"
    },
    {
      "question": "暮す",
      "answer": "くらす",
      "meaning": "to live, to get along, to spend (time)"
    },
    {
      "question": "開会式",
      "answer": "かいかいしき",
      "meaning": "opening ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "柘榴",
      "answer": "ざくろ,せきりゅう",
      "meaning": "pomegranate (Punica granatum)"
    },
    {
      "question": "握り飯",
      "answer": "にぎりめし",
      "meaning": "rice ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "検挙",
      "answer": "けんきょ",
      "meaning": "arrest, roundup"
    },
    {
      "question": "救護班",
      "answer": "きゅうごはん",
      "meaning": "relief squad, rescue party"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り針",
      "answer": "つりばり",
      "meaning": "fish hook"
    },
    {
      "question": "前腕",
      "answer": "ぜんわん,まえうで",
      "meaning": "forearm"
    },
    {
      "question": "実益",
      "answer": "じつえき",
      "meaning": "actual profit, practical use, benefit"
    },
    {
      "question": "風物詩",
      "answer": "ふうぶつし",
      "meaning": "thing that reminds one of a particular season, poem about natural scenery, poem about a particular s"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぽっと出",
      "answer": "ぽっとで",
      "meaning": "fresh off the farm, inexperienced"
    },
    {
      "question": "夫婦仲",
      "answer": "ふうふなか",
      "meaning": "conjugal relations, conjugal affection"
    },
    {
      "question": "女人",
      "answer": "にょにん,じょじん",
      "meaning": "woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "見做す",
      "answer": "みなす",
      "meaning": "to consider as, to regard (as equivalent), to deem (as), to equate"
    },
    {
      "question": "複写",
      "answer": "ふくしゃ",
      "meaning": "copying, duplication, reproduction, copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "内偵",
      "answer": "ないてい",
      "meaning": "secret investigation, private enquiry, private inquiry, reconnaissance, scouting"
    },
    {
      "question": "過労死",
      "answer": "かろうし",
      "meaning": "karoshi, death from overwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "真ん丸",
      "answer": "まんまる",
      "meaning": "perfect circle, cute"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶柱",
      "answer": "ちゃばしら",
      "meaning": "upright-floating tea stalk (considered a lucky omen)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白玉",
      "answer": "しらたま,はくぎょく",
      "meaning": "white gem (esp. a pearl), rice flour dumpling, white-flowered camellia, white gem"
    },
    {
      "question": "本州",
      "answer": "ほんしゅう",
      "meaning": "Honshū (largest of the four main islands of Japan), Honshu"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠乗り",
      "answer": "とおのり",
      "meaning": "long ride"
    },
    {
      "question": "思慕",
      "answer": "しぼ",
      "meaning": "yearning, longing for, deep affection"
    },
    {
      "question": "天草",
      "answer": "てんぐさ",
      "meaning": "any red algae in the family Gelidiaceae (esp. Gelidium crinale)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賜",
      "answer": "たまもの",
      "meaning": "gift, boon, (good) result, fruit (e.g. of one's efforts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "千切り",
      "answer": "せんぎり",
      "meaning": "finely cut strips (of vegetables), shredded vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "発汗",
      "answer": "はっかん",
      "meaning": "sweating, perspiration, sudation, hidrosis, diaphoresis"
    },
    {
      "question": "好成績",
      "answer": "こうせいせき",
      "meaning": "good results"
    },
    {
      "question": "脂ぎる",
      "answer": "あぶらぎる",
      "meaning": "to become greasy, to become oily, to be loud and garish"
    },
    {
      "question": "白日",
      "answer": "はくじつ",
      "meaning": "bright sunshine, broad daylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "座長",
      "answer": "ざちょう",
      "meaning": "chairman, leader of a troupe, proprietor of a theatrical company"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸薬",
      "answer": "がんやく",
      "meaning": "pill"
    },
    {
      "question": "図案",
      "answer": "ずあん",
      "meaning": "design, sketch"
    },
    {
      "question": "延長戦",
      "answer": "えんちょうせん",
      "meaning": "extended game, overtime, extra innings (baseball)"
    },
    {
      "question": "笠に着る",
      "answer": "かさにきる",
      "meaning": "to wear the mantle of (borrowed) authority and misuse it"
    },
    {
      "question": "調教師",
      "answer": "ちょうきょうし",
      "meaning": "animal trainer"
    },
    {
      "question": "坊さん",
      "answer": "ぼうさん",
      "meaning": "Buddhist priest, monk, boy"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱弱しい",
      "answer": "よわよわしい",
      "meaning": "frail, slender, feminine"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕立て",
      "answer": "うでたて,うでだて",
      "meaning": "push-up, showing off one's physical strength, relying on one's physical strength in a fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り皿",
      "answer": "とりざら",
      "meaning": "individual plate, single individual's small dish on which food taken from shared serving dishes is p"
    },
    {
      "question": "格ゲー",
      "answer": "かくゲー",
      "meaning": "fighting game (usu. one-on-one)"
    },
    {
      "question": "起訴",
      "answer": "きそ",
      "meaning": "prosecution, indictment"
    },
    {
      "question": "番う",
      "answer": "つがう",
      "meaning": "to pair with, to pair up, to pair off"
    },
    {
      "question": "時効",
      "answer": "じこう",
      "meaning": "statute of limitations, lapse of rights after a period of time, prescription (including acquisitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "我が物",
      "answer": "わがもの",
      "meaning": "one's own property, possessions"
    },
    {
      "question": "追究",
      "answer": "ついきゅう",
      "meaning": "investigation (e.g. academically, of the unknown), close inquiry (enquiry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人斬り",
      "answer": "ひときり",
      "meaning": "assassination"
    },
    {
      "question": "私設",
      "answer": "しせつ",
      "meaning": "private"
    },
    {
      "question": "便秘",
      "answer": "べんぴ",
      "meaning": "constipation"
    },
    {
      "question": "求人",
      "answer": "きゅうじん",
      "meaning": "recruiting, job offer, job vacancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "開会",
      "answer": "かいかい",
      "meaning": "opening of a meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "半永久的",
      "answer": "はんえいきゅうてき",
      "meaning": "semipermanent"
    },
    {
      "question": "金閣",
      "answer": "きんかく",
      "meaning": "golden pavilion"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹ごなし",
      "answer": "はらごなし",
      "meaning": "exercise to help digestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "蝕",
      "answer": "しょく",
      "meaning": "eclipse (solar, lunar, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "校章",
      "answer": "こうしょう",
      "meaning": "school badge, school emblem, school insignia"
    },
    {
      "question": "連覇",
      "answer": "れんぱ",
      "meaning": "successive championships"
    },
    {
      "question": "照り焼き",
      "answer": "てりやき",
      "meaning": "teriyaki (meat or fish marinated in sweet soy sauce and broiled)"
    },
    {
      "question": "同輩",
      "answer": "どうはい",
      "meaning": "fellows, comrade, colleague, one's equal"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘶き",
      "answer": "いななき",
      "meaning": "neigh, whinny, bray"
    },
    {
      "question": "城外",
      "answer": "じょうがい",
      "meaning": "outside a castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "水泡",
      "answer": "すいほう,みなわ",
      "meaning": "foam, bubble, nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "情感",
      "answer": "じょうかん",
      "meaning": "feeling, sensitivity, emotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜻蛉",
      "answer": "とんぼ,とんぼう,せいれい",
      "meaning": "dragonfly, damselfly"
    },
    {
      "question": "外務省",
      "answer": "がいむしょう",
      "meaning": "Ministry of Foreign Affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "内線",
      "answer": "ないせん",
      "meaning": "phone extension, indoor wiring, inner line"
    },
    {
      "question": "友愛",
      "answer": "ゆうあい",
      "meaning": "fraternity, friendship"
    },
    {
      "question": "油断大敵",
      "answer": "ゆだんたいてき",
      "meaning": "don't let your guard down, carelessness is the great enemy, danger comes soonest when it is despised"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫除け",
      "answer": "むしよけ",
      "meaning": "insecticide, insect repellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "急患",
      "answer": "きゅうかん",
      "meaning": "emergency case"
    },
    {
      "question": "調印",
      "answer": "ちょういん",
      "meaning": "signature, signing, sealing"
    },
    {
      "question": "錐",
      "answer": "きり,すい",
      "meaning": "drill, gimlet, awl, auger, cone, pyramid"
    },
    {
      "question": "才色兼備",
      "answer": "さいしょくけんび",
      "meaning": "(a woman) being gifted with both intelligence and beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘ったれ",
      "answer": "あまったれ",
      "meaning": "overreliance on others, excessive babyishness, spoiled person (esp. child)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ロシア語",
      "answer": "ロシアご",
      "meaning": "Russian (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が短い",
      "answer": "きがみじかい",
      "meaning": "quick-tempered, having little patience, impatient"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪女",
      "answer": "ゆきおんな",
      "meaning": "yuki-onna (spirit in Japanese folklore), snow woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "本選",
      "answer": "ほんせん",
      "meaning": "final selection"
    },
    {
      "question": "帳面",
      "answer": "ちょうめん",
      "meaning": "notebook, account book, register"
    },
    {
      "question": "生徒指導",
      "answer": "せいとしどう",
      "meaning": "student guidance, student counseling"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉声",
      "answer": "にくせい",
      "meaning": "natural voice (without a microphone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び付く",
      "answer": "とびつく",
      "meaning": "to jump at, to be attracted by"
    },
    {
      "question": "名付け親",
      "answer": "なづけおや",
      "meaning": "godparent, first person to give something its name"
    },
    {
      "question": "宙吊り",
      "answer": "ちゅうづり",
      "meaning": "hanging in midair, suspended in midair, midair stunt, aerial stunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "謝辞",
      "answer": "しゃじ",
      "meaning": "thanks, apology"
    },
    {
      "question": "如何様",
      "answer": "いかさま,いかよう",
      "meaning": "fraud, trickery, hoax, swindle, counterfeit, fake, surely, absolutely, certainly, indeed, what sort"
    },
    {
      "question": "握らす",
      "answer": "にぎらす",
      "meaning": "to let (someone) take hold of your hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "竜胆",
      "answer": "りんどう,りゅうたん",
      "meaning": "gentian (Gentiana scabra var. buergeri), autumn bellflower"
    },
    {
      "question": "油絵",
      "answer": "あぶらえ",
      "meaning": "oil painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡航",
      "answer": "とこう",
      "meaning": "voyage, passage, travelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "潮騒",
      "answer": "しおさい",
      "meaning": "sea roar"
    },
    {
      "question": "打席",
      "answer": "だせき",
      "meaning": "batter's box, one's turn at bat"
    },
    {
      "question": "金メダル",
      "answer": "きんメダル",
      "meaning": "gold medal"
    },
    {
      "question": "保険金",
      "answer": "ほけんきん",
      "meaning": "insurance payout, insurance money"
    },
    {
      "question": "変死",
      "answer": "へんし",
      "meaning": "unnatural death, accidental death, violent death"
    },
    {
      "question": "万策",
      "answer": "ばんさく",
      "meaning": "all means"
    },
    {
      "question": "茨の道",
      "answer": "いばらのみち",
      "meaning": "thorny path"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅舎",
      "answer": "えきしゃ",
      "meaning": "station building"
    },
    {
      "question": "機動隊",
      "answer": "きどうたい",
      "meaning": "riot police, riot squad"
    },
    {
      "question": "希少性",
      "answer": "きしょうせい",
      "meaning": "scarcity, rarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "三半規管",
      "answer": "さんはんきかん",
      "meaning": "semicircular canals"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き直す",
      "answer": "ききなおす",
      "meaning": "to listen again, to ask again"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉巧み",
      "answer": "ことばたくみ,ことばだくみ",
      "meaning": "skillful words, deceitful words, glibness"
    },
    {
      "question": "全集",
      "answer": "ぜんしゅう",
      "meaning": "complete works, complete collection, complete series"
    },
    {
      "question": "染色",
      "answer": "せんしょく",
      "meaning": "dyeing, staining, dyed colour (color)"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗幕",
      "answer": "あんまく",
      "meaning": "blackout curtain"
    },
    {
      "question": "前転",
      "answer": "ぜんてん",
      "meaning": "forward somersault, forward roll"
    },
    {
      "question": "義理立て",
      "answer": "ぎりだて",
      "meaning": "doing one's duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "和紙",
      "answer": "わし,わがみ",
      "meaning": "washi, Japanese paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚劣",
      "answer": "ぐれつ",
      "meaning": "foolishness, stupidity, silliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "端折る",
      "answer": "はしょる,はしおる",
      "meaning": "to tuck up (e.g. skirt), to abridge, to cut short"
    },
    {
      "question": "定説",
      "answer": "ていせつ",
      "meaning": "established theory, accepted opinion, accepted explanation"
    },
    {
      "question": "穢い",
      "answer": "きたない",
      "meaning": "dirty, filthy, foul, unclean, disordered, messy, untidy, poor (e.g. handwriting), indecent (language"
    },
    {
      "question": "人造人間",
      "answer": "じんぞうにんげん",
      "meaning": "android, artificial human, robot"
    },
    {
      "question": "万象",
      "answer": "ばんしょう",
      "meaning": "all creation, all nature, all the universe"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾痕",
      "answer": "だんこん",
      "meaning": "bullet hole, bullet mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "対人関係",
      "answer": "たいじんかんけい",
      "meaning": "personal relations"
    },
    {
      "question": "復学",
      "answer": "ふくがく",
      "meaning": "return to school"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰",
      "answer": "つめ,づめ",
      "meaning": "stuffing, packing, end (esp. the foot of a bridge), lowest-ranking guest at tea ceremony, tea master"
    },
    {
      "question": "文体",
      "answer": "ぶんたい",
      "meaning": "literary style, form of (written) language (e.g. classical, modern)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦断",
      "answer": "じゅうだん",
      "meaning": "running through (north-south), cutting across, travelling across, cutting vertically, sectioning lon"
    },
    {
      "question": "大局",
      "answer": "たいきょく",
      "meaning": "general situation, whole situation, larger picture, main point, overall situation of a game of go"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神科",
      "answer": "せいしんか",
      "meaning": "psychiatry"
    },
    {
      "question": "想念",
      "answer": "そうねん",
      "meaning": "thought, idea, conception"
    },
    {
      "question": "回頭",
      "answer": "かいとう",
      "meaning": "turning round (a ship), changing course, veering"
    },
    {
      "question": "遣る",
      "answer": "やる",
      "meaning": "to do, to undertake, to perform, to play (a game), to study, to send, to dispatch, to despatch, to p"
    },
    {
      "question": "舵取り",
      "answer": "かじとり",
      "meaning": "steering, helmsman, coxswain, guidance, leadership, leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "罅",
      "answer": "ひび",
      "meaning": "crack, fissure, rift, split, chaps, skin fissure"
    },
    {
      "question": "友誼",
      "answer": "ゆうぎ",
      "meaning": "friendship, friendly relations, fellowship"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦にする",
      "answer": "くにする",
      "meaning": "to worry"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔役",
      "answer": "かおやく",
      "meaning": "influential man, boss"
    },
    {
      "question": "最敬礼",
      "answer": "さいけいれい",
      "meaning": "a respectful bow"
    },
    {
      "question": "下草",
      "answer": "したくさ,したぐさ",
      "meaning": "undergrowth, weeds beneath a tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "強権",
      "answer": "きょうけん",
      "meaning": "strong power of the state, iron fist, heavy hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃淡",
      "answer": "のうたん",
      "meaning": "light and shade, shade (of colour, color), depth (of flavor), complexity, strength and weakness (of"
    },
    {
      "question": "養母",
      "answer": "ようぼ",
      "meaning": "foster mother, adoptive mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "所領",
      "answer": "しょりょう",
      "meaning": "territory"
    },
    {
      "question": "活性",
      "answer": "かっせい",
      "meaning": "active"
    },
    {
      "question": "前任",
      "answer": "ぜんにん",
      "meaning": "former (incumbent), predecessor"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖都",
      "answer": "せいと",
      "meaning": "Holy City (e.g. Jerusalem, Mecca)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賽銭箱",
      "answer": "さいせんばこ",
      "meaning": "offertory box"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕",
      "answer": "し",
      "meaning": "official, civil service"
    },
    {
      "question": "咽喉",
      "answer": "いんこう",
      "meaning": "throat"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐女子",
      "answer": "ふじょし",
      "meaning": "woman who likes comics depicting male homosexual love"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳栓",
      "answer": "みみせん,じせん",
      "meaning": "earplug (for protection against noise or water), earplug (traditional jewellery worn in the earlobe,"
    },
    {
      "question": "堆積",
      "answer": "たいせき",
      "meaning": "accumulation, pile, heap, sedimentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "入金",
      "answer": "にゅうきん",
      "meaning": "deposit, payment, money received, money due"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き詰る",
      "answer": "いきづまる,ゆきづまる",
      "meaning": "to come to a dead end, to come to a standstill, to reach a deadlock, to reach an impasse, to reach a"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝記",
      "answer": "でんき",
      "meaning": "biography, life story"
    },
    {
      "question": "大判",
      "answer": "おおばん",
      "meaning": "large size (paper, book, etc.), ōban, large oval gold coin used in the Edo period"
    },
    {
      "question": "完勝",
      "answer": "かんしょう",
      "meaning": "complete victory, total victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "姉や",
      "answer": "ねえや",
      "meaning": "young lady (in ref. to a maid, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み合う",
      "answer": "くみあう",
      "meaning": "to form a partnership or association, to join together, to grapple with"
    },
    {
      "question": "臆す",
      "answer": "おくす",
      "meaning": "to be hesitant, to feel timid"
    },
    {
      "question": "敬服",
      "answer": "けいふく",
      "meaning": "great admiration, deep respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "切に",
      "answer": "せつに",
      "meaning": "eagerly, earnestly, ardently"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き手",
      "answer": "ききて",
      "meaning": "hearer, listener, audience, interviewer, questioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "御堂",
      "answer": "みどう",
      "meaning": "enshrinement hall (of a buddha), temple, cathedral (esp. Catholic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "波形",
      "answer": "なみがた,はけい",
      "meaning": "wavy form, ripply shape, waveform"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗方",
      "answer": "あらかた",
      "meaning": "mostly, almost, nearly, for the most part, roughly, approximately, about"
    },
    {
      "question": "横着",
      "answer": "おうちゃく",
      "meaning": "laziness, shirking, impudent, brazenly dishonest"
    },
    {
      "question": "早送り",
      "answer": "はやおくり",
      "meaning": "fast forward (e.g. VCR, tape deck, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "断ずる",
      "answer": "だんずる",
      "meaning": "to decide, to determine, to judge"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚遇",
      "answer": "こうぐう",
      "meaning": "cordial welcome, hearty welcome, kind treatment, hospitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務官",
      "answer": "じむかん",
      "meaning": "administrative official, secretary, commissioner"
    },
    {
      "question": "征伐",
      "answer": "せいばつ",
      "meaning": "conquest, subjugation, overcoming, chastisement, punishment, punitive expedition"
    },
    {
      "question": "超特急",
      "answer": "ちょうとっきゅう",
      "meaning": "super express"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝儀",
      "answer": "しゅうぎ",
      "meaning": "celebration, celebratory event, wedding ceremony, congratulatory gift, tip, gratuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "血行",
      "answer": "けっこう",
      "meaning": "circulation (of the blood)"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲火",
      "answer": "ほうか",
      "meaning": "gunfire, fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "電極",
      "answer": "でんきょく",
      "meaning": "electrode"
    },
    {
      "question": "無形",
      "answer": "むけい",
      "meaning": "abstract, immaterial, moral, spiritual, intangible"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑心",
      "answer": "ぎしん",
      "meaning": "doubt, suspicion, fear, apprehension"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒稼ぎ",
      "answer": "あらかせぎ",
      "meaning": "making a killing, making easy money, robbery"
    },
    {
      "question": "作為的",
      "answer": "さくいてき",
      "meaning": "intentional, deliberate, contrived, artificial"
    },
    {
      "question": "折紙",
      "answer": "おりがみ",
      "meaning": "origami, art of paper folding, hallmark, certificate of authenticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "一念",
      "answer": "いちねん",
      "meaning": "determined purpose, an incredibly short span of time (i.e. the time occupied by a single thought), a"
    },
    {
      "question": "希有",
      "answer": "けう,きゆう",
      "meaning": "rare, uncommon"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂れ目",
      "answer": "たれめ",
      "meaning": "drooping eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "ペン先",
      "answer": "ペンさき",
      "meaning": "pen nibs"
    },
    {
      "question": "血相",
      "answer": "けっそう",
      "meaning": "expression, looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉書",
      "answer": "はがき",
      "meaning": "postcard, memo, note, card"
    },
    {
      "question": "雹",
      "answer": "ひょう",
      "meaning": "hail (esp. hailballs 5 mm or greater)"
    },
    {
      "question": "入信",
      "answer": "にゅうしん",
      "meaning": "entering a faith, joining a religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "三連",
      "answer": "さんれん",
      "meaning": "three-stranded"
    },
    {
      "question": "深手",
      "answer": "ふかで",
      "meaning": "severe wound, serious wound, gash"
    },
    {
      "question": "髄",
      "answer": "ずい,なずき",
      "meaning": "medulla, marrow, pith, brain, skull, head"
    },
    {
      "question": "百八十度",
      "answer": "ひゃくはちじゅうど",
      "meaning": "180 degrees, complete change"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪魔立て",
      "answer": "じゃまだて",
      "meaning": "deliberate hindrance, obstruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "宴席",
      "answer": "えんせき",
      "meaning": "banquet, dinner party"
    },
    {
      "question": "水玉",
      "answer": "みずたま",
      "meaning": "drop of water, polka dots"
    },
    {
      "question": "齧り付く",
      "answer": "かぶりつく,かじりつく",
      "meaning": "to bite into, to sink one's teeth into, to stick to, to cling to, to hold on to"
    },
    {
      "question": "校風",
      "answer": "こうふう",
      "meaning": "school tradition, school customs, school spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "徹頭徹尾",
      "answer": "てっとうてつび",
      "meaning": "thoroughly, through and through"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘導尋問",
      "answer": "ゆうどうじんもん",
      "meaning": "leading question"
    },
    {
      "question": "縮図",
      "answer": "しゅくず",
      "meaning": "reduced drawing, miniature copy, microcosm, microcosmos"
    },
    {
      "question": "索",
      "answer": "さく,ソー,ソウ",
      "meaning": "rope, cord, counter for bamboo tiles"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀杏",
      "answer": "いちょう,ぎんなん",
      "meaning": "ginkgo (Ginkgo biloba), gingko, maidenhair tree, ginkgo nut, gingko nut"
    },
    {
      "question": "三つ子",
      "answer": "みつご",
      "meaning": "three-year-old, triplets"
    },
    {
      "question": "連係",
      "answer": "れんけい",
      "meaning": "connection, linking, linkage, link"
    },
    {
      "question": "小者",
      "answer": "こもの",
      "meaning": "young person, servant, errand boy in a samurai family, person of lowly status"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒手空拳",
      "answer": "としゅくうけん",
      "meaning": "empty-handed, with nothing to start with, without capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "否や",
      "answer": "いなや",
      "meaning": "as soon as, no sooner than, one way or another, objection"
    },
    {
      "question": "結び付く",
      "answer": "むすびつく",
      "meaning": "to be related, to be connected, to be joined together, to result in, to lead to, to bring about"
    },
    {
      "question": "秀",
      "answer": "しゅう",
      "meaning": "preeminence, supremacy, distinction, excellence"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲口",
      "answer": "ほうこう",
      "meaning": "muzzle (of a gun)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大恩",
      "answer": "だいおん",
      "meaning": "great debt of gratitude, great obligation"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁舌",
      "answer": "べんぜつ",
      "meaning": "speech, eloquence, manner of speaking, manner of expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "残高",
      "answer": "ざんだか",
      "meaning": "(bank) balance, remainder"
    },
    {
      "question": "征",
      "answer": "しちょう",
      "meaning": "ladder (in go)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖歌隊",
      "answer": "せいかたい",
      "meaning": "choir"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒檀",
      "answer": "こくたん",
      "meaning": "ebony"
    },
    {
      "question": "演歌",
      "answer": "えんか",
      "meaning": "enka, traditional-style Japanese popular ballad"
    },
    {
      "question": "模造",
      "answer": "もぞう",
      "meaning": "imitation, counterfeit, fake, sham, ersatz (object)"
    },
    {
      "question": "模写",
      "answer": "もしゃ",
      "meaning": "copy (of the real thing), copying, reproduction, tracing"
    },
    {
      "question": "献金",
      "answer": "けんきん",
      "meaning": "donation, contribution, offering"
    },
    {
      "question": "田園",
      "answer": "でんえん,でんおん",
      "meaning": "the country, countryside, rural districts, cultivated land, fields"
    },
    {
      "question": "席順",
      "answer": "せきじゅん",
      "meaning": "seating order"
    },
    {
      "question": "儀礼的",
      "answer": "ぎれいてき",
      "meaning": "formal, courteous, ritual, ritualistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "三振",
      "answer": "さんしん",
      "meaning": "strikeout, strike out, fanning out"
    },
    {
      "question": "正室",
      "answer": "せいしつ",
      "meaning": "legal wife (of a noble) (as opposed to a concubine), room for receiving guests, heir, successor"
    },
    {
      "question": "薫り",
      "answer": "かおり",
      "meaning": "aroma, fragrance, scent, smell"
    },
    {
      "question": "推挙",
      "answer": "すいきょ",
      "meaning": "recommendation (of a person for a position), nomination"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚類",
      "answer": "ぎょるい",
      "meaning": "fish, fishes"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬨の声",
      "answer": "ときのこえ",
      "meaning": "war cry, battle cry"
    },
    {
      "question": "惰弱",
      "answer": "だじゃく",
      "meaning": "apathetic, lackadaisical, spiritless, gutless, weak-willed, unenterprising, enervated, effete, physi"
    },
    {
      "question": "前屈み",
      "answer": "まえかがみ",
      "meaning": "slouch"
    },
    {
      "question": "接着",
      "answer": "せっちゃく",
      "meaning": "adhesion, glueing, gluing, bonding, binding, adhering, fastening"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち所",
      "answer": "うちどころ",
      "meaning": "spot (where one was hit)"
    },
    {
      "question": "百足",
      "answer": "むかで,ひゃくそく",
      "meaning": "centipede"
    },
    {
      "question": "囲炉裏",
      "answer": "いろり",
      "meaning": "sunken hearth, sunken fireplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "御手",
      "answer": "おて",
      "meaning": "hand, arm, handwriting, penmanship, 'shake' (command to have a dog place its paw in your hand)"
    },
    {
      "question": "陣頭指揮",
      "answer": "じんとうしき",
      "meaning": "taking command of a corps in a battle, command exercised by the leader of a group"
    },
    {
      "question": "兎も角",
      "answer": "ともかく",
      "meaning": "anyhow, anyway, somehow or other, generally speaking, in any case, be that as it may, apart from ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "内紛",
      "answer": "ないふん",
      "meaning": "domestic discord, internal discord, internal strife, internal struggle, infighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "先払い",
      "answer": "さきばらい",
      "meaning": "payment in advance, advance payment, prepayment, payment on delivery (e.g. business-reply mail, coll"
    },
    {
      "question": "大太刀",
      "answer": "おおだち,おおたち",
      "meaning": "extra-long sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "猟銃",
      "answer": "りょうじゅう",
      "meaning": "hunting gun, sportsgun"
    },
    {
      "question": "地層",
      "answer": "ちそう",
      "meaning": "stratum, geological formation, layer, bed (coal, gravel, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛おしむ",
      "answer": "いとおしむ",
      "meaning": "to love, to be attached to, to cherish, to caress"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩行者",
      "answer": "ほこうしゃ",
      "meaning": "pedestrian, walker"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝負服",
      "answer": "しょうぶふく",
      "meaning": "jockey's racing uniform, one's best clothes (esp. for women), normally put aside for important meeti"
    },
    {
      "question": "偵察機",
      "answer": "ていさつき",
      "meaning": "reconnaissance plane, spy plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿場",
      "answer": "しゅくば",
      "meaning": "relay station (esp. on Edo-period highway), post station, stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭け金",
      "answer": "かけきん",
      "meaning": "stakes, bet"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴れ馬",
      "answer": "あばれうま",
      "meaning": "restive horse, runaway horse, out of control horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘酒",
      "answer": "あまざけ",
      "meaning": "sweet half sake, sweet drink made from fermented rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "死去",
      "answer": "しきょ",
      "meaning": "death"
    },
    {
      "question": "全壊",
      "answer": "ぜんかい",
      "meaning": "complete destruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "働き手",
      "answer": "はたらきて",
      "meaning": "worker, breadwinner, supporter, able person, able man, productive worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏ん切り",
      "answer": "ふんぎり",
      "meaning": "determination, decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "反面教師",
      "answer": "はんめんきょうし",
      "meaning": "bad example from which one can learn, good example of what not to do (esp. how not to behave), negat"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳴子",
      "answer": "なるこ",
      "meaning": "clapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "加盟",
      "answer": "かめい",
      "meaning": "joining (an association, agreement, etc.), participation, affiliation, accession"
    },
    {
      "question": "舐る",
      "answer": "ねぶる",
      "meaning": "to lick"
    },
    {
      "question": "運送",
      "answer": "うんそう",
      "meaning": "transport, freight, shipping"
    },
    {
      "question": "心の臓",
      "answer": "こころのぞう",
      "meaning": "heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り回し",
      "answer": "とりまわし",
      "meaning": "(ease of) handling, operation, maneuverability, arrangement (of pipes, wires, etc.), layout, routing"
    },
    {
      "question": "順繰り",
      "answer": "じゅんぐり",
      "meaning": "in turns, alternately, in order"
    },
    {
      "question": "生中継",
      "answer": "なまちゅうけい",
      "meaning": "live broadcast (radio, TV), live coverage"
    },
    {
      "question": "公道",
      "answer": "こうどう",
      "meaning": "public road, highway, righteousness, justice, right path"
    },
    {
      "question": "強国",
      "answer": "きょうこく",
      "meaning": "strong nation, powerful country"
    },
    {
      "question": "不適格",
      "answer": "ふてきかく,ふてっかく",
      "meaning": "disqualification, unfitness, noncompliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔が広い",
      "answer": "かおがひろい",
      "meaning": "well connected, well known, having a large, diverse circle of acquaintances"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関室",
      "answer": "きかんしつ",
      "meaning": "engine room"
    },
    {
      "question": "詐称",
      "answer": "さしょう",
      "meaning": "misrepresentation, false statement"
    },
    {
      "question": "内陸",
      "answer": "ないりく",
      "meaning": "inland"
    },
    {
      "question": "岐路",
      "answer": "きろ",
      "meaning": "forked road, crossroads"
    },
    {
      "question": "無月",
      "answer": "むげつ",
      "meaning": "moonless sky (poetic usage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "羅針盤",
      "answer": "らしんばん",
      "meaning": "compass"
    },
    {
      "question": "貫",
      "answer": "かん,ぬき",
      "meaning": "kan (obs. unit of weight, approx. 3.75 kg, 8.3 lb), kan (obs. unit of currency, equiv. to 1000 mon i"
    },
    {
      "question": "間引き",
      "answer": "まびき",
      "meaning": "thinning out, pruning, culling, curtailing, sub-sampling (e.g. video frames, signals), infanticide"
    },
    {
      "question": "若輩",
      "answer": "じゃくはい",
      "meaning": "young person, inexperienced person, novice"
    },
    {
      "question": "氷の刃",
      "answer": "こおりのやいば",
      "meaning": "gleaming sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "基点",
      "answer": "きてん",
      "meaning": "datum point, cardinal point, reference point, origin"
    },
    {
      "question": "交配",
      "answer": "こうはい",
      "meaning": "mating, crossbreeding, cross-fertilization, cross-fertilisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "向かい風",
      "answer": "むかいかぜ",
      "meaning": "headwind, head wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "即物的",
      "answer": "そくぶつてき",
      "meaning": "practical, matter-of-fact, realistic, utilitarian, pragmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "性愛",
      "answer": "せいあい",
      "meaning": "sexual love, eros"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番星",
      "answer": "いちばんぼし",
      "meaning": "the first star to appear in the evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "車中",
      "answer": "しゃちゅう",
      "meaning": "in a train (car, bus, etc.), on a train"
    },
    {
      "question": "期待値",
      "answer": "きたいち",
      "meaning": "expected value, expectation value, expectation"
    },
    {
      "question": "高じる",
      "answer": "こうじる",
      "meaning": "to grow in intensity, to be aggravated, to get worse, to develop"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗黒時代",
      "answer": "あんこくじだい",
      "meaning": "Dark Ages, dark age"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉感",
      "answer": "にっかん,にくかん",
      "meaning": "sexual feeling, carnal desire, physical feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "短慮",
      "answer": "たんりょ",
      "meaning": "imprudence, quick temper"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟達",
      "answer": "じゅくたつ",
      "meaning": "mastery"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制送還",
      "answer": "きょうせいそうかん",
      "meaning": "forced repatriation, deportation"
    },
    {
      "question": "国主",
      "answer": "こくしゅ",
      "meaning": "king, sovereign, daimyo"
    },
    {
      "question": "従弟",
      "answer": "じゅうてい,いとこ",
      "meaning": "cousin (younger male)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追走",
      "answer": "ついそう",
      "meaning": "chasing, chase"
    },
    {
      "question": "決済",
      "answer": "けっさい",
      "meaning": "settlement, payment of account"
    },
    {
      "question": "植民",
      "answer": "しょくみん",
      "meaning": "colonization, colonisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "初春",
      "answer": "しょしゅん,はつはる",
      "meaning": "beginning of spring, first month of the lunar calendar, New Year"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕末",
      "answer": "ばくまつ",
      "meaning": "closing days of the Tokugawa shogunate, end of Edo era"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒パン",
      "answer": "くろパン",
      "meaning": "brown bread, rye bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "指笛",
      "answer": "ゆびぶえ",
      "meaning": "whistling through one's fingers, whistle made by sticking one's fingers in one's mouth and blowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜粋",
      "answer": "ばっすい",
      "meaning": "extract, excerpt, selection"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝負事",
      "answer": "しょうぶごと",
      "meaning": "gambling, competition, game (of chance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "電池切れ",
      "answer": "でんちぎれ",
      "meaning": "running out of battery, battery depletion, going flat, going dead, loss of energy, depletion of stam"
    },
    {
      "question": "航法",
      "answer": "こうほう",
      "meaning": "sailing, navigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "態々",
      "answer": "わざわざ",
      "meaning": "expressly, especially, taking the trouble (to do), going to the trouble of (doing), going out of one"
    },
    {
      "question": "窄める",
      "answer": "すぼめる,つぼめる",
      "meaning": "to make narrower, to shut (an umbrella), to shrug (one's shoulders), to purse (one's lips)"
    },
    {
      "question": "強壮",
      "answer": "きょうそう",
      "meaning": "able-bodied, robust, sturdy, strong"
    },
    {
      "question": "沖合",
      "answer": "おきあい",
      "meaning": "off the coast, offshore, out at sea"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛酸",
      "answer": "しんさん",
      "meaning": "hardships, privation"
    },
    {
      "question": "点す",
      "answer": "ともす,とぼす,さす",
      "meaning": "to light (a candle, lamp, etc.), to turn on (a light), to pour, to add (liquid), to serve (drinks),"
    },
    {
      "question": "適齢期",
      "answer": "てきれいき",
      "meaning": "suitable age (esp. for marriage), marriageable age"
    },
    {
      "question": "据え膳",
      "answer": "すえぜん",
      "meaning": "meal set before one, women's advances"
    },
    {
      "question": "超回復",
      "answer": "ちょうかいふく",
      "meaning": "supercompensation, overcompensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "阿修羅",
      "answer": "あしゅら,あすら",
      "meaning": "Asura, demigod, anti-god, titan, demigods that fight the Devas (gods) in Hindu mythology"
    },
    {
      "question": "淫蕩",
      "answer": "いんとう",
      "meaning": "dissipation, lewdness"
    },
    {
      "question": "宦官",
      "answer": "かんがん",
      "meaning": "eunuch"
    },
    {
      "question": "一向",
      "answer": "ひたすら,いっこう,ひたぶる",
      "meaning": "intently, single-mindedly, devotedly, solely, earnestly, with all one's heart, completely, absolutel"
    },
    {
      "question": "飴細工",
      "answer": "あめざいく",
      "meaning": "candy fashioned in human and animal forms"
    },
    {
      "question": "受講",
      "answer": "じゅこう",
      "meaning": "taking a lecture, attending a class, taking a course"
    },
    {
      "question": "渋",
      "answer": "しぶ",
      "meaning": "astringent (puckery) juice (of unripe persimmons)"
    },
    {
      "question": "擁立",
      "answer": "ようりつ",
      "meaning": "backing (for a position), giving support to, helping (someone) to a position"
    },
    {
      "question": "電話帳",
      "answer": "でんわちょう",
      "meaning": "telephone book, telephone directory"
    },
    {
      "question": "興行",
      "answer": "こうぎょう",
      "meaning": "show, performance, act, entertainment industry, show business"
    },
    {
      "question": "番頭",
      "answer": "ばんとう",
      "meaning": "(head) clerk"
    },
    {
      "question": "座面",
      "answer": "ざめん",
      "meaning": "seat (of a chair)"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤飯",
      "answer": "せきはん",
      "meaning": "red rice (beans and mochi) for auspicious occasions"
    },
    {
      "question": "宗家",
      "answer": "そうけ,そうか",
      "meaning": "head of family, originator"
    },
    {
      "question": "風音",
      "answer": "かざおと,かぜおと",
      "meaning": "sound of the wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "申",
      "answer": "さる",
      "meaning": "the Monkey (ninth sign of the Chinese zodiac), hour of the Monkey (around 4pm, 3-5pm, or 4-6pm), wes"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒼白い",
      "answer": "あおじろい",
      "meaning": "pale, pallid, bluish-white"
    },
    {
      "question": "常套句",
      "answer": "じょうとうく",
      "meaning": "conventional phrase, stock phrase, cliche, frequently used musical (guitar) phrase"
    },
    {
      "question": "出先",
      "answer": "でさき",
      "meaning": "one's destination"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き芋",
      "answer": "やきいも",
      "meaning": "roasted sweet potato, baked sweet potato"
    },
    {
      "question": "首魁",
      "answer": "しゅかい",
      "meaning": "forerunner, ringleader"
    },
    {
      "question": "撮影会",
      "answer": "さつえいかい",
      "meaning": "photography event, photo session, photo shoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "国教",
      "answer": "こっきょう",
      "meaning": "state religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "国名",
      "answer": "こくめい,くにな",
      "meaning": "country name, country or region name used for people (in the Heian period court)"
    },
    {
      "question": "少女趣味",
      "answer": "しょうじょしゅみ",
      "meaning": "(school) girlish taste (for things that are sweet, cute, romantic, etc.), interest in young girls (r"
    },
    {
      "question": "検察",
      "answer": "けんさつ",
      "meaning": "examination, investigation, prosecution"
    },
    {
      "question": "産声",
      "answer": "うぶごえ",
      "meaning": "first cry of a newborn baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "俄",
      "answer": "にわか",
      "meaning": "sudden, abrupt, unexpected, improvised, hasty, offhand, impromptu skit, bandwagon fan, fair-weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "高齢者",
      "answer": "こうれいしゃ",
      "meaning": "old person, old people"
    },
    {
      "question": "大流行",
      "answer": "だいりゅうこう",
      "meaning": "big craze, boom, popular trend, huge popularity, widespread contagion, large outbreak"
    },
    {
      "question": "不届き",
      "answer": "ふとどき",
      "meaning": "outrageous, reprehensible, rude, insolent, nefarious"
    },
    {
      "question": "神職",
      "answer": "しんしょく",
      "meaning": "Shinto priest, Shinto priesthood"
    },
    {
      "question": "記憶障害",
      "answer": "きおくしょうがい",
      "meaning": "defect of memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "怖々",
      "answer": "こわごわ",
      "meaning": "fearfully, timidly, cautiously, nervously"
    },
    {
      "question": "大回り",
      "answer": "おおまわり",
      "meaning": "wide turn, detour, the long way around"
    },
    {
      "question": "二度手間",
      "answer": "にどてま,にどでま",
      "meaning": "double effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し分",
      "answer": "もうしぶん",
      "meaning": "objection, shortcomings"
    },
    {
      "question": "若君",
      "answer": "わかぎみ",
      "meaning": "young lord or prince"
    },
    {
      "question": "全勝",
      "answer": "ぜんしょう",
      "meaning": "complete victory, winning a tournament with no losses"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸分かり",
      "answer": "まるわかり",
      "meaning": "understanding completely, understanding all there is to know"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏を取る",
      "answer": "うらをとる",
      "meaning": "to collect evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "暇を潰す",
      "answer": "ひまをつぶす",
      "meaning": "to waste time, to kill time"
    },
    {
      "question": "真綿",
      "answer": "まわた",
      "meaning": "silk floss, silk wadding"
    },
    {
      "question": "月影",
      "answer": "げつえい,つきかげ",
      "meaning": "moonlight, moon, moonbeams"
    },
    {
      "question": "窪む",
      "answer": "くぼむ",
      "meaning": "to cave in, to become depressed, to sink"
    },
    {
      "question": "知識欲",
      "answer": "ちしきよく",
      "meaning": "thirst for knowledge, intellectual thirst"
    },
    {
      "question": "徽章",
      "answer": "きしょう",
      "meaning": "medal, badge, insignia"
    },
    {
      "question": "外務",
      "answer": "がいむ",
      "meaning": "foreign affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴威",
      "answer": "ぼうい",
      "meaning": "tyranny, abuse of power, violence (e.g. of a storm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "干る",
      "answer": "ひる",
      "meaning": "to dry"
    },
    {
      "question": "別宅",
      "answer": "べったく",
      "meaning": "secondary residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "喪",
      "answer": "も,そう",
      "meaning": "mourning, calamity, misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "残暑",
      "answer": "ざんしょ",
      "meaning": "late summer heat (from Aug. 8 and onwards), lingering summer heat"
    },
    {
      "question": "醸す",
      "answer": "かもす",
      "meaning": "to brew (sake, etc.), to cause, to bring on, to bring about, to give rise to"
    },
    {
      "question": "渦巻き",
      "answer": "うずまき",
      "meaning": "whirlpool, eddy, coil"
    },
    {
      "question": "研究開発",
      "answer": "けんきゅうかいはつ",
      "meaning": "research and development, R&D"
    },
    {
      "question": "若い衆",
      "answer": "わかいしゅ,わかいしゅう",
      "meaning": "young man, youth, lad, servant boy, young shopboy"
    },
    {
      "question": "上り下り",
      "answer": "のぼりくだり,のぼりおり",
      "meaning": "rising and falling, going up and down"
    },
    {
      "question": "袖にする",
      "answer": "そでにする",
      "meaning": "to be cold (to), to ignore (someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "見納め",
      "answer": "みおさめ",
      "meaning": "last look, farewell look"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯖",
      "answer": "さば",
      "meaning": "mackerel (esp. the chub mackerel, Scomber japonicus), server (in an online game)"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷戦",
      "answer": "れいせん",
      "meaning": "cold war"
    },
    {
      "question": "個数",
      "answer": "こすう",
      "meaning": "number of articles, quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏様",
      "answer": "ほとけさま",
      "meaning": "a Buddha, deceased person"
    },
    {
      "question": "悔し涙",
      "answer": "くやしなみだ",
      "meaning": "tears of regret, bitter tears, vexation, chagrin"
    },
    {
      "question": "往生際",
      "answer": "おうじょうぎわ",
      "meaning": "brink of death, time to give up, knowing when to give up"
    },
    {
      "question": "垣",
      "answer": "かき",
      "meaning": "fence, hedge, barrier, wall, railing"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞台装置",
      "answer": "ぶたいそうち",
      "meaning": "stage setting"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵便物",
      "answer": "ゆうびんぶつ",
      "meaning": "mail, postal matter, postal item"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝書鳩",
      "answer": "でんしょばと",
      "meaning": "carrier pigeon, homing pigeon"
    },
    {
      "question": "澱み",
      "answer": "よどみ",
      "meaning": "stagnation, deposit, sediment, backwater, faltering, hesitation, pause"
    },
    {
      "question": "星間",
      "answer": "せいかん",
      "meaning": "interstellar"
    },
    {
      "question": "苗床",
      "answer": "なえどこ",
      "meaning": "seedbed, nursery, seed-plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "値上げ",
      "answer": "ねあげ",
      "meaning": "price hike, mark-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "脅し文句",
      "answer": "おどしもんく",
      "meaning": "threatening words"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉱",
      "answer": "あらがね,あらかね",
      "meaning": "ore"
    },
    {
      "question": "追体験",
      "answer": "ついたいけん",
      "meaning": "vicarious experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈鬱",
      "answer": "ちんうつ",
      "meaning": "melancholy, gloom, depression"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘲り",
      "answer": "あざけり",
      "meaning": "ridicule, scorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "船尾",
      "answer": "せんび",
      "meaning": "stern of a ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "謹製",
      "answer": "きんせい",
      "meaning": "carefully made, carefully produced, quality product, product made with care"
    },
    {
      "question": "美肌",
      "answer": "びはだ,びき",
      "meaning": "beautiful skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し渡す",
      "answer": "もうしわたす",
      "meaning": "to tell, to announce, to declare, to order"
    },
    {
      "question": "即する",
      "answer": "そくする",
      "meaning": "to conform to, to agree with, to be adapted to, to be based on"
    },
    {
      "question": "水洗い",
      "answer": "みずあらい",
      "meaning": "washing with cold water (without using soap, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "世襲",
      "answer": "せしゅう",
      "meaning": "heredity, heritage"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲調",
      "answer": "きょくちょう",
      "meaning": "melody, tune"
    },
    {
      "question": "生活態度",
      "answer": "せいかつたいど",
      "meaning": "way of living, manner of living, lifestyle"
    },
    {
      "question": "片耳",
      "answer": "かたみみ",
      "meaning": "one ear"
    },
    {
      "question": "世話好き",
      "answer": "せわずき",
      "meaning": "obliging person, person who likes looking after others"
    },
    {
      "question": "口が堅い",
      "answer": "くちがかたい",
      "meaning": "tight-lipped, able to keep a secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "三白眼",
      "answer": "さんぱくがん",
      "meaning": "sanpaku eyes (eyes with visible white between the iris and the lower eyelid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "商才",
      "answer": "しょうさい",
      "meaning": "business ability, business acumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "殴り込む",
      "answer": "なぐりこむ",
      "meaning": "to raid, to launch an attack, to invade"
    },
    {
      "question": "温床",
      "answer": "おんしょう",
      "meaning": "hotbed, breeding ground"
    },
    {
      "question": "吠え面",
      "answer": "ほえづら",
      "meaning": "tearful face"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛痒",
      "answer": "つうよう",
      "meaning": "pain and itching, mental anguish, unhealthy emotions"
    },
    {
      "question": "姪っ子",
      "answer": "めいっこ",
      "meaning": "niece"
    },
    {
      "question": "日和る",
      "answer": "ひよる",
      "meaning": "to wait and see, to sit on the fence, to be noncommittal"
    },
    {
      "question": "山内",
      "answer": "さんない",
      "meaning": "in the mountains, within the grounds of a temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し包む",
      "answer": "おしつつむ",
      "meaning": "to envelop, to blanket, to cloak"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴れ者",
      "answer": "しれもの",
      "meaning": "fool, dunce, idiot"
    },
    {
      "question": "貢ぎ物",
      "answer": "みつぎもの",
      "meaning": "tribute"
    },
    {
      "question": "老け込む",
      "answer": "ふけこむ",
      "meaning": "to age, to become old"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺繡",
      "answer": "ししゅう",
      "meaning": "embroidery"
    },
    {
      "question": "煎れる",
      "answer": "いれる",
      "meaning": "to be roasted, to be parched, to be irritated, to be annoyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "名付け",
      "answer": "なづけ",
      "meaning": "naming, christening, fiance, fiancee"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し花",
      "answer": "おしばな",
      "meaning": "pressed flower"
    },
    {
      "question": "相手役",
      "answer": "あいてやく",
      "meaning": "opposing role, partner"
    },
    {
      "question": "良縁",
      "answer": "りょうえん",
      "meaning": "good match, suitable candidate (for marriage), good opportunity to be saved by Buddha"
    },
    {
      "question": "望外",
      "answer": "ぼうがい",
      "meaning": "unexpected (joy, success, etc.), unanticipated, beyond what one hoped, beyond one's expectations"
    },
    {
      "question": "突発",
      "answer": "とっぱつ",
      "meaning": "outbreak, occurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "侍従長",
      "answer": "じじゅうちょう",
      "meaning": "grand chamberlain"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍医",
      "answer": "ぐんい",
      "meaning": "military physician or surgeon"
    },
    {
      "question": "安楽",
      "answer": "あんらく",
      "meaning": "comfort, ease"
    },
    {
      "question": "顚末",
      "answer": "てんまつ",
      "meaning": "details (of an incident, event, etc.), whole story, course of events, facts, circumstances, particul"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧家",
      "answer": "きゅうか",
      "meaning": "old family, old-established family, one's old home, one's childhood home"
    },
    {
      "question": "垂涎",
      "answer": "すいぜん,すいえん,すいせん",
      "meaning": "avid desire, craving, thirst, envy, watering at the mouth, drooling"
    },
    {
      "question": "前後不覚",
      "answer": "ぜんごふかく",
      "meaning": "unconsciousness, having no recollection of one's actions"
    },
    {
      "question": "臓",
      "answer": "ぞう",
      "meaning": "viscera, bowels"
    },
    {
      "question": "小路",
      "answer": "こうじ,しょうじ,こみち",
      "meaning": "lane, alley, path"
    },
    {
      "question": "裾野",
      "answer": "すその",
      "meaning": "foot of a mountain, plain at the foot of a mountain, range, spread, extent, encompassing circle"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛切",
      "answer": "つうせつ",
      "meaning": "keen, acute, heartfelt"
    },
    {
      "question": "生存競争",
      "answer": "せいぞんきょうそう",
      "meaning": "struggle for existence"
    },
    {
      "question": "医薬品",
      "answer": "いやくひん",
      "meaning": "medical and pharmaceutical products, medicinal supplies, drugs, pharmaceuticals, medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒天",
      "answer": "かんてん",
      "meaning": "freezing weather, agar-agar, vegetable gelatin"
    },
    {
      "question": "賽",
      "answer": "さい,さえ",
      "meaning": "dice, die, baton (of command)"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓜",
      "answer": "うり",
      "meaning": "melon, gourd"
    },
    {
      "question": "和睦",
      "answer": "わぼく",
      "meaning": "reconciliation, peace, rapprochement"
    },
    {
      "question": "横手",
      "answer": "よこて,よこで",
      "meaning": "side, beside, feature of a sword blade"
    },
    {
      "question": "飯屋",
      "answer": "めしや",
      "meaning": "eating house, restaurant that serves simple food"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺影",
      "answer": "いえい",
      "meaning": "portrait of deceased person"
    },
    {
      "question": "差配",
      "answer": "さはい",
      "meaning": "conduct of business, management, acting as agent (of a land owner, house owner, etc.), being in char"
    },
    {
      "question": "古木",
      "answer": "こぼく,ふるき",
      "meaning": "old tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩天楼",
      "answer": "まてんろう",
      "meaning": "skyscraper"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧い",
      "answer": "ふるい",
      "meaning": "old, aged, ancient, antiquated, antique, timeworn, long, since long ago, time-honored, of the distan"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭酸飲料",
      "answer": "たんさんいんりょう",
      "meaning": "carbonated drinks"
    },
    {
      "question": "安産",
      "answer": "あんざん",
      "meaning": "easy delivery, easy childbirth, safe birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒切れ",
      "answer": "ぼうきれ,ぼうぎれ",
      "meaning": "stick, piece of wood, billet, piece of a broken pole"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝っ玉",
      "answer": "きもったま",
      "meaning": "guts, pluck, nerve, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀製",
      "answer": "ぎんせい",
      "meaning": "made of silver"
    },
    {
      "question": "降り",
      "answer": "ふり,おり",
      "meaning": "rainfall, snowfall, alighting, descending, giving up on winning a hand and discarding only safe tile"
    },
    {
      "question": "一過性",
      "answer": "いっかせい",
      "meaning": "transient (symptom, phenomenon), temporary, passing, fleeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝え",
      "answer": "つたえ",
      "meaning": "legend, tradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "先攻",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "batting first"
    },
    {
      "question": "物理学",
      "answer": "ぶつりがく",
      "meaning": "physics"
    },
    {
      "question": "八方",
      "answer": "はっぽう",
      "meaning": "all sides, the four cardinal directions and the four ordinal directions, large hanging lantern"
    },
    {
      "question": "適宜",
      "answer": "てきぎ",
      "meaning": "suitable, appropriate, fitting, proper, appropriately, accordingly, as required, at one's discretion"
    },
    {
      "question": "程良い",
      "answer": "ほどよい",
      "meaning": "moderate, proper, just right"
    },
    {
      "question": "運任せ",
      "answer": "うんまかせ",
      "meaning": "leaving to chance, leaving to fate"
    },
    {
      "question": "凸",
      "answer": "でこ,とつ",
      "meaning": "brow, forehead, bump, convex"
    },
    {
      "question": "歴史学",
      "answer": "れきしがく",
      "meaning": "(study of) history"
    },
    {
      "question": "離婚届",
      "answer": "りこんとどけ",
      "meaning": "official divorce registration papers"
    },
    {
      "question": "作風",
      "answer": "さくふう",
      "meaning": "style (of a work, author, artist, etc.), characteristics"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭火",
      "answer": "すみび",
      "meaning": "charcoal fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "尼僧",
      "answer": "にそう",
      "meaning": "nun, priestess"
    },
    {
      "question": "緊縛",
      "answer": "きんばく",
      "meaning": "binding tightly, tight binding, (sexual) bondage"
    },
    {
      "question": "政変",
      "answer": "せいへん",
      "meaning": "political disturbance, political change, change of government, political upheaval, overthrowing of a"
    },
    {
      "question": "種火",
      "answer": "たねび",
      "meaning": "pilot light, spark, live coals (for firelighting)"
    },
    {
      "question": "保健所",
      "answer": "ほけんじょ,ほけんしょ",
      "meaning": "health care center, health care centre, animal shelter"
    },
    {
      "question": "気障",
      "answer": "きざ",
      "meaning": "affected, smug, pompous, conceited, snobby, pretentious"
    },
    {
      "question": "試験的",
      "answer": "しけんてき",
      "meaning": "experimental, provisional"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳が早い",
      "answer": "みみがはやい",
      "meaning": "being quick-eared, having sharp ears, being first to know about something"
    },
    {
      "question": "用兵",
      "answer": "ようへい",
      "meaning": "tactics"
    },
    {
      "question": "直帰",
      "answer": "ちょっき",
      "meaning": "returning home directly"
    },
    {
      "question": "世代交代",
      "answer": "せだいこうたい",
      "meaning": "alternation of generations"
    },
    {
      "question": "片腹痛い",
      "answer": "かたはらいたい",
      "meaning": "ridiculous, absurd"
    },
    {
      "question": "半田",
      "answer": "はんだ",
      "meaning": "solder, pewter"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関砲",
      "answer": "きかんほう",
      "meaning": "autocannon"
    },
    {
      "question": "位相",
      "answer": "いそう",
      "meaning": "phase (e.g. wave, electricity, moon), topology, register"
    },
    {
      "question": "縫い",
      "answer": "ぬい",
      "meaning": "embroidery, sewing"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤茶ける",
      "answer": "あかちゃける",
      "meaning": "to turn reddish-brown, to turn rufous, to become discolored, to become discoloured"
    },
    {
      "question": "糞尿",
      "answer": "ふんにょう",
      "meaning": "feces and urine, excreta, human waste"
    },
    {
      "question": "部屋割り",
      "answer": "へやわり",
      "meaning": "room allocation, assignment of rooms"
    },
    {
      "question": "喉仏",
      "answer": "のどぼとけ",
      "meaning": "laryngeal prominence, Adam's apple"
    },
    {
      "question": "単細胞",
      "answer": "たんさいぼう",
      "meaning": "single cell, simple-minded person, one-track-minded person"
    },
    {
      "question": "放任主義",
      "answer": "ほうにんしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "principle of laissez-faire"
    },
    {
      "question": "目くじら",
      "answer": "めくじら",
      "meaning": "corner of one's eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "与党",
      "answer": "よとう",
      "meaning": "ruling party, government party, party in power, government"
    },
    {
      "question": "正眼",
      "answer": "せいがん",
      "meaning": "holding one's sword pointing towards the opponent's eyes (kendo stance)"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け軸",
      "answer": "かけじく",
      "meaning": "hanging scroll"
    },
    {
      "question": "不釣合い",
      "answer": "ふつりあい",
      "meaning": "imbalance, disproportion, disparity, mismatch, asymmetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "日雇い",
      "answer": "ひやとい",
      "meaning": "daily employment, hiring by the day, day laborer, day labourer"
    },
    {
      "question": "火曜",
      "answer": "かよう",
      "meaning": "Tuesday"
    },
    {
      "question": "物見遊山",
      "answer": "ものみゆさん",
      "meaning": "going on a pleasure jaunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り倒す",
      "answer": "はりたおす",
      "meaning": "to knock down, to slap down, to floor"
    },
    {
      "question": "心配り",
      "answer": "こころくばり",
      "meaning": "exerting care, attention, consideration, thoughtfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "空模様",
      "answer": "そらもよう",
      "meaning": "look of the sky, weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き違う",
      "answer": "ゆきちがう,いきちがう",
      "meaning": "to cross (each other), to pass (each other), to misunderstand, to go amiss"
    },
    {
      "question": "海兵隊",
      "answer": "かいへいたい",
      "meaning": "Marine Corps, Royal Marines"
    },
    {
      "question": "糧食",
      "answer": "りょうしょく",
      "meaning": "provisions"
    },
    {
      "question": "支社",
      "answer": "ししゃ",
      "meaning": "branch office"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺骨",
      "answer": "いこつ",
      "meaning": "cremated remains (esp. the bones), ashes, remains (of war dead)"
    },
    {
      "question": "施策",
      "answer": "しさく",
      "meaning": "policy, measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "開眼",
      "answer": "かいがん,かいげん",
      "meaning": "enlightenment, spiritual awakening, opening one's eyes to the truth, gaining eyesight, restoring eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪戯っ子",
      "answer": "いたずらっこ",
      "meaning": "mischievous child, scamp, rascal, elf, imp"
    },
    {
      "question": "上昇気流",
      "answer": "じょうしょうきりゅう",
      "meaning": "ascending air current, updraft, upward trend, rise in popularity, influence, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "校外",
      "answer": "こうがい",
      "meaning": "out-of-school, off-campus"
    },
    {
      "question": "肺炎",
      "answer": "はいえん",
      "meaning": "pneumonia"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬服",
      "answer": "ふゆふく",
      "meaning": "winter clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "三々五々",
      "answer": "さんさんごご",
      "meaning": "in groups of twos and threes, in small groups"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝り",
      "answer": "しこり,こり,こごり",
      "meaning": "muscle stiffness (esp. in shoulders), lump (in tissue, esp. breast), swelling, hardening, lesion, li"
    },
    {
      "question": "写し取る",
      "answer": "うつしとる",
      "meaning": "to make a copy, to transcribe, to reproduce, to trace"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆撃機",
      "answer": "ばくげきき",
      "meaning": "bomber (aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白々",
      "answer": "しらじら,しらしら",
      "meaning": "growing light (e.g. at dawn), pale, appearing dumb, talking in an obvious way"
    },
    {
      "question": "山火事",
      "answer": "やまかじ",
      "meaning": "forest fire, bushfire, wildfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪天候",
      "answer": "あくてんこう",
      "meaning": "bad weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "後の世",
      "answer": "のちのよ",
      "meaning": "after ages, posterity, future life, the next world"
    },
    {
      "question": "切々",
      "answer": "せつせつ",
      "meaning": "passionate, fervent, affecting, moving, touching"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵送",
      "answer": "ゆうそう",
      "meaning": "mailing, posting"
    },
    {
      "question": "一葉",
      "answer": "いちよう,ひとは",
      "meaning": "one leaf, one page, one sheet, one card, one photo, one boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "値上がり",
      "answer": "ねあがり",
      "meaning": "price advance, increase in value"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝賀",
      "answer": "しゅくが",
      "meaning": "celebration, congratulations"
    },
    {
      "question": "婦女子",
      "answer": "ふじょし",
      "meaning": "women and children, woman, grown woman, wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "大黒柱",
      "answer": "だいこくばしら",
      "meaning": "central pillar (of a building), mainstay (e.g. of an economy), backbone (e.g. of a family), provider"
    },
    {
      "question": "うまい話",
      "answer": "うまいはなし",
      "meaning": "too-good-to-be-true offers (e.g. scams and frauds), too-good-to-be-true stories"
    },
    {
      "question": "鑢",
      "answer": "やすり",
      "meaning": "file, rasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "風雪",
      "answer": "ふうせつ",
      "meaning": "wind and snow, snowstorm, blizzard, hardships"
    },
    {
      "question": "特使",
      "answer": "とくし",
      "meaning": "special envoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "順路",
      "answer": "じゅんろ",
      "meaning": "(regular) route"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸",
      "answer": "すん",
      "meaning": "sun (approx. 3.03 cm), length, measurement, shortness, tininess"
    },
    {
      "question": "張りぼて",
      "answer": "はりぼて",
      "meaning": "papier mâché, something that looks good superficially"
    },
    {
      "question": "切れ込み",
      "answer": "きれこみ",
      "meaning": "cut, notch, incision"
    },
    {
      "question": "自棄",
      "answer": "やけ,じき",
      "meaning": "desperation, despair, self-abandonment"
    },
    {
      "question": "輝石",
      "answer": "きせき",
      "meaning": "pyroxene, augite"
    },
    {
      "question": "階位",
      "answer": "かいい",
      "meaning": "rank, order"
    },
    {
      "question": "建築家",
      "answer": "けんちくか",
      "meaning": "architect"
    },
    {
      "question": "綴り",
      "answer": "つづり",
      "meaning": "spelling, orthography, patching, binding"
    },
    {
      "question": "幾何学的",
      "answer": "きかがくてき",
      "meaning": "geometrical"
    },
    {
      "question": "所在地",
      "answer": "しょざいち",
      "meaning": "location, address"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻高々",
      "answer": "はなたかだか",
      "meaning": "proudly, triumphantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊女",
      "answer": "ゆうじょ",
      "meaning": "prostitute, harlot"
    },
    {
      "question": "前夜祭",
      "answer": "ぜんやさい",
      "meaning": "the eve (of a festival) (e.g. Christmas Eve)"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶接",
      "answer": "ようせつ",
      "meaning": "weld, welding"
    },
    {
      "question": "帯電",
      "answer": "たいでん",
      "meaning": "electrification"
    },
    {
      "question": "一律",
      "answer": "いちりつ",
      "meaning": "uniform, even, across-the-board, equal"
    },
    {
      "question": "原画",
      "answer": "げんが",
      "meaning": "original picture, key frame, key animation"
    },
    {
      "question": "叛逆",
      "answer": "はんぎゃく",
      "meaning": "treason, treachery, mutiny, rebellion, insurrection"
    },
    {
      "question": "除",
      "answer": "じょ",
      "meaning": "division"
    },
    {
      "question": "資本主義",
      "answer": "しほんしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "capitalism"
    },
    {
      "question": "排水溝",
      "answer": "はいすいこう",
      "meaning": "drainage, gutter, ditch"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯嚙み",
      "answer": "はがみ",
      "meaning": "grinding of the teeth, involuntary nocturnal tooth grinding, bruxism, grinding one's teeth out of an"
    },
    {
      "question": "目薬",
      "answer": "めぐすり",
      "meaning": "eye drops, eyewash"
    },
    {
      "question": "視聴率",
      "answer": "しちょうりつ",
      "meaning": "ratings (e.g. of a television program), audience rating, viewing rate"
    },
    {
      "question": "名医",
      "answer": "めいい",
      "meaning": "noted doctor, excellent physician"
    },
    {
      "question": "小出し",
      "answer": "こだし",
      "meaning": "(apportioning) in small amounts"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅ビル",
      "answer": "えきビル",
      "meaning": "station building"
    },
    {
      "question": "他方",
      "answer": "たほう",
      "meaning": "one (esp. of two), the other, one way, the other way, one direction, the other direction, one side,"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏食",
      "answer": "へんしょく",
      "meaning": "unbalanced diet"
    },
    {
      "question": "卒業証書",
      "answer": "そつぎょうしょうしょ",
      "meaning": "graduation certificate, diploma, testamur"
    },
    {
      "question": "一般教養",
      "answer": "いっぱんきょうよう",
      "meaning": "general education"
    },
    {
      "question": "余り物",
      "answer": "あまりもの",
      "meaning": "remains, leavings, remnant, surplus"
    },
    {
      "question": "電圧",
      "answer": "でんあつ",
      "meaning": "voltage"
    },
    {
      "question": "将官",
      "answer": "しょうかん",
      "meaning": "general, admiral"
    },
    {
      "question": "講和",
      "answer": "こうわ",
      "meaning": "reconciliation (between warring nations), (making of) peace"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅客機",
      "answer": "りょかくき,りょかっき",
      "meaning": "passenger plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "初期化",
      "answer": "しょきか",
      "meaning": "initialization, initialisation, formatting, resetting"
    },
    {
      "question": "発電所",
      "answer": "はつでんしょ",
      "meaning": "power plant, power station"
    },
    {
      "question": "出馬",
      "answer": "しゅつば",
      "meaning": "running (for election), coming forward as a candidate, going on horseback, going in person, letting"
    },
    {
      "question": "囀り",
      "answer": "さえずり",
      "meaning": "chirp, twitter, warble, whale tongue"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き当り",
      "answer": "つきあたり",
      "meaning": "end (of a street, hallway, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き込む",
      "answer": "ききこむ",
      "meaning": "to get information, to find out, to get wind of"
    },
    {
      "question": "同一視",
      "answer": "どういつし",
      "meaning": "viewing and treating as one, regarding as the same, equating one thing with another, identification"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛憎",
      "answer": "あいぞう",
      "meaning": "love and hate"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝導",
      "answer": "でんどう",
      "meaning": "conduction, transmission"
    },
    {
      "question": "小切手",
      "answer": "こぎって",
      "meaning": "cheque, check"
    },
    {
      "question": "下克上",
      "answer": "げこくじょう",
      "meaning": "juniors dominating seniors, inferiors overthrowing their superiors, retainer supplanting his lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "帳尻",
      "answer": "ちょうじり",
      "meaning": "closing part of a balance sheet, balance of accounts"
    },
    {
      "question": "俊足",
      "answer": "しゅんそく",
      "meaning": "swiftness of foot, fast runner, person of great talent, gifted person"
    },
    {
      "question": "積み木",
      "answer": "つみき",
      "meaning": "wooden building blocks, wooden bricks, playing with building blocks, piled timber, piling up wood"
    },
    {
      "question": "自認",
      "answer": "じにん",
      "meaning": "admission, (self-)acknowledgment, (self-)acknowledgement, self-identification"
    },
    {
      "question": "子役",
      "answer": "こやく",
      "meaning": "dramatic role for child, child actor"
    },
    {
      "question": "灯油",
      "answer": "とうゆ",
      "meaning": "kerosene, paraffin, lamp oil"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑魚寝",
      "answer": "ざこね",
      "meaning": "sleeping together in a huddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "禍根",
      "answer": "かこん",
      "meaning": "root of an evil, source of a problem, source of trouble, cause of misfortune"
    },
    {
      "question": "力自慢",
      "answer": "ちからじまん",
      "meaning": "boasting of one's strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "格上げ",
      "answer": "かくあげ",
      "meaning": "status elevation, upgrading, promotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "水田",
      "answer": "すいでん",
      "meaning": "(water-filled) paddy field"
    },
    {
      "question": "枝豆",
      "answer": "えだまめ",
      "meaning": "edamame (green soybeans)"
    },
    {
      "question": "老練",
      "answer": "ろうれん",
      "meaning": "experienced, veteran, skilled, expert"
    },
    {
      "question": "親鳥",
      "answer": "おやどり",
      "meaning": "parent bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸らす",
      "answer": "むらす",
      "meaning": "to cook by steam"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯加減",
      "answer": "ゆかげん",
      "meaning": "water temperature (esp. bath)"
    },
    {
      "question": "隊形",
      "answer": "たいけい",
      "meaning": "battle formation, disposition of troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "温泉宿",
      "answer": "おんせんやど",
      "meaning": "hot spring inn, hot spring hotel, hot spring resort"
    },
    {
      "question": "木炭",
      "answer": "もくたん",
      "meaning": "charcoal"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊泳",
      "answer": "ゆうえい",
      "meaning": "swimming, bathing, getting on in the world"
    },
    {
      "question": "被害届",
      "answer": "ひがいとどけ",
      "meaning": "filing a (criminal) complaint, reporting a crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "別枠",
      "answer": "べつわく",
      "meaning": "additional, extraordinary, outside the norms, special case"
    },
    {
      "question": "村落",
      "answer": "そんらく",
      "meaning": "village, hamlet, settlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "一合",
      "answer": "いちごう",
      "meaning": "180.39 millilitres, 180.39 milliliters, 0.3306 square metres, 0.3306 square meters, one-tenth of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "画用紙",
      "answer": "がようし",
      "meaning": "drawing paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "能無し",
      "answer": "のうなし",
      "meaning": "incompetence, ne'er-do-well, incompetent, dimwitted, brainless"
    },
    {
      "question": "念頭",
      "answer": "ねんとう",
      "meaning": "(on one's) mind, heed"
    },
    {
      "question": "地獄耳",
      "answer": "じごくみみ",
      "meaning": "sharp ear, long ears, ability to remember everything one hears"
    },
    {
      "question": "算",
      "answer": "さん",
      "meaning": "divining sticks, counting, calculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "倍加",
      "answer": "ばいか",
      "meaning": "doubling"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏地",
      "answer": "うらじ,うらち",
      "meaning": "lining, land that does not adjoin to public or private roads"
    },
    {
      "question": "オフ会",
      "answer": "オフかい",
      "meaning": "offline meeting (face-to-face meeting by people who normally interact online)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本堂",
      "answer": "ほんどう",
      "meaning": "main temple building, nave"
    },
    {
      "question": "律義",
      "answer": "りちぎ",
      "meaning": "upright, honest, faithful, conscientious, sincere"
    },
    {
      "question": "腎臓",
      "answer": "じんぞう",
      "meaning": "kidney"
    },
    {
      "question": "一丸",
      "answer": "いちがん",
      "meaning": "one lump, one body, one group"
    },
    {
      "question": "小町",
      "answer": "こまち",
      "meaning": "belle, (town) beauty"
    },
    {
      "question": "歩道橋",
      "answer": "ほどうきょう",
      "meaning": "pedestrian bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛味",
      "answer": "からみ,しんみ",
      "meaning": "hot taste, sharp taste, pungent taste, salty taste"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀傷",
      "answer": "かたなきず,とうしょう",
      "meaning": "sword wound, sword cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵情",
      "answer": "てきじょう",
      "meaning": "enemy movements, enemy's position"
    },
    {
      "question": "審美眼",
      "answer": "しんびがん",
      "meaning": "aesthetic sense, sense of beauty, eye for the beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち回り",
      "answer": "もちまわり",
      "meaning": "rotation (of a post, role, etc.), taking turns"
    },
    {
      "question": "念仏",
      "answer": "ねんぶつ",
      "meaning": "nenbutsu, nianfo, prayer to Amitabha Buddha, visualizing a Buddha (in one's mind)"
    },
    {
      "question": "野党",
      "answer": "やとう",
      "meaning": "opposition party, political opposition, opposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "矢筒",
      "answer": "やづつ",
      "meaning": "quiver"
    },
    {
      "question": "忘我",
      "answer": "ぼうが",
      "meaning": "trance, ecstasy, enthusiasm"
    },
    {
      "question": "一縷",
      "answer": "いちる",
      "meaning": "slightest connection, slender connection, sliver (e.g. of hope), one thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "気構え",
      "answer": "きがまえ",
      "meaning": "readiness, preparedness, attitude, kanji 'vapor' radical"
    },
    {
      "question": "同業",
      "answer": "どうぎょう",
      "meaning": "same trade, same business, same profession"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰砕け",
      "answer": "こしくだけ",
      "meaning": "collapsing in the middle of a bout, breaking down (while in the middle of something), faltering half"
    },
    {
      "question": "大山",
      "answer": "たいざん,おおやま",
      "meaning": "great mountain, big gamble, big plunge, big mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛行場",
      "answer": "ひこうじょう",
      "meaning": "airfield, airport"
    },
    {
      "question": "太平",
      "answer": "たいへい",
      "meaning": "peace, tranquility, tranquillity, happy-go-lucky"
    },
    {
      "question": "適役",
      "answer": "てきやく",
      "meaning": "suitable post or role"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿地",
      "answer": "しっち,しめじ",
      "meaning": "damp ground, wetland, bog, marsh, Lyophyllum shimeji (species of edible mushroom), euagaric fungus ("
    },
    {
      "question": "操縦士",
      "answer": "そうじゅうし",
      "meaning": "pilot"
    },
    {
      "question": "総体",
      "answer": "そうたい",
      "meaning": "all, the whole, on the whole, all in all, generally, all things considered"
    },
    {
      "question": "過つ",
      "answer": "あやまつ",
      "meaning": "to err"
    },
    {
      "question": "白湯",
      "answer": "さゆ,しらゆ,はくとう",
      "meaning": "(plain) hot water, boiled water"
    },
    {
      "question": "請け合い",
      "answer": "うけあい",
      "meaning": "assurance, guarantee"
    },
    {
      "question": "水温",
      "answer": "すいおん",
      "meaning": "water temperature"
    },
    {
      "question": "市警",
      "answer": "しけい",
      "meaning": "city police, municipal police"
    },
    {
      "question": "必要悪",
      "answer": "ひつようあく",
      "meaning": "necessary evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "現国",
      "answer": "げんこく",
      "meaning": "modern Japanese (esp. as a school subject)"
    },
    {
      "question": "表側",
      "answer": "おもてがわ",
      "meaning": "the front"
    },
    {
      "question": "再考",
      "answer": "さいこう",
      "meaning": "reconsideration"
    },
    {
      "question": "出家",
      "answer": "しゅっけ,すけ",
      "meaning": "entering the priesthood, priest, monk, bonze"
    },
    {
      "question": "伍",
      "answer": "ご,いつ,い",
      "meaning": "five, company, group, class, troop, rank, file"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊牧民",
      "answer": "ゆうぼくみん",
      "meaning": "nomad"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔球",
      "answer": "まきゅう",
      "meaning": "miracle ball, magic ball"
    },
    {
      "question": "清め",
      "answer": "きよめ",
      "meaning": "purification"
    },
    {
      "question": "腑",
      "answer": "ふ",
      "meaning": "internal organ, viscera, gut"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼食会",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょくかい",
      "meaning": "luncheon meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "意気地",
      "answer": "いくじ,いきじ",
      "meaning": "self-respect, self-confidence, guts, backbone, pride, drive, willpower"
    },
    {
      "question": "水脈",
      "answer": "すいみゃく,みお",
      "meaning": "water vein, underground stream of water, waterway, channel, wake (of a ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "北国",
      "answer": "きたぐに,ほっこく",
      "meaning": "northern country, northern provinces, northern regions, northland"
    },
    {
      "question": "拘留",
      "answer": "こうりゅう",
      "meaning": "custody, detention, confinement"
    },
    {
      "question": "殺人的",
      "answer": "さつじんてき",
      "meaning": "horrible, deadly, punishing, murderous"
    },
    {
      "question": "三枚目",
      "answer": "さんまいめ",
      "meaning": "comedian, actor who plays comic roles, figure of fun, laughing stock"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠者",
      "answer": "いんじゃ",
      "meaning": "hermit, recluse"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀河系",
      "answer": "ぎんがけい",
      "meaning": "Milky Way galaxy, Milky Way, the Galaxy, galactic system, galaxy"
    },
    {
      "question": "五芒星",
      "answer": "ごぼうせい",
      "meaning": "pentagram (as used in divination, etc.)"
    }
  ]
}
